This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</title>
<link> https://gamemonetize.com</link>
<description>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<atom:link href="https://gamemonetize.com" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<id>68369</id>
<title>Sprunky Rich Rich Rich</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Sprunky brothers fall into rivalry and start a competition. Both Sprunky brothers are very ambitious and want to win against each other. In this two-player game, the one who collects and deposits the most money into the piggy bank wins. Collect all the money before your brother and win the game. Be careful &mdash; dangerous objects are coming from everywhere. Dont hit them or youll lose the game!</description>
<instructions> Use WASD keys and Arrow Keys to move &bull; The first player to collect 50 coins wins the game &bull; Be careful while collecting money. Sharp blades come from the sides and above!</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Arena, Platform, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rjqx9s7cgzy7rtwescn049jwps2u2twv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rjqx9s7cgzy7rtwescn049jwps2u2twv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68334</id>
<title>Skibidi Toilet Melon Sandbox</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Skibidi Toilet Melon Sandbox, where youll embark on a journey in epic battlefield with brave warrior. These Casual Merge Games bring exquisite model and scene, immersing battle master in the strategic challenges between monsters and warriors. In Monster Battle toilet games, take on the role of a strategic Battle Master, defeating toilet warriors by synthesizing fight monster! Toilet games emphasize thinking, make key decisions that affect victory or defeat!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>Poppy Playtime, Sandbox, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/u1xads6x3swgts3gnmgdevln4ppa92qg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/u1xads6x3swgts3gnmgdevln4ppa92qg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68251</id>
<title>Tung TungBall and Labububall</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You must survive in the world of balls. Two friends, Tungball and Labububall, need your help. They must collect all the coins, escape from the forest, find the key, and unlock the castle gate. Both friends must reach the castle safely. Reach the castle safely and earn the right to move on to the next level. Be careful &mdash; if the shelled monsters catch you, you&rsquo;ll lose.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control *Collect all the coins and the golden key, then reach the gate.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Ball </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/t8cff8dsfvu1mrtphdb8jl7nkj9yjbxp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/t8cff8dsfvu1mrtphdb8jl7nkj9yjbxp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67163</id>
<title>Bank Boom Tung Tung Sahur</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for a bank heist? You have 20 seconds to crack the safe! Compete with your friend &mdash; the first to open the vault wins. Smash the safe open and beat your friend to it. Hit your friend with a club to slow them down and win the race. The club is a powerful weapon. The fate of the game is in your hands. Strike fast and unlock the bank vault!</description>
<instructions>&bull; Move using WASD or the Arrow Keys. &bull; Press S or the Down Arrow to swing the club. &bull; Playable on both mobile and PC. &bull; Stand on the vault for 20 seconds to open it and win the game.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, Battle, survival </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/48kgynv9m53l0aukny9c1ql383thrcjq/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/48kgynv9m53l0aukny9c1ql383thrcjq/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67617</id>
<title>Sprunki Dead Rails</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Sprunki Dead Rails - protect the train! Cooperative survival against zombies with block building. To make the game easier, you can buy a turret that will help destroy zombies. Play on one of 6 maps. The maps themselves are huge! Play with a friend, or in single player mode. The game has 15 Sprunki skins for both players, as well as 12 different blocks. The game has 4 types of weapons: pistol, PP, AK-47, RPG. </description>
<instructions>On a mobile device, controls are provided using on-screen buttons. On PC: - Blue player (main): &bull; Movement: arrow keys (&larr;, &rarr;, &uarr;, &darr;) &bull; Shoot: J &bull; Build: K - Red player: &bull; Movement: WASD &bull; Shoot: F &bull; Build: </instructions>
<category>Boys</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Best Games, Defense, Mobile, Shooter, Sprunki, Tower Defense, two player games, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/iixpxl3s6ss7gqrvced5eaysnigvw0os/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/iixpxl3s6ss7gqrvced5eaysnigvw0os/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67516</id>
<title>Labubu and Friends 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Labubu and his friend need to escape the island during summer! Be very careful as you adventure together and collect all the golden clams along the way. Of course, collect those golden clams first &mdash; then reach the giant gift box! Both adorable Labubu friends must make it to the gift box, because inside are their favorite things. But watch out &mdash; the path is full of dangers and obstacles!</description>
<instructions>*Use WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Collect all the Golden Clams and reach the Gift Box. *Playable on both mobile and PC.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/lv9gv1e4b0nnycb2h3v6chrzmsiwp1zr/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/lv9gv1e4b0nnycb2h3v6chrzmsiwp1zr/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64664</id>
<title>Stone Sheet Shears</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Unleash your strategy and reflexes in Stone Sheet Shears, a fast-paced, modern twist on the classic game of Rock, Paper, Scissors! Dive into a colorful and engaging world where you&rsquo;ll face off against opponents in exciting, high-stakes rounds of Stone (Crushes), Sheet (Wraps), and Shears (Slices). Test your decision-making in real-time battles, sharpen your instincts, and outthink your challengers to climb the leaderboard. With vibrant graphics, smooth animations, and multiple modes to explore, Stone Sheet Shears delivers both nostalgia and excitement in every match. </description>
<instructions>Use mice or tap!</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Casual, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qgcgsh667058s3w49a8dcsjqw2p8euf2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qgcgsh667058s3w49a8dcsjqw2p8euf2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67183</id>
<title>La Casa de Tung Tung Sahur</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Tung Tung Sahur Brothers are trying to rob a bank and need your help! Help them collect all the money in the bank. There are two silver keys you need to find&mdash;collect them all to reach the big vault. Open the vault and empty the bank! Play together with your friend and help the Tung Tung Sahur Brothers succeed.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Collect all the coins, find the red and blue keys, and open the bank vault. *Playable on both mobile and PC.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, attack, Tung Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2i1bs67w2y0ltciqn0d364wh7rzm411k/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2i1bs67w2y0ltciqn0d364wh7rzm411k/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65767</id>
<title>Domino Online Multiplayer</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Do you like strategy, excitement and duel battles? You will find different modes, flexible settings and strong opponents. Variety of modes: With a computer &ndash; hone your skills against AI of varying difficulty Online Duels - fight with live players in real time Play with a friend &ndash; send a link and play together, even from a distance On one screen &ndash; convenient for pair battles at home Flexible settings: 9 difficulty levels Time control Cancel the move Hints Rating and statistics Customization The history of moves Emotions and chat</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>2 Player, Board, Boy, Brain, Classic, Logic, Memory, Multiplayer, Puzzle, PvP </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cesnlh8sq40hoqm7t79vz7xnb1mzvnbx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cesnlh8sq40hoqm7t79vz7xnb1mzvnbx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65267</id>
<title>Underwater Aim</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Underwater Aim dives deep into the classic 8-ball pool experience&mdash;now with a refreshing underwater twist! Challenge your skills in beautifully designed ocean-themed tables where every shot feels smooth and satisfying. Line up your cue, calculate the angles, and sink all your balls before your opponent in this immersive pool game. From shimmering jellyfish lights to coral-lined pockets, each level is bursting with aquatic charm. Play solo, challenge friends, or compete in underwater tournaments. Unlock cues, explore sea-themed arenas, and become the ultimate pool shark of the deep. Cue up and make a splash in Underwater Aim!</description>
<instructions>Use mouse or touch scren for play game.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 8 Ball Pool, Pool </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/hksjgjkch7vvkjnpwboj6noif3qm8osd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/hksjgjkch7vvkjnpwboj6noif3qm8osd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66834</id>
<title>Hugli Wugli vs Tung Tung Sahur</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Hugli Wugli brothers are in danger! They&rsquo;re trapped in the dungeon and want to escape, but Tung Tung Sahur is trying to catch them. Avoid Tung Tung Sahur and escape the dungeon. To get out, you must find the red and blue keys. Collect the keys and help the Hugli Wugli brothers reach the dungeon door safely!</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Collect all the coins, find the red and blue keys, and head to the door. *Playable on both mobile and PC.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, huggy, Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/p5bhtgvycsyp72kvjav36mdr3enkd8oj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/p5bhtgvycsyp72kvjav36mdr3enkd8oj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66640</id>
<title>2 Player BlockMiner Escape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Miners, run quickly to the minecart! The miners have jumped in and are escaping from the giant zombie. Never look back and help Steve and Alex. They need to escape the mine, but first they must reach the gold chest at the end. Help them get to the gold chest. The mine is very dangerous &mdash; there are obstacles and spiders everywhere. Reach the gold chest safely!</description>
<instructions>*Press W or the Up Arrow key to jump *Playable on both mobile and PC *Double jump available</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Adventure, Arcade, Block, mineblock, Minecraft, Miner, Superhero </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1h6mir5kz3punj2p0b12iw94gp6tljm0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1h6mir5kz3punj2p0b12iw94gp6tljm0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66530</id>
<title>Red and Blue Hugli Wugli</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Hugli Wugli brothers are lost in the castle, and in the first game of the series, you must help them. These mischievous brothers have strapped hoverboards to their feet and are trying to escape from the castle. But beware &mdash; the castle is full of traps, and you need to be careful! Find the red and blue keys as quickly as possible. Watch out for the zombie in the castle &mdash; if you get caught, you lose.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Collect all the coins, find the red and blue keys, and head to the door. *Playable on both mobile and PC.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Boys, Cute, Girl, huggy, Kids, Platform, Poppy Playtime </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gt4qdl9f189axek4mc1se2stklu58o2e/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gt4qdl9f189axek4mc1se2stklu58o2e/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65911</id>
<title>Battle Tung Tung Sahur 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for the battle of the Tung Tung Sahurs? Two teams are fighting each other, and the one who reaches the chest wins the game. Get ready to fight alongside your friend. Hit your opponent with the sticks and win the game. The player who stays at the chest the longest will be the winner. To win the game, you must defeat your friend.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys to play. Press the S key to hit with the stick. *Use the Arrow keys to play. Press the Down Arrow key to hit with the stick. *Stay near the chest for 20 seconds to win the game.</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, Battle, Mobile, Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/oqdhfw0lgqnslcbui0vpeyqao696j1m5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/oqdhfw0lgqnslcbui0vpeyqao696j1m5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65691</id>
<title>Ludo King offline Ludo Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive into the world of Ludo Super, an all-in-one board game experience featuring Ludo, Bead 16, Tic Tac Toe, and Snakes &amp; Ladders! Connect with friends and family from around the globe, and engage in real-time voice chats for a truly interactive gaming experience. Whether youre a fan of classic board games or looking to make new friends through gaming, Ludo Super has something for everyone. </description>
<instructions>Mouse Controls</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 3D Games, Best Games, Board, free games for your site, free games for your website, free html5 games for your website, Games, Multiplayer, onlinegames io </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e8vfdarke5qjx5uemefer4jtnbo3dc01/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e8vfdarke5qjx5uemefer4jtnbo3dc01/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>960</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65912</id>
<title>GunMyTungtungSahur 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Tung Tung Sahur brothers are very angry. Both of them are furious with each other now. You must help them in their battle together with your friend. Grab a weapon and let the fastest one win. You need to collect the drops falling from the sky. The one who gets hit the most loses the battle. Fight your friend and win this war. Take the drop to get a more powerful weapon.</description>
<instructions>*The red player moves using the WASD keys. *The blue player moves using the arrow keys. *The one who gets hit 20 times loses.</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Battle, Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6boqqttzooqr6azcr6vqqdy44et5pvpp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6boqqttzooqr6azcr6vqqdy44et5pvpp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60541</id>
<title>Santa Giftbox 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Be very careful, yes, the New Year has arrived, and Santa Claus and the Green Monster need to race. You need to be either the Green Monster or Santa Claus and hold the gift box in your hands. The one who holds the most gift boxes by the time the timer runs out wins. Take the gift box and avoid your friend, dont let them take it from you. To win the game, hold onto the gift box until the time runs out.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys or the Arrow Keys to move. *Hold the gift box for 2 minutes to win the game. *When time runs out, the player holding the gift box wins.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Christmas, mineblock, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/nngjr5g2xn0wa47v5g7q1rblajzq3hza/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/nngjr5g2xn0wa47v5g7q1rblajzq3hza/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65510</id>
<title>Othello Five</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Classic Othello with a twist - get 5 in a row to win! Flip your opponents stones by trapping them between yours, but victory comes from creating a line of 5 consecutive stones or eliminating all opponent pieces. Three AI difficulty levels: Easy: For beginners Normal: Casual challenge Hard: Strategic mastery Features: - Modern interface with animations - Play against AI or a friend - See AIs thinking process - Track your stats Perfect for quick games or deep strategy sessions.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2D, Board, Casual, Hypercasual, Strategy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/wdff7m73hqjk029wulmw15id0tcjkz43/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/wdff7m73hqjk029wulmw15id0tcjkz43/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>800</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64607</id>
<title>TICTAK TOE play AI easy hard</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Option 1: Short &amp; Catchy (Tagline / Very Short Description) Classic Tic Tac Toe: Reimagined! Play PvP or challenge Easy/Hard AI. Modern Tic Tac Toe Fun! Battle friends or test your skills against the AI. Sleek Tic Tac Toe: PvP &amp; AI Modes. Quick games, endless fun! Option 2: Medium Description (Standard Portal / App Store Description) Enjoy the timeless fun of Tic Tac Toe with a fresh, modern twist! Challenge your friends in local Player vs Player mode, test your skills against our casual Easy AI, or face a true test with the strategic Hard AI opponent. Featuring a sleek design with smooth animations, clear visual feedback, and a dynamic backg</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play and enjoy game </instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>HTML5, html5 games, html5 games for your site, Interactive, Match3, Puzzle, puzzleblock </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/a3bmdrog6l9466oe54492y1ngxl6e7b2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/a3bmdrog6l9466oe54492y1ngxl6e7b2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65123</id>
<title>Dog and Cat Sweet</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for the adventure of Dog and Cat? A super exhausting journey awaits you. There are obstacles everywhere, and you must be very careful. The cat and dog must be like siblings. They need to work together as a team; otherwise, they wont reach the doghouse at the finish line. They must collect all the food they find on the way because the cat and dog must not go hungry. Gather all the food you find, watch out for obstacles, cross the bridge and the iron gate, and reach the doghouse.</description>
<instructions>*Move using the WASD and Arrow Keys. *Only the dog can open the bridge and the iron gate. *Playable on both mobile and PC. *Collect all the cat and dog food and reach the doghouse.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Animal, Arcade, Boys, Cat, Girls, Kid, Kids </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/15qh6hiivgium85ak4oh9u5rwe1l4svq/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/15qh6hiivgium85ak4oh9u5rwe1l4svq/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64974</id>
<title>Helicopter Battle Steve 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Get on the helicopter and choose either the blue or red player. Destroy your friend&rsquo;s helicopter to win the game.Winning is simple: just don&rsquo;t let your helicopter crash! Jump and shoot to defeat your opponent. To beat the red or blue player, you must play your best. The player whose helicopter explodes the most will lose the game.</description>
<instructions>*To use the red helicopter, press the W key. *To use the blue helicopter, press the Up Arrow Key. *The first to reach 10 points wins.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Arcade, Arena, Battle, fly </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zlpj0cuc8qtjtptpl8o7t5jqtes478wz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zlpj0cuc8qtjtptpl8o7t5jqtes478wz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64702</id>
<title>Retro Pong</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into gaming history with Retro Pong, a digital revival of the classic arcade experience! This simple yet legendary game pits two paddles against each other in a fast-paced volley of bouncing pixels. Score by sending the ball past your opponent&mdash;first to 5 wins! Perfect for quick breaks or friendly showdowns, this old-school gem proves that sometimes, the simplest games are the most addictive. Are you quick enough to claim victory?</description>
<instructions>Control is available for one or two players using the keyboard.</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2D, Arcade, Arkanoid, Ball, Best, Bounce, free games for your site, Fun, HTML5, Hypercasual, Multiplayer, Retro, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/u3h8dwolvxrk64ubak2speaguqywravz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/u3h8dwolvxrk64ubak2speaguqywravz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64891</id>
<title>Sprunki Happy Easter 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Sprunki brothers are competing against each other this Easter. The player who collects the most Easter eggs wins the game. Show your sibling or friend that youre the better player. Collect the eggs as fast as you can and bring them to the chest. Whoever delivers the most eggs to the chest wins the game.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *The player who collects 20 eggs wins. *Take the egg from the balloon and bring it to the chest. *Mobile touch control available.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Easter, Pixel, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/oob75i4ksvub445ck5q3adkw0piwsu0l/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/oob75i4ksvub445ck5q3adkw0piwsu0l/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64322</id>
<title>tic tak to </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Tic Tac Toe Game - Description &amp; Controls Game Description This Tic Tac Toe game is a modern, interactive version of the classic two-player strategy game. Players take turns marking X or O on a 3&times;3 grid, aiming to get three of their symbols in a row (horizontally, vertically, or diagonally). Game Features: Two-Player Mode (Player X vs. Player O) Score Tracking (Wins are recorded) Winner Announcement (Popup when a player wins or its a draw) Responsive Design (Works on mobile &amp; desktop) Simple &amp; Clean UI (Easy to play)</description>
<instructions> Controls 1 How to Play: Click/Tap on any empty cell to place your X or O. Players take turns automatically. The first player to get 3 in a row wins! If all cells are filled with no winner, its a draw. 2 Game Buttons: Play Again Button (Resets the game bu</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>2 Player, Stickman </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/vhwpg74ut6qx4jpq2zaun36b5083v3i4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/vhwpg74ut6qx4jpq2zaun36b5083v3i4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64413</id>
<title>Sprunki 456 Squid Cookie</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Sprunki brothers have invaded the entire forest and theyre everywhere. You must help the turquoise and red-suited brothers to reach the cash register as quickly as possible. Help all the brothers. Collect the cookies and reach the cash register. Throw cookies at the Sprunki brothers and defeat them.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Double jump is enabled. *Collect all the cookies and find the golden key.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Sprunki, squid, squidgame </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yv9zfw3upjb12a2hmnll9m49c57poyir/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yv9zfw3upjb12a2hmnll9m49c57poyir/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64187</id>
<title>Sprunki Horror Version Dark</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The world of the Sprunki characters has turned into a terrifying place, with everything scattered and surrounded by darkness and blood. To escape this dark world, never, ever stop and reach the portal. You need to reach the portal. Be careful in the dark forest, as there are thorns and terrifying traps everywhere. Be very careful and reach the portal safely.</description>
<instructions>Press the WASD keys to move. *Mobile touch controls are available. *Reach the portal safely.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Cartoon, Pixel, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m7jq7ijmk3ra8i2jjy1nm9te3vekdow1/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m7jq7ijmk3ra8i2jjy1nm9te3vekdow1/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63001</id>
<title>2Player Tanks of War</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for a realistic tank battle? Now, get ready to fight in a tank battle with your friend on 8 different maps. Fight with your friend, and the one with the most hits lost will lose. In the game, you can also buy a galaxy costume if you want. Blow up your friend the most and you&rsquo;ll win the battle. The fight is really tough, so you must be very careful. Blow up your friend and victory will be yours. A two-player tank battle game.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow Keys to move. *Use the Q and P keys to fire the tank. *A never-ending tank battle game. *8 different maps.</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/etvwt8f327x14otf6ftwsj3g6zjmxfp4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/etvwt8f327x14otf6ftwsj3g6zjmxfp4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63888</id>
<title>Apocalypse Rush</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Apocalypse Rush is a fast-paced survival game where you must defend your trailer against endless waves of enemies! Arm yourself with various weapons, collect coins for upgrades, and try to survive as long as possible. The longer you last, the more challenging the game becomes! Are you ready for the chaos?</description>
<instructions> Controls Player 1 Move: Arrow Keys Shoot: K Special Attack: L Player 2 Move: W, A, S, D Shoot: C Special Attack: V Survive the endless apocalypse and unleash powerful attacks! </instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, apocalypse, Best Games, Defense, Enemies, free games for your site, free games for your website, free html5 games for your website, Fun, Games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yp4fk09eq150ovmu0hhii0v3s1gph4zr/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yp4fk09eq150ovmu0hhii0v3s1gph4zr/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63812</id>
<title>Sprunki Lava Escape 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Together with your friend, you must save the Sprunki characters from the rising lava. You must be very careful. The lava is rising, and youre in danger. Escape the lava with 6 different characters and jump as high as you can. An endless jumping and lava escape awaits you. Collect all the music notes along the way. You need the music notes.</description>
<instructions>Use the WASD keys to move and jump in the game. Use the Arrow Keys keys to move and jump in the game. *Mobile Control Available </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/nm9f14h5afstuwu8l4tywu40cita6cs0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/nm9f14h5afstuwu8l4tywu40cita6cs0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63582</id>
<title>Sprunki vs MCCraft</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Sprunki team has fallen into the McCraft world, and they want to escape and return to their own world. Help the Sprunki siblings and make sure they escape this world. Dont forget, the McCraft world is very dangerous, and there are many powerful monsters here that want to eat them. To defeat the monsters, throw music notes at them. Defeat all the monsters and reach the portal at the end of the game.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Defeat all the monsters and reach the portal safely. *Collect all the music notes in the forest. *Guide the Sprunki siblings to the end of the level safely.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Minecraft, Mobile, Pixel, Platform, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/l0xnsvo70hdy3xl74cs83d8mjjyjlx5f/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/l0xnsvo70hdy3xl74cs83d8mjjyjlx5f/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63287</id>
<title>Baby Noob vs Baby Obby Horse</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Two baby siblings need to find a key and a chest in the forest. Help the baby siblings find the key and, after finding it, open the chest with the key. There are terrifying animals in the forest, so you must be very careful. To defeat the animals in the forest, you should throw bottles. The bottle is a very powerful weapon, so dont hesitate to use it. Collect the lollipops in the forest. The babies love lollipops, so dont forget to collect them.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and arrow keys to move. *Press the P key to throw the bottle. *There are 12 different challenging levels. *Double jump is enabled.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Animal, Block, Horse, Minecraft, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qoi0njrme4iwwxsawr338w1592i3loeu/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qoi0njrme4iwwxsawr338w1592i3loeu/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61671</id>
<title>Turkish draughts</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The main feature is that moves and captures with checkers are made horizontally and vertically, and not diagonally, as in most popular types of checkers. Accordingly, the initial arrangement of checkers is different. On a 64-cell board, opponents place their 16 checkers on all cells of the second and third horizontals. You can play the game with artificial intelligence, with another person on one device, or with an opponent online in multiplayer mode. You can also watch other players play, act as a spectator, or suggest your own version of the next move to the player by making it on the board.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>2 Player Games, Board, Brain, Classic, Multiplayer, two player games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/d2gokou3otdsj4x3y2l09gxx4ktk1okw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/d2gokou3otdsj4x3y2l09gxx4ktk1okw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63230</id>
<title>Sprunki Team</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>All the Sprunki timin want to escape from the forest. There is a mysterious monster in the forest that scares everyone. Time is running out. Escape before time runs out and stay safe. Reach the blue door. Collect the gold and green money. Dont forget anything and never look back. Escape with your friend, dont stop.</description>
<instructions>*Use WASD Keys to move and jump. *First, collect the gold coin, and then collect the green coin. *Both mobile and desktop playability.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/biaritszahsq40psbz7emoq58safe8vu/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/biaritszahsq40psbz7emoq58safe8vu/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63028</id>
<title>Tank Soccer Battle 1 2 3 4 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for a tank battle with your friends? A tank battle with a soccer ball! Bring your friends and fight with tanks.Fill up your tanks&rsquo; ammunition and blow up all your friends&rsquo; tanks. While blowing up your friends&rsquo; tanks, don&rsquo;t forget to shoot the soccer ball. The player who gets the soccer ball to the goal wins. You need to score a goal to win. Team up with your friend in a 2vs2 game and work together to score a goal.</description>
<instructions>*Green Tank: Use WASD to move and Q to fire *Blue Tank: Use Arrow Keys to move and P to fire *Yellow Tank: Use UHJK to move and M to fire *Red Tank: Use FCVB to move and N to fire</instructions>
<category>Soccer</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Arcade, attack, Casual, Tank, Tanks </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cb3avofz0w2mb5dfykhoq88540ae7f0a/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cb3avofz0w2mb5dfykhoq88540ae7f0a/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63010</id>
<title>1 2 3 4 Player Tank Game 2D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for the legendary tank battles? Gather all your friends and start the tank war.All tanks take their positions and the endless battle begins. The tank that destroys the most of your friends tanks wins. In this fun tank battle game, compete with your friends and be the one who destroys the most tanks. Be careful, its not about being fast, but being smart that will lead you to victory.</description>
<instructions>*Green Tank: Use WASD to move and Q to fire *Blue Tank: Use Arrow Keys to move and P to fire *Black Tank: Use UHJK to move and M to fire *Red Tank: Use FCVB to move and N to fire</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Tank, Tanks </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/p9pb620g5wsc78hjtez664cev0ibae6d/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/p9pb620g5wsc78hjtez664cev0ibae6d/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62293</id>
<title>Pixcade 2 Player Escape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The twin siblings need to escape from the house. Help the twins and ensure they manage to escape. Find two keys and escape the house. The house is like a prison, and the two siblings must escape. They need to find both keys and collect all the coins to escape. To get out of the house, you and your friend must stay close together, finding and collecting everything that needs to be found without straying too far from each other.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Double jump is enabled. *Find and collect both keys, and gather all the coins.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Arcade, Casual, Escape </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/mvmjkf5ad4s4hp5pek2mxdf303yivfnm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/mvmjkf5ad4s4hp5pek2mxdf303yivfnm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62423</id>
<title>Dominoes classic duel</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>A board game in which a chain of dominoes (bones, stones) is built, touching halves with the same number of dots indicating the number of points. You can play the game with artificial intelligence or with an opponent online in multiplayer mode. A classic set has 28 dominoes, they are also called stones or bones. These rectangles are divided into 2 parts, each with dots from 0 to 6. Two players play the game. At the beginning of the game, 7 bones are dealt to each player. The remaining ones are kept aside in reserve, with the clean side up (on the market). The player who has a double 6-6 starts, he puts up a bone. The next players place</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Board, Classic, Multiplayer, two player games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/l3njgmefn0e3h9ih3zyhyctgjj2jlpsv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/l3njgmefn0e3h9ih3zyhyctgjj2jlpsv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62489</id>
<title>Stickman Huggy Party Duo</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Red and Blue Huggy Stickmen need to work together to escape the terrifying temple prison. They must find the key and reach the door to open it. Collect all the gold in the prison. Be very careful, as there are many dangerous obstacles in the prison. Overcome the obstacles, avoid the toxic water, and reach the door safely. Together with your friend, guide the red and blue stickmen to the door.</description>
<instructions>*Press the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Double jump is activated. *Find the golden key and go to the door.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, huggy, Platform, Poppy Playtime </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/us299ne1hbpos1ahpnu22jzl6rmr9xz0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/us299ne1hbpos1ahpnu22jzl6rmr9xz0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61370</id>
<title>Squid Obby Game 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hey players, you need to be fast. Collect all the shapes nonstop and help your friend escape from the prison. Escape before time runs out and reach the helicopter. The helicopter is waiting for you, hurry up. And dont forget, be careful of the guys in red uniforms. If they catch you, you lose. Be quick, hurry, and escape from the prison to reach the helicopter.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys and the Arrow keys to move. *Both players must reach the helicopter before the 40-second timer runs out. *Reach the helicopter safely. *You must collect all the shapes in the level.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel, squid, squidgame </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/tjw1x8uvaxn755yvq8w5458o0j9iwaea/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/tjw1x8uvaxn755yvq8w5458o0j9iwaea/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62298</id>
<title>MCBros PixelCraft</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In the adventure of Steve and Alex, you need to help them. They must collect all the diamonds. Be very careful while collecting the diamonds. There are many thorny obstacles both inside the cave and outside. Dont forget, there are monsters in the cave, and they are very dangerous. To get rid of the monsters, jump on them and crush them. This way, you can defeat all the monsters and reach the portal at the end of the level. Be careful and make sure both players reach the portal safely.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow Keys to move. *Double jump is enabled. *Collect all the coins and find the key and chests.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Adventure, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft, Pixel, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/naecvvaggklei84wmnmiwfdmid5jhqu0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/naecvvaggklei84wmnmiwfdmid5jhqu0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57677</id>
<title>Player Bomber 2d 4 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is a 4 Player Bomber game where you have to bomb the walls with the Bomb and you can instantiate one bomb at a time and you can also play with 4 players to this game.</description>
<instructions>Use WASD Keys to move Player 1 Left Shift for Bomb</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player Games, 2D, Block </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/xikw2i1nv9n5cqnfqgnqj4jevf50rlsk/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/xikw2i1nv9n5cqnfqgnqj4jevf50rlsk/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62289</id>
<title>Pixcade Squid</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In the world of the twin pixel brothers, there are chests they need to collect, and they must gather the chests to move on to the next level. Of course, collecting the chests wont be easy. While collecting the chests, there are coins they need to gather as well. They must collect all the coins and complete the level. Help the brothers and assist them in completing the level.</description>
<instructions>*Press WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Find and collect the two chests and coins. *Be careful of the spikes on the map.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/awz10upstscb0bif43sxx3pe3tq47wlg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/awz10upstscb0bif43sxx3pe3tq47wlg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60861</id>
<title>X O Battle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>X-O Battle is the perfect choice for players who enjoy fast-paced puzzle games and strategic challenges. With its combination of classic gameplay, modern design, and mobile compatibility, it provides an exciting and immersive gaming experience for casual players and puzzle lovers alike. Whether youre looking for a fun way to pass the time or aiming to become the ultimate Tic-Tac-Toe champion, this game offers endless entertainment. Play now and enjoy the ultimate Tic-Tac-Toe challenge anytime, anywhere!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Board, Casual, Strategy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yeqh7inen60dcrtwluqfcgp1bubl7god/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yeqh7inen60dcrtwluqfcgp1bubl7god/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61829</id>
<title>Squid Escape But Blockworld</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You need to escape from the Squid competition, but while running away, you fell into the Block world. It&rsquo;s a bit hard to escape from the Block world, but don&rsquo;t stop and keep running. Never stop running until you reach the purple portal. Don&rsquo;t forget to collect the money you see on the way. Be careful of the big monsters chasing you from behind; they want to catch you, and if they do, you&rsquo;ll lose.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *To survive, run to the portal at the end of the level and be careful of obstacles.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7j45fxwmc08v7zvi4zac82w6qmvcpdue/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7j45fxwmc08v7zvi4zac82w6qmvcpdue/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61380</id>
<title>Combo Snake</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Control the snake to move and collect gems. Collecting gems of the same color will create nodes of the corresponding color on the snakes body. When three nodes of the same color are connected, they will be automatically eliminated. Eliminating nodes can earn you extra points. Hitting the wall or colliding with itself will lead to the end of the game. Successfully eliminating the entire snakes body results in a game victory.</description>
<instructions>Computer: Use the arrow keys to control. Mobile phone: Tap the screen to control the direction.</instructions>
<category>Bejeweled</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/s3qipzsmowz03sobcyid3h15cn3zssfv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/s3qipzsmowz03sobcyid3h15cn3zssfv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>800</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61704</id>
<title>MCraft TNT 2 Player Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you up for an intense challenge with your friends? You should compete against your friend.Its the perfect time for a race with your friend. The one who collects flying TNTs the fastest wins. There are two teams, red and blue. The team that collects the most TNTs wins. The first to collect 20 TNTs wins. You must collect them before your friend does. Catch the TNTs flying in the air.</description>
<instructions>*The red player moves using the WASD keys. *The blue player moves using the arrow keys. *Collect the TnT and bring it to the chest.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/im338qab7zdca1svduu0hxodibvkiddo/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/im338qab7zdca1svduu0hxodibvkiddo/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61705</id>
<title>Hammer Climb MinisCrafter</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>hey you player! Have you ever moved with a friend using just a hammer? you even have to use a hammer to do it back and forth.Use the hammer to move and reach the lucky box at the end of the level, and when you reach it with your friend, you will have the right to pass to the next level. Dont forget there are obstacles in the game, you have to be very careful.</description>
<instructions>*Use WASD Keys to play player 1. *Use Arrow keys to play player 2. *The game can be played on mobile.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2aw9424lk5zwww93mc0zqhk6wgz2wj4n/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2aw9424lk5zwww93mc0zqhk6wgz2wj4n/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61372</id>
<title>Squid Escape Game 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You must escape from this iron-covered labyrinth prison. Both blue players need to escape the prison. You must collect all the geometric shapes. Collect all the shapes and find both keys. Find the keys and run to the door. Be very careful, there are thorny obstacles on the ground. Dont stray too far from your friend; if you lose each other, you will lose the game.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys and the Arrow keys to move. *Both players must reach the door safely and complete the level. *You must collect all the shapes in the level.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ptog1yv2rirz05wbsbtvc396j280xso8/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ptog1yv2rirz05wbsbtvc396j280xso8/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61159</id>
<title>Duo Skibidi 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Two red and blue camera men need to break the toilets. The toilets have risen and want to be broken. Break the blue and red toilets, collect all the money. You must be very careful. Enemies are everywhere and each level is filled with challenges. You can lose at any moment. Break the toilets carefully. Break the blue and red toilets, collect the money, and move to the next level.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Jump on the toilets to break them. *Double jump available. *Collect all the money.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cuiguucd2ffqvopk1i2t8tsv7fzntu3n/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cuiguucd2ffqvopk1i2t8tsv7fzntu3n/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61171</id>
<title>Two Player Stick Steve and Alex</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Steve and Alex, the stick figure characters, want to escape from the Nether world. To help them in this adventure, you must be two players. In this two-player game, you must escape from the Nether world with your friend. Be very careful while escaping because monsters are coming from everywhere and they never stop. Reach the portal at the end of the level safely.</description>
<instructions>Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Avoid the monster at the end of the level and reach the portal at the end. *Double jump available.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gi0ramqaafpynar1wey5eb5xvh2n5md7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gi0ramqaafpynar1wey5eb5xvh2n5md7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60897</id>
<title>Youtuber Mcraft 2Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You need to help the YouTuber girl and her boyfriend escape from prison. In this two-player adventure, they must collect all the YouTube plaques without getting too far apart, obtain the key and the golden plaque, and reach the chest. Open the chest and run to the door. You need to be very fast, you must escape from prison!</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD and Arrow keys to move. *Double Jump available. *Collect all YouTube plaques and find the key. *After finding the key, reach the chest.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7hnht9qa27besyoif2tiofvur8mqnym2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7hnht9qa27besyoif2tiofvur8mqnym2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59344</id>
<title>Sweet Dolls Fashion Princess</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is a dress-up and decorating game for girls. Here you can customize your favorite characters and dress them up. The game offers a wide range of styles of clothes and accessories to choose from to dazzle you. You can also accumulate gold coins for exchanging for pets and caring for them.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Baby Games, Dress Up </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/0cbaawo0asqeb3czgly0bpejvwcvmnjp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/0cbaawo0asqeb3czgly0bpejvwcvmnjp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60313</id>
<title>Minesweeper Duel</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Compete with friends one-on-one online. Play for free against computer. Minesweeper Duel is a new mode for the game familiar from childhood for the mind and logic In a one-on-one competition, you open the cells in turn with your opponent and get points equal to the face value of the open cell. The player with the highest score wins. The player who stumbles upon a mine loses immediately. Available field sizes: - Newbie - Amateur - Professional Time for thinking is limited, choose different modes: - The bullet - Blitz - Classic</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2048, 2D, Brain, Educational, Logic, Logical, Math, Memory, Mobile, Multiplayer, Puzzle, PvP, Turn Based </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/mhp0ae8pj0i7r9f5aaxohl1tuhdplkw9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/mhp0ae8pj0i7r9f5aaxohl1tuhdplkw9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60223</id>
<title>Baby Noob vs Heroman 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Baby Noob and Heroman are lost in the forest. They need to reach home safely. Baby Noob is a master at unlocking chests, so he must open all the chests in the forest and find the mysterious key hidden deep in the forest at a house. Although Heroman is fearless, the monsters are huge and enormous, so he must be very careful. To defeat the monsters, he should use his sword. Some houses have iron doors, and he must use his sword to break those doors. Collect all the diamonds and find the key.</description>
<instructions>* Use the WASD and Arrow Keys to move. *Press the P key to throw the sword. *Playable on both mobile and PC. *Collect all the diamonds and obtain the golden key. *Find both chests in the game. *Reach the house at the end of the game safely.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/82rtwcjengxh8wh6tg4kq45wmaiumpp0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/82rtwcjengxh8wh6tg4kq45wmaiumpp0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60362</id>
<title>Grench vs Santa</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>New Years has arrived, and a terrifying New Years monster has appeared! The green New Years monster wants to steal the gift boxes. Before the green monster can take the boxes, Santa must urgently grab them and put them into the chest. Santa has a tough mission ahead&mdash;he must quickly collect all the gift boxes and secure them in the safe chest. Its the perfect time to play with your friend, beat them, and win the game!</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys and the Arrow Keys to move. *The player who collects the most gift boxes in the shortest time wins. *Choose one of the 4 different hats.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Block, Minecraft, Mobile, Pixel, Santa, Santa Claus </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ohtw9zyg734saqan70abiz3r8jtf0ajg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ohtw9zyg734saqan70abiz3r8jtf0ajg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55470</id>
<title>Noob vs Pro Chicken</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready to compete with your friend in this adventure? One of you will be a NOOB, and the other will be a PRO. The player who collects the fastest chickens will win. To win this fun competition, you need to collect all the chickens before your friend does. Gather the chickens and bring them to the coop to win. The player who collects the fastest chickens wins the game. Be careful, the chickens are very fast and may escape, so catching them will be a bit challenging. Play with your friend and win this fun competition.</description>
<instructions>*Move using the WASD keys and the arrow keys. *The first player to collect 10 chickens wins. *The player who collects the most chickens before time runs out wins. *Mobile controls available.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ww9kzir5202mimwipvq5fwziveg0fzi5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ww9kzir5202mimwipvq5fwziveg0fzi5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59302</id>
<title>2 Player Online Chess</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Jump into the timeless fun of chess with 2 Player Online Chess! Play solo against the computer or team up with a friend for a match in 2 Player mode. With a simple, easy-to-use design, it&rsquo;s all about having a great time while sharpening your skills. Ready to make your first move? Let the game begin!</description>
<instructions>Use your mouse or swipe with your finger to control the action</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Board, Brain, Casual, Classic, Educational, Fun, Game, Games, HTML5, html5 games, Strategy, Train </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/tgsetdb6p6hq5xt6a1uz2se32gfjeo4l/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/tgsetdb6p6hq5xt6a1uz2se32gfjeo4l/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>768</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59333</id>
<title>Nubiks build a defense vs zombies</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Nubiks build a defense vs zombies - a game with elements of construction and survival. Build defenses and survive against waves of zombies! Who will be eaten first? The game has a single player mode. But the whole game is focused on a two-person mode, and all the fun is there, so lets call friends and have fun!</description>
<instructions>PC management: Blue is the arrow keys, while the down arrow is the build. Red WAD - movement, S - build. There is a double jump in the game! On a mobile device, control using on-screen buttons.</instructions>
<category>Boys</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, Ghost, mineblock, Minecraft, Mobile, Monster, Sandbox, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ypk4vwpjaia00rdje91pp17emhjv3tmb/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ypk4vwpjaia00rdje91pp17emhjv3tmb/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>640</width>
<height>480</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55447</id>
<title>Friends Battle Knock Down</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, two fighting friends need to push each other off a cliff. In this fun game, push your friend off the cliff. To throw them off, just push them. Be careful as TNT falls from the sky, and if it explodes, it can knock you down too. Avoid the TNT to stay safe and win the game by being the one who knocks the most enemies down.</description>
<instructions>*Press the S key or the Down Arrow key to push or hit. *The player with the most points in 120 seconds wins. *Use the WASD keys or the Arrow keys to move.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Battle, Battlegrounds, mineblock, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zovn2qqvlxcealoc9nbtj78blzmccbxl/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zovn2qqvlxcealoc9nbtj78blzmccbxl/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58099</id>
<title>Horror Ban Ban 1 2 Player Parkour</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The terrifying siblings need to escape the haunted house. They must face their fears and collect what they need to get away. Choose one of the two siblings and escape together. Each sibling has specific items to gather, and you&rsquo;ll need to find the red and blue remotes to unlock the door. Be very careful&mdash;there are thorns and sharp knives everywhere in this frightening house. Make sure to reach the door safely!</description>
<instructions>*Use WASD Keys to move and jump. *Find the blue and red remotes to unlock the door. *Both mobile and desktop playability.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Block, Horror, Mobile, Pixel, sky </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m9rmolvne3a31grtkcbwj0s6b123aq8v/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m9rmolvne3a31grtkcbwj0s6b123aq8v/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58252</id>
<title>Ping Pong Table Tennis</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In Ping Pong: Table Tennis, you&rsquo;ll enter the exciting world of table tennis matches! This game allows you to enjoy the fun of sports! It&rsquo;s a perfect casual game for every Ping Pong enthusiast.The gameplay is simple and easy to play. Control the ping-pong racket, hit the ball accurately,and react quickly! In every game, use skill and tactics. Beat your opponent and fight for every point. Your opponents will get tougher, try to adjust your strategy and find their weaknesses! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Casual, html5 games, Tennis </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/92la82a07m5svdcghv5t1ytio7bf4q9j/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/92la82a07m5svdcghv5t1ytio7bf4q9j/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1624</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57287</id>
<title>Obby Skate Forever Parkour</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, youre skating through a very dangerous course, and you must, under no circumstances, fall off. Obby is mastering the art of skateboarding and is navigating through extremely perilous areas. He&rsquo;s skating on top of building rooftops or construction blocks, and sometimes performing very risky moves. The only thing he needs to do is collect all the coins and reach the finish line at the end of the level.</description>
<instructions>*The Grey player moves using the WASD. *Collect all the coins. *Mobile gameplay, mobile touch control is available.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Adventure, Arcade, Block, Minecraft, Pixel, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/17zhjad19qrb0ao3mj1dkzlusgq94i5m/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/17zhjad19qrb0ao3mj1dkzlusgq94i5m/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57945</id>
<title>Old School Billard Pool</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description> Simple and casual billiards game, with a classic childhood theme, with some featured characters and small references, have fun! You can be either the red ball or the yellow ball, its your choice!</description>
<instructions>Use the mouse or finger to use the stick</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>2 Player, 8 Ball Pool, Ball, Best Games, Billiard, Casual, crash, Fun, Math, touchscreen </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/l66p6uc8ivvlisk6ussl9gxvuarq46w2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/l66p6uc8ivvlisk6ussl9gxvuarq46w2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57199</id>
<title>Skateboard Obby 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, Obby and his friend Bacon need to navigate through a challenging world filled with skateboards and obstacles to reach the finish line. Stay alert, as you might fall off while skating at high altitudes. Skateboarding has never been this difficult. Be very cautious of the obstacles on the path. Avoid them and make it to the finish line with your friend.</description>
<instructions>*The Yellow player moves using the WASD keys. *The Grey player moves using the arrow keys. *Collect all the coins. *Mobile gameplay, mobile touch control is available.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Minecraft, Mobile, Skateboard </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1q8gtpd9hk04ry75punqmrvkgn78tmus/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1q8gtpd9hk04ry75punqmrvkgn78tmus/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57445</id>
<title>Redpool Skyblock 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You must take your place in the adventure of the men in red and yellow costumes, as an action-packed journey awaits you. The red and yellow players need to collect purple potion boxes. If you gather all the potion boxes, the yellow player will claim them and can activate the portal with the potion. The red player can see and eliminate invisible enemies. You must be very careful&mdash;monsters are everywhere, and they want to eat you!</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys. *Pay attention to obstacles and collect all the purple potion boxes. *Collect all the purple potion boxes and obtain the purple potion boxes.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel, Platform, sky </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gxropu31452995t0os1hzy1jh5grogtx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gxropu31452995t0os1hzy1jh5grogtx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55771</id>
<title>Neon Billard Pool</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play a game of pool to have fun and enjoy and play with a friend, each one plays a round, one is the yellow player and the other is the red player! Have fun!</description>
<instructions>Use the mouse to control and bounce the white ball.</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>2 Player, 8 Ball Pool, Ball, Best Games, Billiard, Casual, crash, Fun, Math </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bfy6fbzievlze6nan6vk7eyanal6ybaz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bfy6fbzievlze6nan6vk7eyanal6ybaz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57015</id>
<title>Blaze Ball Showdown</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the heat of Blaze Ball Showdown, a fiery sports arcade game where players battle it out in a high-speed, action-packed ball game. Set in a blazing arena, your goal is to outmaneuver your opponent, score goals, and defend your own net in intense 1v1 matches. With dynamic gameplay and hot visual effects, this game brings excitement to every shot and block. Whether playing solo or against a friend, the challenge is on &ndash; who will reign supreme in the fiery Blaze Ball arena? Key Features: Single-player and multiplayer modes Fast-paced, head-to-head gameplay Fiery arena with stunning animations Simple yet engaging controls.</description>
<instructions>Player 1 Movement: Use W to move up and S to move down. Player 2 Movement: Use the Up Arrow to move up and the Down Arrow to move down.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>2 Player, Fire, Sport, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/et5cfkegc1ohyt0ewhzt80mmrfzzgx60/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/et5cfkegc1ohyt0ewhzt80mmrfzzgx60/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57302</id>
<title>Cute Bros 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, two siblings need to find all the necessary items. Each sibling must locate their own special key. After finding the keys, they must reach the chests. Before finding the keys and chests, they need to collect all the green coins along the way. The siblings must survive the challenges of the forest and reach the finish line safely. At the end, a floating portal awaits them.</description>
<instructions>*Players use WASD AND Arrow key keys to move. *Mobile gameplay, mobile touch control is available. *Open all the chests, </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/i1gzfmj9weuab5rvifbrndc4qeg4x0t7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/i1gzfmj9weuab5rvifbrndc4qeg4x0t7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57286</id>
<title>Noob vs Pro HorseCraft</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, a noob and their closest friend, the Pro, are trying to reach and open a chest in a dangerous forest. The forest is so perilous that it could lead to their deaths, which they must avoid. Only the noob can assemble the key to the chest, so the noob needs to find all the pieces of the key. Meanwhile, with their powerful sword, the Pro can defeat all the monsters in the forest, ensuring a safer journey to the chest.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys to move. *Press the P key to attack with the sword and throw the sword. *Mobile controls are available for playing on mobile. *Double jump is active in the game. You can jump twice.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Animal, Arcade, Minecraft, Mobile, Pixel, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/kk29quu58skgfi3c9kmy4g3afao9zilv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/kk29quu58skgfi3c9kmy4g3afao9zilv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57053</id>
<title>Heaven Challenge 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, you need to collect the red and yellow keys to find out if its heaven or hell. You must be very careful as there are obstacles everywhere. Both the obby and noob must be extremely cautious, or you might die. Collect the yellow and red keys without dying and get back to the door before time runs out. You need to be quick. Dont forget, you must go everywhere together. If you get separated, youll get lost on the camera.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys and Arrow keys to move. *Collect the yellow and red keys. *Reach the door before time runs out.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/icfsx6amos7isqogbzljlwhih74zuvlo/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/icfsx6amos7isqogbzljlwhih74zuvlo/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55549</id>
<title>Noob and Pro Monster School</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In our adventure, theres a school monster that constantly chases you. Sometimes its a green monster, and other times its a black monster. You need to escape from the school monsters. The school monsters want to eat you. Escape the school monsters with Noob and Pro. While running from the monster, never, ever look back. Run from the monster, collect all the diamonds you find on the way, and reach the portal at the end of the level.</description>
<instructions>*Noob , Press WASD keys to move and jump. *Pro , Press Arrow Keys keys to move and jump. *Mobile Control Available</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft, Pixel, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ivswntj4sbdhc9isbtkf22quftemm5ny/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ivswntj4sbdhc9isbtkf22quftemm5ny/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52815</id>
<title>Volley Lama</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Lamas are playing volleyball! Experience a different outcome with every hit with the random physics engine. Try to get the highest score alone or with your friend. A fun and wacky volleyball game&nbsp;awaits&nbsp;you!</description>
<instructions>One Player Mode : Player : Up Arrow or Click Two Player Mode : Player 1: W , Screen Left Click or Touch Player 2: Up Arrow , Screen Right Click or Touch You can play the game with touch on smart phone or tablets.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Ball, Fun, Funny, Mobile, Pixel, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qi0hunod9z9qvnlv0m0j0b5rlyc0f3tw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qi0hunod9z9qvnlv0m0j0b5rlyc0f3tw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>450</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56793</id>
<title>Noob vs Pro Super Hero</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, Noob is now very strong; Noob is saving Pro. Pro got injured in the forest and needs Noob to get home. If Noob can find the Superpower Totem, he can rescue both of them from the forest. With the Superpower Totem, he can jump very far or run very fast. Use all the superpowers to reach the portal and get through the doors to reach the portal.</description>
<instructions>*Use the Arrow Keys to move the Pro. *Use the WASD to move the Noob. *both mobile and desktop playability.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/4e9d06p2ondqoarz9ii6eq7rnu83n9lf/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/4e9d06p2ondqoarz9ii6eq7rnu83n9lf/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>54890</id>
<title>Obby and Noob Barry Prison</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hello, are you ready for this adventure? Help Obby and Noob escape from the prison. Barry, a bad cop, is everywhere, and you must avoid him. Barry is very dangerous; if he catches you, hell throw you in jail. Obby and Noob are in a very scary prison and need to escape from there. Collect the keys you need to open the prison door and escape.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Mobile Touch Control *Collect 3 keys and unlock the door.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1w46epju6l9hih6gf6rwg8hlq1787wui/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1w46epju6l9hih6gf6rwg8hlq1787wui/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56558</id>
<title>Snowcraft 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In the world of Snowcraft, it&rsquo;s snowing and the temperature is dropping rapidly. Steve and Alex need to be very careful. They must reach the portal before they freeze. Steve can use his sword to defeat the snowman monsters. Defeat all the snowman monsters and reach the end of the level. The snowman monsters are very smart and are constantly wandering through the snowy forest. Use your sword to kill them. Collect all the coins. Gather all the coins and reach the portal.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys to move. *Press the P key to attack with the sword and throw the sword. *Mobile controls are available for playing on mobile. *Double jump is active in the game. You can jump twice.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, Adventure, Arcade, Block, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e9nj3yn4mirpg3meigkown1zov5d62yg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e9nj3yn4mirpg3meigkown1zov5d62yg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56586</id>
<title>PixelCraft Animal School</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In order to survive in this world, you must avoid dangerous animals. On a cold winter day, you need to reach the portal. You can either go alone or with a friend to collect gold in the snow-covered forest. Gather all the gold and reach the portal at the end of the level without dying. Collect the gold and buy different costumes for yourself. Bears, wolves, wild boars, and other terrifying animals will chase you, so dont stop&mdash;run without looking back.</description>
<instructions>*Alex , Press WASD keys to move and jump. *Steve , Press Arrow Keys keys to move and jump. *Mobile Control Available *Collect the gold and reach the portal safely.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Animal, Arcade, Battle, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/26ep0w2hgpmy22lsygextvvxv4as2kl0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/26ep0w2hgpmy22lsygextvvxv4as2kl0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56540</id>
<title>RedPool Legend 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this game, two siblings must do everything they can to survive their adventure full of surprises. The yellow and red siblings need to advance together. Since the red character is the leader, they must move together. Collect all the coins and reach the invisible door.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Boys, Pixel, Super, Superhero </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/sjzwvzpgyoj0vj3vogehwpgxfyf3dq2i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/sjzwvzpgyoj0vj3vogehwpgxfyf3dq2i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55843</id>
<title>AnimalCraft Friends</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, two sweet animals need to survive. Help the pig and the sheep reach the barn. The pig and the sheep must escape from the very dangerous forest. Guide the pig and the sheep to run away from the forest and hide in the barn. The pig and the sheep are hungry; you should feed them carrots and hay to fill their stomachs. Be careful and watch out for the farmer; if he catches them, he will eat the pig and the sheep.</description>
<instructions>*Played with WASD + Arrow Keys. *Mobile touch control is available *Gather all the hay and carrots. Reach the barn.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Animal, Arcade, Cute, mineblock, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/sz81v16rr1h6jp61pk95gf62e7sx822u/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/sz81v16rr1h6jp61pk95gf62e7sx822u/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55927</id>
<title>Minescraftter Two Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, you need to survive in a 2-player game. Steve and Alex must rescue the animals and reach the end. Beware of the monsters along the way, as they can kill you. Steve has a weapon and can shoot all the monsters in his path. Reload his weapon and eliminate all the monsters. Alex needs to catch and collect all the animals.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/eueexa64q431mmoj8kd6wh6fxfgax0uu/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/eueexa64q431mmoj8kd6wh6fxfgax0uu/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56026</id>
<title>Silly Team 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, Steve joined Noob to help him, and they embarked on a joint quest together. Noob collected all the gold to create the key. Steve has the ability to see invisible levers, allowing him to activate and reveal invisible bridges. He can also open iron-locked doors. Because of this, Noob needs Steves assistance. Together, Noob and Steve must first reach the chest. Once they reach and open the chest, the invisible portal becomes visible, and they can access it.</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys. *Pay attention to obstacles and collect all the gold. *Collect all the gold and obtain the key.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, Adventure, Android, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft, Mobile, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/l9xdwli5oclfjmie6ho6rhpqvylfrwrt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/l9xdwli5oclfjmie6ho6rhpqvylfrwrt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56251</id>
<title>Little Yellowmen Jumping</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, you need to escape from the pink poison thats rising and trying to kill you. You can play alone or with a friend as you avoid the poison. Climb as high as you can and never look back. Keep jumping without looking behind and escape from the laboratory. If you don&rsquo;t escape from the laboratory, you might drown in the pink poison.</description>
<instructions>Use the WASD keys to move and jump in the game. Use the Arrow Keys keys to move and jump in the game. *Mobile Control Available </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/eqsi0bmmxv2rtb3qm06v2u8yrihzqbfw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/eqsi0bmmxv2rtb3qm06v2u8yrihzqbfw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56256</id>
<title>Hamster Cute Merge </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the dynamic and intriguing world of Hamster cute mer, the ultimate puzzle game that challenges your mind with a twist of personality! In this engaging and addictive game, your goal is to merge and match various iconic faces to create mega-characters and achieve high scores. Gameplay Features: Intuitive Controls: Simply swipe to combine faces and create new, larger characters. Easy to learn, but hard to master! </description>
<instructions>Mouse/Touch</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io Games, Alien, angryplants, Baby Hazel, blockchain, builder, Hidden </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/kx1hh75oaeemzapc05ogsoxogsckl6u7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/kx1hh75oaeemzapc05ogsoxogsckl6u7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>400</width>
<height>800</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56255</id>
<title>Noob Prison Escape Obby</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, Obby needs to rescue his brother Bacon from prison. Obby teams up with Noob, who arranges a helicopter for him. Obby goes to the prison and searches for three iron bars. After finding all three, he uses them to make a key to free Bacon from the prison.With the key, Obby unlocks the iron bars and escapes with Bacon. However, Steve, the police officer, is patrolling the area, so they must be very careful not to get caught. If Steve catches them, they wont be able to escape.Obby and Bacon manage to get out of the prison, and Noob picks them up with the helicopter and they fly away.</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys. *Collect the 3 iron bars and make a key. Use the key to unlock the prison iron bars. *Be careful of obstacles and avoid the police officer.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Mobile, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/5x2qpdxndev6a12knc0yo2ea8e8fbkpk/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/5x2qpdxndev6a12knc0yo2ea8e8fbkpk/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56096</id>
<title>Hungry Cat</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this game where we control two hungry cats, we try to catch the fish hovering in the air and try to eat more fish than our opponent. 10 fish eaters win</description>
<instructions>PC -player 1 : space -player 2 : up arrow MOBLE -player 1 : left of the screen -player 2 :right of the screen</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Animal, Best Games, Cat, Fish, Pixel, two player games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/djw8vqjdhtlj54ba02jic7wlec0xeqto/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/djw8vqjdhtlj54ba02jic7wlec0xeqto/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>540</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56070</id>
<title>Fall Boys 2D Parkour</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, you must complete the course to survive. Complete the entire course with your friend. The course may be challenging and filled with obstacles. This does not mean you cannot complete the course. As men, carefully navigate through the entire course. Obstacles are present throughout the course. Be cautious and finish the course. Reach the finish line. The royal crown awaits you. The crown at the end of the chapter is waiting for you.</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys. *Collect all the gold and reach the royal crown at the end of the level. *Complete the level safely with your friend.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cvzmo5oppnxkmo71caz1uhe6urv5pfo5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cvzmo5oppnxkmo71caz1uhe6urv5pfo5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56101</id>
<title>Obby Papa Pizzas Escape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, Obby and Bacon are doing everything they can to survive and escape from the pizza place. Help Obby and Bacon escape from the pizza place with your friend. Be careful, as Chef Papa Pizza is very angry and wants to catch you. Watch out for the pizza maker&mdash;if they catch you, you cant escape and youll lose. Be very careful, as there are obstacles everywhere and the pizza maker is very angry. Bacon can defeat the pizza maker with his sword by throwing it at the pizza maker at the right time. Obby and Bacon need to collect all the pizzas and reach the red door to escape from the pizza maker</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys and Arrow Keys *Playable on mobile. Mobile controls are available. *Collect all the pizzas and reach the red door. *Press the P key to throw the sword.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/r3f64hwuv06hh5tcp57jxxadyn50x28o/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/r3f64hwuv06hh5tcp57jxxadyn50x28o/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56029</id>
<title>Troll Stick Face Escape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Troll Stick brothers need to collect all the money and become very rich. Help the Troll Stick brothers and make sure they collect all the money. You need to gather all the gold and reach the portal. They must survive in an extreme course full of obstacles and challenges. They need to collect the coins and reach the portal before time runs out. Both Troll Stick brothers need to reach the portal. Ensure they get to the portal safely.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Best, Mobile, Stickman </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/iecnnc16bzgecvs074g1h7jdw3u1vsup/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/iecnnc16bzgecvs074g1h7jdw3u1vsup/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55931</id>
<title>TrollHead to Face</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, the troll-faced stick must remain calm and humorous as he needs to survive in this sky parkour challenge. The troll-faced character must be fast and collect all the gold before time runs out. He needs to gather the gold, run, and reach the black portal. Surviving in this perilous world full of parkours is truly difficult. To survive, you must run very quickly. You need to collect the gold safely and pass each parkour without falling down. Navigate through the obstacles on the way and reach the portal.</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys. *The game features double jumping. *Reach the portal before time runs out.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Best, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/p1tsoue1cg06e4jrmg21yvhrka0kj919/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/p1tsoue1cg06e4jrmg21yvhrka0kj919/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55844</id>
<title>Red and Blue Stick Huggy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventurous game, the stick huggies, the huggy brothers, need to reach the finish line. The red and blue huggies must run very fast to reach the finish line. You should collect the red and blue hands along the way. Collect all the hands on the road and reach the black portal at the finish line. You must reach the portal safely before time runs out. Both friends need to reach the finish line.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Battle, Friv, Platform, survival </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/dwdig81cmf18m9d9uhzdfaqdg35pciph/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/dwdig81cmf18m9d9uhzdfaqdg35pciph/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55652</id>
<title>Bitcoin Mining Simulator X</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Bitcoin mining simulator game. Build up your bitcoin balance and get rich. Buy different pcs to keeps getting richer and build up your bitcoin empire. [This game does not give bitcoin]</description>
<instructions>Click bitcoin to earn!</instructions>
<category>2 Player</category>
<tags>1 Player </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/glarfn6gagok3igj8v2mqz5h9isrm7v3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/glarfn6gagok3igj8v2mqz5h9isrm7v3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55505</id>
<title>Noob vs Pro Snowman</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this epic adventure in the land of snow, you must not fall to your death on the icy ground. Both noob and pro need to survive. Snowmen are trying to knock you down by throwing snowballs at you, so be careful, the ground is very slippery. You need to survive on the slippery surface. The one who falls down the most loses. Do your best not to fall. Beware of the snowballs and whatever you do, dont fall down. Survive with your friend in this fun adventure.</description>
<instructions>*Press the S key or the Down Arrow key to push or hit. *The player with the most points in 120 seconds wins. *Use the WASD keys or the Arrow keys to move.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/89cf3zogeg47tr5ihwvtgrdq2f5f217t/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/89cf3zogeg47tr5ihwvtgrdq2f5f217t/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55589</id>
<title>Skyblock Parkour Easy Obby</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, Obby and his girlfriend need to complete a skyblock obstacle course that seems easy but is actually quite challenging. They must be careful and never, ever separate from each other. If they do, they could die. Both of them need to reach the finish line safely. They must be very cautious as there are obstacles everywhere. The course features spiked traps on the ground and moving obstacles that go up and down. Help Obby and his girlfriend reach the finish line.</description>
<instructions>*Use the Arrow Keys to move the Obby. *Use the WASD to move the Girl Friend. *both mobile and desktop playability.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, mineblock, Pixel, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/hdoly8bhxjovlea78vo07du3vovrnz49/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/hdoly8bhxjovlea78vo07du3vovrnz49/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55665</id>
<title>Zombie Herobrine Escape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In our adventure, we need to escape in the best way possible to survive. Zombie Herobrine is chasing us, and we really need to get away from him. You must escape from that terrifying monster. Run from the zombie with your friend. The zombie is chasing you very quickly. Never look back and dont stop running. Be very careful on this obstacle course road. Watch out for the monsters, be careful. The monsters are advancing in a frightening manner everywhere. The monsters are chasing us; escape with your friend without dying and dont look back.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, mineblock, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/u36310kvnlviswkawyb1wtcom7e6t1n7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/u36310kvnlviswkawyb1wtcom7e6t1n7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55678</id>
<title>Extreme Huggy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Huggy needs to survive. Help Huggy and ensure he reaches the finish line. Do everything you can to get him into the black portal at the finish line. The area is full of obstacles: spinning gears descending from above and traps on the ground. Reach the portal safely without dying. Remember, the time is slowly running out, so you must hurry and reach the portal without hitting any obstacles before the time runs out.</description>
<instructions>*You can move by pressing the WASD keys. *The game features double jumping. *Reach the portal before time runs out.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Arena, Battle, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gijrsk71539wdzkuln0a6fjzrv06vcr6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gijrsk71539wdzkuln0a6fjzrv06vcr6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55651</id>
<title>Stick Bros Leave Prison</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Stick Bros Leave prison is the latest installment in the stickman jail series, where you get to control not one but two individuals. Finding the proper colored keys to open the door is your objective as you lead them to the levels end. Staying one step ahead of the guards is the goal. Unlock better skins by collecting money scattered across the level. Leap and dodge obstacles to make it to your destination safely as you navigate the game.</description>
<instructions>INSTRUCTIONS Find the key to change characters so you can move and get to the exits on time; the goal is to get all the stick figures to the door. Every single stickman jail game is available right now on Kiz10 for free online play. To move and leap, use</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>Escape, kiz10, Prison, Stickman </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/tydglseu5zkccaej7e99is984cam6y3a/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/tydglseu5zkccaej7e99is984cam6y3a/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>900</width>
<height>550</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55613</id>
<title>MCCraft 2 Player</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, the boy in the blue shirt and the girl in the green shirt need to find the chests. They must find the chests and reach the portal. Our adventure is very dangerous and challenging, with monsters everywhere. The monsters are very powerful, but you can defeat them. To defeat them, you need to jump on them and crush them. Dont forget to collect all the coins. Collect all the coins, find the chests, and reach the portal. Both players must reach the portal. Reach the portal to move to the next level.</description>
<instructions>*Played with WASD + Arrow Keys. *Mobile touch control is available *Find the chests and collect all the coins</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cryy20n9i7kgkftfcttlvl731wf1lgah/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cryy20n9i7kgkftfcttlvl731wf1lgah/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55570</id>
<title>Noob vs Hacker Gold Apple</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, we must eat the golden apple. By eating the golden apple, we will gain more strength. Be careful, if youre not cautious, you might eat a poisoned golden apple and shrink in size. Catch the golden apples and aim to have the highest score before time runs out. Compete with your friend and win this game. Catch and eat the most golden apples in this fun race. May your height grow the most, and may you win the game.</description>
<instructions>*Press the S key or the Down Arrow key to push or hit. *The player with the most points in 120 seconds wins. *Use the WASD keys or the Arrow keys to move.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Arcade, Battle, mineblock, Minecraft </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/v1gnx9ksj59xuahx4e9kt94qbu5224jw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/v1gnx9ksj59xuahx4e9kt94qbu5224jw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55558</id>
<title>Brothers are making a cake</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready to start a cake-making race with your friend in this adventure? The one who makes the cake the fastest wins. Collect the flying cake ingredients with your friend. There are cake ingredients in the balloons; gather them to make your cake. The player who makes the cake the quickest wins the game. Come on, compete in this fun rivalry with your friend and win. Be the best cake master!</description>
<instructions>*Press the S key or the Down Arrow key to push or hit. *The player with the most points in 120 seconds wins. *Use the WASD keys or the Arrow keys to move.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Cook, Cooking, mineblock, Minecraft, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/oglqfu1hgpzhlef06nkzll0djjj5p5c5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/oglqfu1hgpzhlef06nkzll0djjj5p5c5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55497</id>
<title>Pixel Battle Upward</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this adventure, we must avoid the lava and push our enemy into it. Are you ready for a fun game of avoiding the lava with your friend? Whoever falls into the lava loses. To avoid falling into the lava, you must evade your friend. Run away from your friend or push them into the lava. Watch out for rockets falling from the sky. These rockets can kill you. The player who falls into the lava or dies the most loses the game. Play with your friend and try to beat them.</description>
<instructions>*Press the S key or the Down Arrow key to push or hit. *The player with the most points in 120 seconds wins. *Use the WASD keys or the Arrow keys to move.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/s4cw0jv77r2zsls099sg1y5ht0p1zlyl/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/s4cw0jv77r2zsls099sg1y5ht0p1zlyl/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55353</id>
<title>Noob vs Pro Sand island</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In the adventure of Noob and Pro, there are very dangerous desert monsters. You must kill all the monsters and animals. Although Noob is clumsy and unintelligent, only he can activate the portal. Noob needs to collect iron and flint to activate the portal. Of course, Pro needs to help Noob. Pro must kill all the monsters and animals and collect all the coins. Together, Noob and Pro must reach the portal.</description>
<instructions>*Use the WASD keys to move. *Press the P key to attack with the sword and throw the sword. *Mobile controls are available for playing on mobile. *Double jump is active in the game. You can jump twice.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Android, Arcade, mineblock, Minecraft, Mobile, Pixel </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/byukioh9zbd300wj1gi537bl15sdjcan/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/byukioh9zbd300wj1gi537bl15sdjcan/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>