This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</title>
<link> https://gamemonetize.com</link>
<description>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<atom:link href="https://gamemonetize.com" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<id>68246</id>
<title>Labubu Zombie Miner</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Labubu got lost in the mine while searching for gold and valuable minerals. The mines owner, a zombie miner, is chasing Labubu. Labubu must escape safely. Help him escape and reach the parchment at the end of the mine. The parchment is very important &mdash; it contains the way out of the mine. Reach the parchment safely!</description>
<instructions>*Press W the key to jump *Playable on both mobile and PC *Double jump available</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Mine, Miner, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/t85v3af7y1yzwrpikrqr1zobpb3udk69/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/t85v3af7y1yzwrpikrqr1zobpb3udk69/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68214</id>
<title>The Ink Shop Tattoo Art ASMR</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the evocative world of tattoo artistry with The Ink Shop - Tattoo Art ASMR. Designed to offer a unique blend of creativity and relaxation, the application puts you in the role of a skilled tattoo artist, responsible for turning clients visions into stunning inked realities. This immersive game not only allows you to explore artistic expressions but also provides the soothing ambiance of ASMR through every phase of the tattooing process.</description>
<instructions>At the heart of the app, you will encounter customers each with a unique backstory and tattoo ideas. Your task is to guide them through the tattoo journey - from preparing the skin with shaves and antiseptics to the meticulous inking. With hundreds of des</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>Coloring, Drawing </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e7wae4uvniaucl2txzi4h0di7t680amw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e7wae4uvniaucl2txzi4h0di7t680amw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67371</id>
<title>Great ZigZag Game 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hello! Change the direction of the ball by clicking on the screen and try not to fall! You earn points with each click! Try to get the highest score! Be careful, if you accidentally fall, you lose! Be the one who gets the highest score among your friends! Are you ready to have fun with this zigzag game played with simple logic? If you are ready, why are you waiting! Start playing this zigzag game suitable for all ages right away! Be careful, the game will get faster and harder! But we have no doubt that you will get the highest score thanks to your skills!</description>
<instructions>When you click on the screen the direction of the ball changes</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>3D, Casual, Click, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/irxqhf16k9lw6miolq132b9a5effvfc9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/irxqhf16k9lw6miolq132b9a5effvfc9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>480</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68203</id>
<title>Dinosaur Shifting Run</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Imagine sprinting across a scorching desert as a human adventurer, then transforming into a mighty dinosaur to smash through obstacles in a lush jungle! Unlike other runner games, Dinosaur Shifting Run offers unique challenges in every level, keeping the gameplay fresh and exciting.</description>
<instructions>- Transform the character to suit the environment. - Make sure you choose the right one to become the winner. - The higher level it is, the more difficult game-play it is.</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>dino, Dinosaur, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ok4q1z95gioil2getwab0s9atkxovc4x/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ok4q1z95gioil2getwab0s9atkxovc4x/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68111</id>
<title>ROAD CROSSER</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is a 3D casual game. You can control the character to eat coins while avoiding cars. Coins can be used to buy new and cuter skins.</description>
<instructions>Keyborard</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>3D, Bird, Cars </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/a2039w4pyybxc19zxs2qiiy4gpnpwyv4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/a2039w4pyybxc19zxs2qiiy4gpnpwyv4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68195</id>
<title>Tung Tung Tung Sahur VS Bombardino Crocodilo</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The two greatest enemies meet on a long road. Although one is strong, the others powerful stick blows are breaking through the air. Will you be able to carry the true hero to victory?</description>
<instructions>W or Up Arrow or Spacebar or Slide up for jump. D or Right Arrow or Slide right for right. A or Left Arrow or Slide reft for left. Left Mouse Button or Fire Button for throw bat. </instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, Adventure, Brainrot Italian, Italian Brainrot, running, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/c3a4z7osw0f0ywsr1xo49dhed1knukin/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/c3a4z7osw0f0ywsr1xo49dhed1knukin/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>540</width>
<height>960</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68164</id>
<title>Shape Shifting: Race Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Shape Shifting will take you across of all environment: land, air, sea To conquer them, you have to adapt quickly through all these environments Game Features - Transformable characters - Beautiful graphic design and relaxing soundtrack - Many exciting levels - Satisfying and addictive game-play</description>
<instructions>- Transform the character to suit the environment - Make sure you choose the right one to become the winner - The higher level it is, the more difficult game-play it is</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/oa6vl05onazdmyfx6vji5p6dzp0otupv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/oa6vl05onazdmyfx6vji5p6dzp0otupv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>33852</id>
<title>Level Rotator </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The game is about a single ball that is located at the beginning of the pipe. Help him reach the end. Here you control not the ball, but all the levels at once! Try to reach the end by avoiding various obstacles along the way. In the game you will find: Memorable levels Intuitive operation Good graphics Just relax and turn on the game. Meditate and complete simple levels! Have a good game!</description>
<instructions>Relax and get into the game! Start passing the first level, you need to control the level, you can do this using the mouse or keyboard. Complete the levels and get rewards! Go ahead!</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Ball, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2ruoa47wae2lqe8yfax8p1wcm72zz2s3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2ruoa47wae2lqe8yfax8p1wcm72zz2s3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64918</id>
<title>Cosmic Strike 2.0</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>A game where you can explore space and battle spaceships. Come on, head into space and fight against extremely tough bosses. What happened, are you scared? There are 3 long levels in the game and each level has a boss with its own different gameplay. As you destroy enemies and bosses, you earn money and can buy new ships. Each ships different damage and firing style make the game different. And last boss is not broken it has a weak spot.</description>
<instructions>W to acceleration S to slow, Left Click to Fire Move with mouse. f a ship crashs you, you die also.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, Action, amazing, Android, Arcade, Space, Spaceship </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fukc1o594u4o3turx87lvd2tqk1shhmm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fukc1o594u4o3turx87lvd2tqk1shhmm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67815</id>
<title>Drive Zone</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive into a world of speed and thrill! This game takes you on a ride through city streets, rally tracks, and wild off-road terrains. Feel the power of the engines, master every turn, and unleash your inner racer. Its not just about speed &mdash; its about freedom, challenge, and the rush of the unknown. Are you ready to become a legend on every surface?</description>
<instructions>Desktop: W - Accelerator S - Brake/Reverse A - Left D - Right C - Camera Switch Esc - Pause Mobile: Use on-screen controls.</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>3D, Car, Driving, endless, Game, jeep, Mobile, offroad, Race, Racing, realistic, Road, Simulator, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/preebt8pchos3u8ul57dozj2gulh46ms/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/preebt8pchos3u8ul57dozj2gulh46ms/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67197</id>
<title>Sauce Silk Spy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Sauce Silk Spy: The Doomsday War of Shiba Inu Agent On the wasteland devoured by zombie viruses, a skilled Shiba Inu will shoulder the ultimate mission of saving humanity. When traditional doomsday themes encounter cute pet agents, a passionate and absurd breakout battle is about to begin!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Battle, Gun </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e294zypmnxmyfqliqwsdr8gac0o0v8a4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e294zypmnxmyfqliqwsdr8gac0o0v8a4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>800</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67299</id>
<title>SokoMatch</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>SokoMatch 3D is a strategic puzzle game that combines block-pushing mechanics with match-3 gameplay. Push colorful animal blocks around the board to create groups of three or more matching animals, which will then disappear. Your goal is to clear all blocks from each level using the fewest moves possible. Navigate through increasingly challenging levels featuring special mechanics like ice blocks that freeze animals in place, and one-way arrow tiles that restrict your movement direction. Plan your moves carefully - some puzzles require strategic thinking to avoid getting stuck with unmatchable blocks.</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Arrow Keys or WASD - Move player R - Restart current level Q/E - Rotate camera view Space - Continue to next level / Start game Mouse - Click UI buttons Mobile/Touch: Swipe - Move player (swipe in direction you want to move) Tap buttons - Use on-</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, Brain, Casual, Hypercasual, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/r4in7whqj17v1j0om49i6os2p2dng6z7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/r4in7whqj17v1j0om49i6os2p2dng6z7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1200</width>
<height>1000</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66467</id>
<title>BigHead</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Control the character to jump on the platforms on both sides. Different obstacles will appear during the jump. Seize the right moment to jump and avoid hitting the obstacles. Its super exciting. Come and experience it now.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>Action, Adventure, jump </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m4gogzmvxhqk5tih1b17uz79h7veouij/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m4gogzmvxhqk5tih1b17uz79h7veouij/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67137</id>
<title>BrrBrr Patapim</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>BrrBrr Patapim is an epic 3D first-person shooter where you face off against the bizarre and powerful enemy&mdash;BrrBrr Patapim! Explore the map, collect powerful weapons, and toss grenades as you fight to survive the madness. With fast-paced action, meme-fueled energy, and nonstop fun, this is a wild and over-the-top shooting experience you wont forget! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>3D, Animal, Anime, Cartoon, Shooter </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1656arhg2u1z6evbbz5bcdqy39eyxk1d/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1656arhg2u1z6evbbz5bcdqy39eyxk1d/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67020</id>
<title>Collect And Break</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive into a adventure in Collect And Break which is running game! In this fun arcade game keep collecting coin and food(get energy to break the walls) . You need to be flexible , making sure to collect as coin and food as possible during the run.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play Use Mouse left click/Drag to move player left right.</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>1 Player, Mouse, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bmzifa3ps1halac7g1qu9bxyqn17nxm5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bmzifa3ps1halac7g1qu9bxyqn17nxm5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>450</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66022</id>
<title>Cook it 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive into the colorful and exciting world of match-3! Collect juicy ingredients on a plate to cook unique recipes and surprise everyone with delicious masterpieces. Uncover new ingredients, discover even more delicious recipes and become a master of culinary adventures! Ready for a fun and delicious challenge? Then start right now!</description>
<instructions>Combine 3 required ingredients on the plate with your mouse or finger to get points. Do not add more than 3 products to the plate.</instructions>
<category>Cooking</category>
<tags>3D, Cooking, Food, Simulator </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/w4h80fkwq0ipv6u699rm3mwr6wcfjpqx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/w4h80fkwq0ipv6u699rm3mwr6wcfjpqx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66902</id>
<title>Residents Evil Tariff War</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In the shadow of a global tariff war, the world teeters on the edge of collapse. The President has been abducted by a hostile nation and taken to a top-secret bio-lab for unspeakable experiments. You are a former special ops agent sent deep into enemy territory on a high-stakes rescue mission. Navigate a maze of infected corridors, solve deadly puzzles, and face off against horrific bio-engineered monsters in this third-person shooter survival adventure. Every bullet counts. Every decision matters. Uncover the truth behind the war&hellip; and save the leader of the free world&mdash;before its too late.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>Horror, Maze, Puzzle, Shooting, War, weapons, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fflrrt8bl8iqdlrz9drpklg3o8phfasd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fflrrt8bl8iqdlrz9drpklg3o8phfasd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65846</id>
<title>Italian Brainrot 3D Puzzle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Italian Brainrot 3D Puzzle is a modern take on the classic jigsaw puzzle, featuring stunning and realistic 3D graphics that bring each piece to life. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Animal, Brain, Crazy, Puzzle, Sahur, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/h4j30ed88mnbzb5diu2k53vj96vbfcd5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/h4j30ed88mnbzb5diu2k53vj96vbfcd5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66153</id>
<title>TempleEscape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Control the character to avoid being chased by giant spheres and avoid various traps. During the game you can get gold, gold can be used to buy a variety of cool character skins, the game is endless gameplay, quick to see how many points you can achieve.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Escape, Pixel, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e8obwrp27n7wdygzw1jj9sev8jg0widn/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e8obwrp27n7wdygzw1jj9sev8jg0widn/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66146</id>
<title>CarRunner</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>It is very important to control the safe turning of a car on the road and grasp the right timing. If the timing is wrong, it is very easy to hit the rocks by the roadside and fail. You can get coin rewards during the cars movement. The coins can be used to purchase other exquisite cars. Come and give it a try. Its very exciting and fun.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D Games, car tuning </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yw1sj1a3364d8x3tejjanf4r3u6kok6w/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yw1sj1a3364d8x3tejjanf4r3u6kok6w/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66155</id>
<title>PopPopPop</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Control the ball safely to the end. There will be many roads on the way to the end, and the ball needs to be timed to safely enter each road.Come and experience it.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Bounce, Casual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gwu7mswl6zdifoums1132jvb5ui3p219/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gwu7mswl6zdifoums1132jvb5ui3p219/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65850</id>
<title>Astra runner 3d</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Bounce your way through a colorful world full of moving platforms, tricky gaps, and endless challenges! Control a ball with simple tap or click mechanics &mdash; jump over obstacles, time your movements perfectly, and aim for the highest score.</description>
<instructions>Use the arrow keys (or on-screen buttons) to move your character. Collect coins and avoid obstacles. The game restarts when you lose. Try to get the highest score! Controls: Arrow Keys / Touch Buttons &ndash; Move character Space / Tap &ndash; Jump or per</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>3D, Adventure, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6oxu0a040730x639r8y1m0pysg2d5cyc/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6oxu0a040730x639r8y1m0pysg2d5cyc/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64331</id>
<title>Weapon Shooter</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Weapon Shooter 3D Shooting Game! You play as a knight and your mission is to spin and choose your weapon to attack the monsters. Have fun!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>Monster, weapons, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zuyr8qluffzmjsqa9k33eiwv5vd2rxew/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zuyr8qluffzmjsqa9k33eiwv5vd2rxew/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65629</id>
<title>Toy Claw Simulator</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Toy Claw Simulator is a fun and addictive arcade game where you take control of a virtual claw machine to collect a wide variety of adorable toys! Carefully aim and time your claw to grab plushies, action figures, and surprise collectibles. Once youve stocked up your toy inventory, head over to the factory to sell them for shiny coins! Use your earnings to run the machine to use the crane to unlock new toys. Its a charming blend of skill, strategy, and rewarding progression!</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Use WASD or Arrow keys to move the crane. Spacebar to grab a toy. Mobile: Touch and move your finger to move the crane. Click to red button to grab a toy.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Arcade, Casual, Machine, Physics, Puzzle, Simulation, Simulator </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/f15co4i47og2xj3qc10oe77l69ga8f6n/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/f15co4i47og2xj3qc10oe77l69ga8f6n/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65139</id>
<title>Escape from School: Hellish Teacher!</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Youve entered the Strictest School in the World! Evil Teacher Mr. MeanieHead hates his students! Can you escape? Challenges, parkour, catch up, obby! Roblox!</description>
<instructions>PC: WASD (Digital) or arrows + mouse Phone: Joystick + Buttons on the screen</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Android, Escape, Fun, Funny, Granny, jump, Jumping, roblox, run, running, School </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2rv392rx86yjbl4zz5aefk82w51a7gyh/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2rv392rx86yjbl4zz5aefk82w51a7gyh/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60370</id>
<title>Tung Tung Sahur Trap Maze</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to the exciting game Tong Tong Sahor: Maze Escape! A unique arcade awaits you, where you have to escape from the funny, but extremely dangerous character Tong Tong Sahor! Immerse yourself in a world of adventure full of intricate mazes, traps, and unexpected turns. Be quick, find the keys, and avoid meeting Tong Tong Sahor! Only the smartest and most agile will be able to find a way out! Game features: Intense chase in 3D mazes Unique character Tong Tong Sahor Exciting levels with puzzles Tense and fun atmosphere Simple and relaxing gameplay for all ages Are you ready to survive this dangerous adventure?</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Anime, Tung Tung Tung, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/dxalg236am3cfiqy9z7bh15zgs9v1c2o/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/dxalg236am3cfiqy9z7bh15zgs9v1c2o/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65196</id>
<title>Resident Evil: Purge Operation</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>At the start of each level, players must quickly locate powerful weapons like the shotgun and sniper rifle, crucial for fending off hordes of zombies. Once the eerie alarm sounds, grotesque, ferocious undead flood the area. A single mistake can lead to being swarmed, so precise marksmanship, agile movement, and calm judgment are essential for survival.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>3D, Horror, Shoot, weapons, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8dmfr9r473kkux0h9kbqn7iolfllp6ak/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8dmfr9r473kkux0h9kbqn7iolfllp6ak/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61185</id>
<title>Slippery Descent By Car</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Pass obstacles on cars from the cube game! A hardcore game that takes you into an exciting world of gambling challenges. You have to conquer dangerous descents on various cars, overcoming the most difficult obstacles on the way to victory. Each level is unique, full of surprises and challenges!</description>
<instructions>The machines are controlled by the standard WASD keys or the arrows on the keyboard. You can control the car in the air! &bull; Space &mdash; handbrake &bull; C &mdash; change the camera view &bull; R &mdash; level reset &bull; H &mdash; main menu</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Car, Driving, Minecraft, Obstacle, Race, Racing, unity, vehicle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fkxqezxenbtebu05zip7vmmxgbzub4ug/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fkxqezxenbtebu05zip7vmmxgbzub4ug/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64655</id>
<title>Idle Zombie Wave</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Zombies are invading, and the world is on the brink of collapse! In this apocalyptic survival clash, you will command a team of survivors as a smart and decisive leader. The undead horde is relentless, and only you can lead the survivors in this tower defense (TD) battle to defend your home from wave after wave of the undead.</description>
<instructions>Tap or Click</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>3D, apocalypse, Gun, Strategy, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ebb6jk1kjrirnnzifnoouvq7wcd8s672/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ebb6jk1kjrirnnzifnoouvq7wcd8s672/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63811</id>
<title>Velocity Puck</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Get ready for fast-paced, physics-driven air hockey action in Velocity Puck! Designed with Three.js for smooth 3D gameplay, this game brings intense one-on-one air hockey battles to life with dynamic puck physics, AI opponents, and character customization. Key Features: Realistic Physics &ndash; Experience high-speed gameplay with fluid puck movement and skill-based rebounds. Single &amp; Multiplayer (Coming Soon) &ndash; Challenge AI opponents or test your reflexes against real players. Customization &ndash; Choose from different characters and paddle colors to make your mark. Immersive Audio &amp; Visuals &ndash; Enjoy neon-lit arenas and satisfying sound </description>
<instructions> Basic Controls: Move Paddle (Mouse/Touch) Mouse: Move your cursor to control the paddle. Touchscreen: Drag your finger to move the paddle. Hit the Puck Simply move your paddle into the puck to strike it. The force and angle determine the puck&rsquo;s m</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/jll9bmbb1qxr1uux1t1khn56z4xpvibs/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/jll9bmbb1qxr1uux1t1khn56z4xpvibs/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64485</id>
<title>Math Landing Basic Operations</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Help the plane make an emergency landing by solving basic math operational problems with select the correct answer button to brake the plane to a stop. Select the correct answer button to brake the plane.</description>
<instructions>Click buttons to answer and press X/Y to steer the plane.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>3D, Plane, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6m4atgw1f179hepkg4c1nnu5kejjl0pi/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6m4atgw1f179hepkg4c1nnu5kejjl0pi/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>854</width>
<height>480</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64164</id>
<title>Gorilla Multiplayer</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Gorilla Multiplayer Unleash your inner primate in Gorilla Multiplayer, an exhilarating online adventure! Join players worldwide in dynamic, fast-paced environments where agility, strategy, and teamwork reign supreme. Climb, swing, and jump your way through challenging terrains, all while competing or collaborating with friends. With customizable avatars, thrilling game modes, and a lively community, the jungle has never been this fun. Are you ready to go bananas?</description>
<instructions>On PC: Use the Arrow Keys to move your gorilla. Control the camera and aim with the Mouse. On Mobile: Use the on-screen Joystick to move. Tap the Jump Button to leap into action.</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>Animal, Online, Word </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/i5povrpxi9gwdyq2d9zr1haw3cm0il6h/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/i5povrpxi9gwdyq2d9zr1haw3cm0il6h/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64169</id>
<title>Hero Merge</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hero Merge is an exciting tower defense game where strategy and firepower combine! Merge your heroes to create stronger units, strategically position them on grid, and defend your wall against waves of different enemies. Unlimited waves, plenty of perks and many different units! Will your heroes stand strong, or will the enemies break through?</description>
<instructions>Everything is controlled by mouse or touch if on a device with a touchscreen</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, Casual, Enemies, Shoot, Strategy, Tower Defense </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qqchzm8cx660fsm7cx7cra7ya4d4q5pc/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qqchzm8cx660fsm7cx7cra7ya4d4q5pc/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64053</id>
<title>Punch King 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>To be a slap king! Try to have relaxed and release your press by beat your opponent. Grab the right timing and hit until your opponents fly out the arena area and knock out them. </description>
<instructions>Tap to play. </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8lh0qrhh83bqcastoyjsl8z631edrkos/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8lh0qrhh83bqcastoyjsl8z631edrkos/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1344</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63962</id>
<title>Shape Walls</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Shape Walls is a fun and challenging puzzle game where you arrange shape pieces to reveal hidden objects. Tap to rotate the pieces and fit them into the correct outline. With increasing difficulty, each level tests your logic, observation, and spatial skills. Enjoy a relaxing yet brain-teasing experience as you complete unique puzzles. No time limits&mdash;just pure problem-solving fun!</description>
<instructions>Tap on a shape piece to rotate it. Adjust the pieces to fit within the given outline. Complete the shape correctly to reveal the hidden object. Progress through levels with increasing complexity. Enjoy the challenge and relax while solving puzzles!</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/q6lsd6q6espgn26s1ac2whbkw6r9yibk/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/q6lsd6q6espgn26s1ac2whbkw6r9yibk/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63972</id>
<title>WhackAMole3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Whack-a-Mole WebGL is a fun and fast-paced arcade game where your reflexes are put to the test! Moles randomly pop out of their holes, and it&rsquo;s your job to tap them as quickly as possible. The more moles you whack, the higher your score. As the game progresses, the speed increases, making it more challenging and exciting.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Action, angry, Animal, Cartoon, Crazy, Whack </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/5q307jg2lld43bre7amoent0ir1czpa3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/5q307jg2lld43bre7amoent0ir1czpa3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63953</id>
<title>Alphabet Run</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Alphabet Run 3D, an amazing game! You play as Alphabet A, and your mission is to collect as many alphabets as possible to defeat the blue monster. Choose the same color as your player to multiply your alphabets. Enjoy! </description>
<instructions>Tap or mouse click to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Hypercasual, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/n55awbyki5yltw2zabcywtzc5jv983xu/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/n55awbyki5yltw2zabcywtzc5jv983xu/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61606</id>
<title>Word Connect Crossword Puzzle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Word Connect - Crossword Puzzle Game is completely brain game with more fun &amp; relaxing word game in a crossword format made for brain activity and challenging word game By playing this game you will improve your spelling skills &amp; vocabulary. How to Play : Move your finger connecting letters to form a meaningful word You can form word horizontally &amp; Vertically Find as many words as possible to level completed and earn bonus rewards. Features: Get bonus coins for free hints! Fun and relaxing word search brain game! While Moving to the Next Level, You can feel more interest. 1000+ Challenging Game levels in</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/x9al1kr1h1mpaj5s6umdfgamd09okq4m/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/x9al1kr1h1mpaj5s6umdfgamd09okq4m/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63890</id>
<title>Jump Smash 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Jump Smash 3D &ndash; The Ultimate High-Speed Jumping Challenge! Jump Smash 3D is an exciting hyper-casual game where precision, speed, and quick reflexes are the key to victory. Designed for mobile gaming, this game delivers smooth and addictive gameplay that keeps players engaged for hours. If you love casual games, hybrid casual games, and high-energy 3D challenges, then Jump Smash 3D is the perfect game for you! Fast-Paced Jumping Action &ndash; Control a dynamic ball as it jumps, smashes obstacles, and navigates challenging levels. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>3D, Casual, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2r0abfblnfbdacepnn2mlivnkumcj9a5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2r0abfblnfbdacepnn2mlivnkumcj9a5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61330</id>
<title>Draw 2 Save Stick man Puzzle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Introducing Draw to Save, the ultimate blend of IQ testing, creativity, and brain-teasing puzzles! Engage in a unique rescue stickman drawing game that takes you through funny and unexpected scenarios, from feeding fish to avoiding getting wet. Challenge your intellect, think outside the box, and embark on an entertaining journey after long hours of work or study GAME FEATURES: &bull; Simple yet engaging combination of puzzle and drawing games. &bull; Countless levels with unexpected and humorous situations. &bull; Challenge your creativity and logical thinking. &bull; Funny, addictive, and suitable for all ages. HOW TO PLAY: 1. Draw only one line </description>
<instructions> Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, Adventure </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/53csccii7nfop4sanfmzrr10hlu3cwek/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/53csccii7nfop4sanfmzrr10hlu3cwek/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61471</id>
<title>Candy Balls</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Everyone wants to relax after the a hectic pace of a work day, and this game knows how to help with that, Simple actions, fresh and cool design, a wide variety of tasks - this game has plenty of levels so you can have lots of fun while playing game. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, Puzzle, unity </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/feedzwi36w7lqv9gxmaueotlji1b8uo0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/feedzwi36w7lqv9gxmaueotlji1b8uo0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63476</id>
<title>Screw Master 3D: Pin Puzzle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to get a screw: puzzle! -A game that will truly spin your brains! Here you have to solve exciting puzzles, twist the screws and collect mechanisms in the exciting 3D-world. Each level is a unique task where you need to accurately and quickly choose the necessary details. Simple management, but what interesting trials! With every step you become more and more clever masters of the screws! For children and adults - get a screw: puzzle! This is the perfect combination of fun and training for the mind. Just go to the game and you will not want to go out! Immerse yourself in the world of funny puzzles and enjoy eve</description>
<instructions> Democtop: Press the desired color with the left mouse button. Close or move closer to the wheel. Squeeze the paintwork and lead to the sides - rotate the model. smartphone: Press your finger on the screw to get it. Squeeze your finger and lead to the si</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, Boys, Brain, Casual, free games for your site, Girls, Logic, Logical </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7kzc77ikesq2bdej5ip6ecevhvsfyqsq/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7kzc77ikesq2bdej5ip6ecevhvsfyqsq/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60466</id>
<title>Carve Cookie, Candy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Carve Cookie Candy is a special game for cookies shape. multiple cookie handle puzzle game. Best game of real time game play. different levels with new experience.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>Action, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/y2cfyvl4lpb6rpfoiqc50uwb2c7r99h2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/y2cfyvl4lpb6rpfoiqc50uwb2c7r99h2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61332</id>
<title>Anti Stress Mind Relax Games</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>As playing games in this, you would really enjoy the game play. are on the hunt for stress anxiety relief games, then you must get your hands on our new antistress games. Pop it game and various other stress anxiety relief games</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1ts4hgizpc8ns5et55o1yp3ws4x9m0ii/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1ts4hgizpc8ns5et55o1yp3ws4x9m0ii/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63289</id>
<title>Ramp race</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this exciting race, you will have a unique opportunity to become a master of high-speed tracks! Buy and customize cars to suit your style: choose spoilers, change the color, improve each element. Every day, get gifts and new bonuses that will help you achieve success faster. Test your strength on many different levels, full of unexpected obstacles that will make each race unpredictable and exciting. Compete with other players, climb the leaderboard and prove that you are the best racer! Ramp jumps, sharp turns and competitive spirit await you on every level. Are you ready to become number one? Your rivals are already at the start</description>
<instructions>Controls on the computer: WASD - control the car (forward, backward, left, right). R - restart the level H - exit to the main menu Space - stop the car For mobile devices, the game interface is used.</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Best Games, Cars, Driving, Game, HTML5, html5 games, Mobile, Race, Skill, unity games, Unity3D, WebGL </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/c32o5le1bu4sxm4xdzwervlir7xw7u99/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/c32o5le1bu4sxm4xdzwervlir7xw7u99/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61512</id>
<title>Additive Fun 2048</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description> The gameplay is simple: you slide the numbered tiles in any of the eight directions, and when two tiles with the same number collide, they merge into one. Slide the Same Numbers offers a clean and minimalist design, with simple graphics and soothing sound effects. It is a game that will test your logical thinking and strategy skills, providing a challenging and engaging gameplay experience.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/a61yv7ccsw9cp0hkykud3hbfb48ti7x7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/a61yv7ccsw9cp0hkykud3hbfb48ti7x7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61570</id>
<title>Tabla Drum Kit Music</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you a music enthusiast who loves playing drums? Do you want to become a drum master? Then, Tabla Drum Kit Music is the app for you! This app lets you learn drums, practice, and play with realistic sound and touch on your phone or tablet. Whether youre a beginner or an advanced drummer, you can use this app to improve your skills and become a drum master.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, Music </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/d43ikk1x7fj1x72cr53a8wi8b1zdcck1/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/d43ikk1x7fj1x72cr53a8wi8b1zdcck1/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61567</id>
<title>Blob Dash Endless Runner</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Blob Dash - Endless Runner is an exciting adventure game that takes you on a fast-paced journey through a colorful world filled with challenges and obstacles. As the player, you must control a cute blob and guide it through levels of increasing difficulty. In this game, youll have to run, jump, dodge, and slide your way past hazards such as spikes, gaps, and other obstacles.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>3D Games, Action </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/hhxuvwcwnaledkbjmz8gsdehf0aits6i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/hhxuvwcwnaledkbjmz8gsdehf0aits6i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58814</id>
<title>Bridge Builder 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Become a design engineer who will have to improvise and, above all, adapt to the task at hand. Use different materials to build structures that can support the weight of the vehicle. Game Features: - Excellent physics - a real simulator - Challenging levels in four different locations - Challenging puzzles requiring the use of thinking and logic - Built-in hint system will help you develop your skills</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Use your mouse or touchpad to build a bridge. Mobile: Use touchscreen and on-screen controls.</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Bridge, Cars, construction, destruction, Logic, trucks </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ukljsw8m1k5q4mixm7qfcqh5mov87u0r/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ukljsw8m1k5q4mixm7qfcqh5mov87u0r/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62926</id>
<title>CluckNRun</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Embark on a thrilling journey through the countryside in ClucknRun, where your mission is to return a lost chickens to their farm home! Navigate through vibrant farm landscapes, collecting bountiful chickens and essential gasoline along the way. But be cautious&mdash;barrels are scattered across the path, ready to derail your ride!</description>
<instructions>Use the A and D keys for smooth left and right movement, or simply control the flow with your mouse for an effortless experience.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D, Chicken, endless, Farm, Relaxation, running, Truck </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/un43s6zge8nvgf46063pjnn520n11c92/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/un43s6zge8nvgf46063pjnn520n11c92/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61508</id>
<title>Knife Master Hit</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Knife Master Hit - Throw On Target is best challenge game. Throw the knife on rotating fruit without touching other knife, if you touch on the other knife level will be failed. If you hit all the knives without touching other knives then the level will be completed.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D Games, Arcade, unity </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8k5qgu56u8rq5cz1htirbry626ag4t2j/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8k5qgu56u8rq5cz1htirbry626ag4t2j/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63017</id>
<title>Blob Shooter 3D Assassin Hit</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Enter the colorful world of Blob Shooter 3D - Assassin Hit. In this 3D action adventure, you take control of a colorful blob assassin tasked with navigating tricky parkour challenges, battling enemies, and overcoming crazy obstacles!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>assasin, run, Shooter, Stickman </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/3tq22g1dr214dfty1fo442lif9dip77x/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/3tq22g1dr214dfty1fo442lif9dip77x/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62827</id>
<title>Hide Heist</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hide &amp; Heist is a single-player game where player control two characters &ndash; the smart and the strong. The smart excels at open locks and hacking systems, while the strong excels at eliminating guards and breaking through obstacles. Players must strategically utilize both characters unique abilities to sneak into secure corporate offices and banks, execute the heist, and escape undetected. The gameplay combines actions, strategy, stealth, and quick thinking, offering an engaging and challenging experience.</description>
<instructions>Touch Screen: Touch &amp; Drag Keyboard: ASDW Mouse: Left Click</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>Escape, Police, run, Thief </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/emrw0pl8r61oghqr4e7rhei8ebldoocd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/emrw0pl8r61oghqr4e7rhei8ebldoocd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61608</id>
<title>Block Mover Unlock Your Brain</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Relax Your Mind Between Rush Hours whether youre a kid or an adult. Engage Your Intellect and Unlock Your Brain with Wooden Board Puzzles Unblock Me gives you an immersion in a world where logic, flow, and simplicity come together.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/lzqyfr7oj6mx7fa2f3n8pi736y9i9q2j/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/lzqyfr7oj6mx7fa2f3n8pi736y9i9q2j/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62353</id>
<title>Home Rush The Fish War</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Engage in an epic battle between Humans and The Fish! Your goal is simple: drag and hold to move the Human to the perfect spot to defeat The Fish. Watch out for obstacles and tough enemies along the way. Take down The Fish, then return safely to the starting point. But remember, only Humans of the same color can defeat The Fish! Experience exciting levels with increasing challenges, stunning 3D visuals, unique characters, and easy-to-learn controls for all ages. Enjoy the adventure!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Fish, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qopeb4icv6in54sldnbutbxy0dm4f3e8/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qopeb4icv6in54sldnbutbxy0dm4f3e8/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61646</id>
<title>Count Master: Crowd Runner 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Select the highest gate, pass through it and assemble stickman warriors to confront the opposing crowd. Overcome obstacles, outpace competitors, collect coins, and advance your prowess. Triumph over the King-stickman in the ultimate showdown to seize the castle</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D Games, Arcade, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/27e1daygmn0v9rdj1ce533s7hqi2puja/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/27e1daygmn0v9rdj1ce533s7hqi2puja/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62152</id>
<title>Renovation!</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You need to control workers, first move furniture into messy houses, and then sell them for money. Use the money you earn to build a brand new house!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zbu7imnkmtb90kevp0u92rwmgl2d1ap8/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zbu7imnkmtb90kevp0u92rwmgl2d1ap8/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61610</id>
<title>Hoop Stack Sort Puzzle Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In Hoop Stack, your primary objective is to stack colorful hoops onto a central pole with perfect precision. Each color sort hoop needs to be placed carefully to ensure it fits correctly on top of the previous one. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/w4fl93r07raosopumiuh6lee2x61sr7j/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/w4fl93r07raosopumiuh6lee2x61sr7j/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61507</id>
<title>Fruits Juice Runner</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Collecting all fruits and coins while moving glass gives you more excitement of game play. it is very easy level of play and more fun! 1. Please move glass left and right with finger touch on screen 2. Collect same color fruits and avoid different color fruits 3. If the size of the glass as its begin them level is fail 4. If you collect the more number of same color fruits then you can share the juice to people at level end.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/32vfyhwp47yx2bybh3azqfih81n7fbhj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/32vfyhwp47yx2bybh3azqfih81n7fbhj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61569</id>
<title>Indian Wedding: DressUp Makeup</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description> Bridal always wants to try with different styles before really goes to apply marriage suits. This game would have that great option to check all bridal accessories to the photo. In this game you can try all Indian Wedding Dress up styles and Fashion style too. Kids also can enjoy by applying Princess Dress up accessories</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/3ciqaacal4so6osov02nzknlarb6z9g4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/3ciqaacal4so6osov02nzknlarb6z9g4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62017</id>
<title>Sprunki Crosser</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>A simple hop-and-dodge game where you help Oren, Raddy, or Clukr cross endless roads and obstacles! Core Gameplay Tap to move forward Move left and right to dodge obstacles Cross roads while avoiding traffic Collect coins along the way Try to beat your high score! Features Three playable characters: Oren, Raddy, and Clukr Simple shop system to unlock characters using collected coins Classic endless arcade gameplay Basic scoring system: +1 point per successful forward move Shop Spend collected coins to unlock new characters Characters available: Oren (Starting character) Raddy (Unlockable) Clukr (Unlockable)</description>
<instructions>swipe to move</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/jiisjc8tsi3bg6hn79prx7knwxfnsjy0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/jiisjc8tsi3bg6hn79prx7knwxfnsjy0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61990</id>
<title>Snake Color Challenge</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive into the thrilling world of Snake Color Rush, an exciting and fast-paced arcade game where reflexes and strategy are key! Inspired by the classic snake game but with a vibrant twist, this online and free-to-play game challenges players to navigate a dynamic world filled with color-changing obstacles.</description>
<instructions>Playing Snake Color Rush is simple! Visit Kiz10.com, search for the game, and start playing instantly from your browser&mdash;completely free and without any downloads or installations.</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Color, kiz10, Puzzle, Snake </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/djlhj9byrm6ma3wa7j8kjtgjfgx5mycy/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/djlhj9byrm6ma3wa7j8kjtgjfgx5mycy/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>450</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62350</id>
<title>Alien Survival</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The player will play the role of an astronaut who has just landed on the surface of a mysterious planet! The landing was tough because the rockets engine had failed. You need to get a certain amount of resources to return home. But will the return be so easy? Hordes of aggressive creatures are everywhere, with which it is useless to establish contact.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D, Alien, Arcade, Casual, Shooting </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/x8xtbv3fi3jqkgyzqbghklghukzlli9o/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/x8xtbv3fi3jqkgyzqbghklghukzlli9o/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61365</id>
<title>Greedy Snake : Brain Hole Explosion</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is a level based puzzle game where players will transform into a greedy snake and challenge different levels.Players need to make flexible judgments and plan their movement paths reasonably in order to safely eat apples and reach the finish line smoothly, winning the level victory.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>2D, 3D, Fun, Kids, Skill, Snake </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1yudmy36siiuyzs0xugdwfegza5n28x2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1yudmy36siiuyzs0xugdwfegza5n28x2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62288</id>
<title>Ladders</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ladders is an addictive game where the player must collect ladders to overcome obstacles and reach the finish line. Turn left and right to collect ladder pieces and dodge obstacles.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Casual, HTML5, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/95u39w4yeyesnwrvs3pgpe1mgdf0e0dr/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/95u39w4yeyesnwrvs3pgpe1mgdf0e0dr/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61626</id>
<title>Train 3D game puzzle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Train 3D Puzzle Game is one of the idle games, where you need to explore all about trains and developing your own business! Become a railway tycoon and enjoy a beautiful train simulator journey!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle, Train </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qiz215x10iitdevcrx8pwk51u0wdo9se/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qiz215x10iitdevcrx8pwk51u0wdo9se/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62232</id>
<title>Bubble run</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Move forward on the platform and destroy the pop it characters or dodge them. Be careful and react quickly to the approaching enemies.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Bubble, Casual, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/p8uwxtn1pcok8aye9lnhnzwkv4iierpj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/p8uwxtn1pcok8aye9lnhnzwkv4iierpj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61628</id>
<title>Jiggle Master Man</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Jiggle master is a best game for time consuming process, you can play like applying logical thinking on every level. In every new level you can feel like exciting.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/avj8mq4gqvzmfcrsqcbbu8o1gej9sgcz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/avj8mq4gqvzmfcrsqcbbu8o1gej9sgcz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62176</id>
<title>Master jumping</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Sit on the splits right between the two walls. You need to get to the very top, but the walls can be glass or with sharp spikes, where twine will not help.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags> </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/s86ncu27nklcl36t361zbfm15s1u85h0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/s86ncu27nklcl36t361zbfm15s1u85h0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61333</id>
<title>Animals Mix Up AI Hybrid</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Discover unique combinations of animals and everyday things in this exciting game! Just pick two animals, and the AI will use a special algorithm to blend them together.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/c531ugxd16u0fyfsqlvunw885pmpffmc/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/c531ugxd16u0fyfsqlvunw885pmpffmc/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61358</id>
<title>Color Candy Circle Hole Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Colorful candies to move them into different shape holes. much entertainment game. Colorful candies to move them into different shape holes. much entertainment game. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D Games, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6zcbfvkf57yl7deoq2q9iomnva3hggdg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6zcbfvkf57yl7deoq2q9iomnva3hggdg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62141</id>
<title>Monster Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Monster Game is an exciting action-packed game where players run through dynamic maps, collecting unique parts to build their ultimate monster. Once your monster is complete, take it to the battlefield and face off against other monsters in epic fights to prove who reigns supreme!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Boys</category>
<tags>3D, Battle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/suh0kkvmzonbeft293c3elziytw0ugpc/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/suh0kkvmzonbeft293c3elziytw0ugpc/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61647</id>
<title>Cube Tower Stack 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this causal game we are providing 9 New characters and you can play the game by collecting coins while moving character building stacks, super fun entertainment game. When you reaching the end of the level you do come across with 7 number of steps to double, multiple your coins. c</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/geco6h1l321svtc6752vr4qteqs6hgq2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/geco6h1l321svtc6752vr4qteqs6hgq2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62070</id>
<title>Five Nights at Spikes</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Night. You are struggling to sleep because there is clearly something wrong in this house... After a morning inspection, you found strange-looking plush toys (which someone has carefully left here!), and something about them terrifies you... Youve fallen asleep and suddenly woke up to the sound of the clock striking 12. And then the real nightmare began. The house is filled with unknown, evil sounds; the footsteps of both small, neat paws and big, fat plush paws can be heard everywhere... Its Spike and his friends who have begun hunting for you! All you have is a phone with cameras, a flashlight, and a few tennis balls! Good luck!</description>
<instructions>On PC: Holding or pressing X: Activates various functions. Holding or pressing Z: Turns on the flashlight. Look around: Use the mouse by aiming the pointer at the sides of the screen. All other controls are mapped to UI buttons.</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, Android, Interactive, iPhone, Point And Click </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cv8uigzlwymvs7n9isr9i8n6yzuh90qc/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cv8uigzlwymvs7n9isr9i8n6yzuh90qc/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1128</width>
<height>615</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61518</id>
<title>Hole Attack Master Collector</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This Christmas, the black hole is on a mission &ndash; to devour all the festive delights! Swipe to control its every move, attack with powerful bullets, and challenge your skills in this yuletide adventure.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D, Arcade, unity, unity games for your site, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/h5d7y6ucet78440zm9j6ro73nbwqktsm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/h5d7y6ucet78440zm9j6ro73nbwqktsm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62113</id>
<title>BanJia</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Casual Moving Game,Includes house decoration!A level-breaking game with a store system that can be used to purchase new skins.Thanks for playing!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yd4jr7h74aelg1b78cgrao3iya1ucgy4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yd4jr7h74aelg1b78cgrao3iya1ucgy4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61660</id>
<title>Food Slicer Food Cutting Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Looking for a new veggie slice &amp; fruit slice game? Love the thrill of chop-chop and slice it challenges? Well, you are sure to adore the new Food Slicer game. Show great chef skills and Whether you need to cut bread, cut vegetables, cut fruits, showcase great reaction, cutting precision, and avoid hitting the wood deck! Can you complete all chopping food levels? Start your quest to slice perfect slices NOW!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qz163h0ssk3paquu2zin2q8dhxko0zm5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qz163h0ssk3paquu2zin2q8dhxko0zm5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61998</id>
<title>Lone Sniper</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You only have 50 seconds to destroy all the enemies. Act very quickly, take a shot and hide behind cover so as not to come under return fire.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>Arcade, Casual, HTML5, Shooting </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/3j6mku04c81ibd0p9kw3weoocxdyo5f2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/3j6mku04c81ibd0p9kw3weoocxdyo5f2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61625</id>
<title>Space Escape Run</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This game is completely like story based. One Spaceship is going to blast so you are going to see alert saying that this space ship is going to blast in few minutes. After that your game play levels will start.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>3D Games, Adventure </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/3kinlftqot78wgdfuku3gckahhxdvd5p/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/3kinlftqot78wgdfuku3gckahhxdvd5p/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61912</id>
<title>Car Stunts Impossible Track</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Car Stunts - Impossible Track Challenge gives a thrilling driving experience game that will make you feel proud of real car driving in the sky. Drive car with top speed in this real car racing on hard tracks with extremely fast speed race on the slim track in this Car Stunts - Impossible Track Challenge Game. The Tracks which you play feels like real racing path car driving experience while driving the car you can see different narrow race tracks caves &amp; track high as well landing experience. Show your extreme car driving game 3D skills and you will become the pro in car racing skills. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Racing, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/i7crwtn7a4fwloe5djewy7qiejzlplsd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/i7crwtn7a4fwloe5djewy7qiejzlplsd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61515</id>
<title>Bus Simulator 3D Bus Coach</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Start to Bus Simulator - 3D Bus Coach, where you&rsquo;re into the driver position to drive on city streets and off-road adventures, picking up and dropping off passengers safely as you master real bus driving skills. Whether you&rsquo;re navigating busy streets or steering through tricky off-road routes, you&rsquo;re set for an exciting drive in this realistic bus driving game!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/r7xjd8d4aqptwfvucsf9tfp06e0nydvz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/r7xjd8d4aqptwfvucsf9tfp06e0nydvz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61903</id>
<title>Garten of BanBan huggy Escape</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the eerie world of Garten of BanBan huggy Escape, a thrilling online horror game where you must outsmart terrifying creatures to survive. Trapped in a sinister, abandoned kindergarten, you must explore dark corridors, solve puzzles, and evade monstrous beings lurking in the shadows. Each step brings a new challenge, making every moment suspenseful and engaging. With immersive 3D graphics and spine-chilling sound effects, Scary BanBan Escape delivers an intense horror experience right in your browser&mdash;no downloads required! The interactive gameplay keeps you on edge, as you search for clues, unlock doors, and strategize your escape. I</description>
<instructions>Instructions : Move around the map to try to escape each level before the monsters find you and you cant escape. Controls: WASD to move around the map Spacebar to jump Mouse to move the camera F to interact with items</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>Escape, kiz10, Room, survival </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zxrcgnvzd0omr9m89x69inz2564qhkim/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zxrcgnvzd0omr9m89x69inz2564qhkim/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>900</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61759</id>
<title>Tower bounce Mania</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Tower Bounce Mania you can enjoy the excitement, you can feel like best bouncing ball. Tower Blast is a challenging bouncing stack ball 3D arcade Game, the moment you give it a try, can hooked you for hours and it turns into your next addiction.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/07vu5z2tjug8dem9qvmoq9gri02lfg7c/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/07vu5z2tjug8dem9qvmoq9gri02lfg7c/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61607</id>
<title>Subway Buddy Road Runner</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play Addictive Subway Buddy Road Runner Free Game. ** PLAY ** +Drag left,right to change the Road Lane +Drag up to jump the Obstacles +Drag down to slide Hurdles Play Addictive Subway Buddy Road Runner Free Game with Colorful HD graphics. -- Game Features -- + Colorful HD graphics + Easy One Touch Controls &amp; Game Play + Nice 3D Graphics and Sounds, + Collect the Coins to Play the Game + Colorful &amp; Best Smooth Graphics + Nice Background Music &amp; Sound Effects + Intense and Exciting Game. + Many Obstacles to Jump Over &amp; to avoid. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Arcade, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zkg9hfg3hekx3505s7ax2y4o54cw49ao/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zkg9hfg3hekx3505s7ax2y4o54cw49ao/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61624</id>
<title>8 Ball Shoot It All 3D Pool</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>best pool gaming with 3D graphics &amp; real-time 3D Zoom! So interesting, you can play like youre at a real pool table, cue in hand, aiming for a victorious shot! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>3D Games, Sport, Sports, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/irq6s4qz3f0h452m9rtmp1obhfpcfdf3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/irq6s4qz3f0h452m9rtmp1obhfpcfdf3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61653</id>
<title>Rescue The Boy Rope to Exit</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Swipe the rope with your finger and cut the rope to boy fell down and move to exit door. It is very interesting, apply your logical thinking while playing every level. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D, Puzzle, unity </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/javhx118b0u7az4sna7kpziuc7zxubbd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/javhx118b0u7az4sna7kpziuc7zxubbd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61665</id>
<title>Rotate Road 3D Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You can see best experience while rotating road while moving ball. use your fingers to rotate to left or right and try to miss the obstacles.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D Games, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2w2262zi3x2nybo83t9bphamit2qs790/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2w2262zi3x2nybo83t9bphamit2qs790/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61658</id>
<title>Rescue Skibd Rope Cut Puzzle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The most fun and simple game in the world, you can happily on every level. Help the man by cutting the thread right place. Can he avoid the pinch of desperate life, enjoy playing every level. It all depends on you!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, unity, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fq3nk1eejjhgoip4k0yuhkwq5dp49me4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fq3nk1eejjhgoip4k0yuhkwq5dp49me4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61575</id>
<title>Bank Robbery Puzzle Shooter</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description> This game is about moving character from one given point to other point to reach the money counter to collect the cash to increase the score. While moving from one point to other there would be chance of defending from obstacle.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, Strategy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/wrphi7m33v5g5au4vbxyd3scarodceqa/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/wrphi7m33v5g5au4vbxyd3scarodceqa/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61645</id>
<title>Branches Rotation Arcade Game </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play addictive Branches Rotation free game. keep move on the branches as long as you can! Branches Rotation Free Game. Endless Game Play very Interesting &amp; Adventure. Just single tap on screen to rotate the branches and keep the character safe. You can get the higher scores and collect coins to unlock new characters. Branches Rotation free game. Rotate Branches to play. Simple Branches Rotation Game Play. Addictive &amp; free to play game. Branches Rotation Game is an exciting fun game with an endless mode. Download Branches Rotation Free Game now!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>3D Games, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/xvn4c3shxv6xap4vcansh2406svvoji6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/xvn4c3shxv6xap4vcansh2406svvoji6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61568</id>
<title>Cut the Grass Cutting Grass</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Cutting Grass by moving lawn mower is very interesting game to play in control. Here you have different crops to experience and different lawn mower to play. On every level you are going to see different crop field shapes like you feel real crop.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8gurfdtsau8sw6i4ds21lktb1dnf2rh9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8gurfdtsau8sw6i4ds21lktb1dnf2rh9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61556</id>
<title>Number Run 3D Casual Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Number Run 3D is a thrilling casual game that challenges your skills and reflexes as you navigate through a world filled with exciting obstacles.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, unity games, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/x70smmdiam8wbqehter3y9yzenqsy6i3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/x70smmdiam8wbqehter3y9yzenqsy6i3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60666</id>
<title>Rubic Cube</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Challenge your mind with the Ultimate Digital Rubiks Cube Simulator! From beginner-friendly 2x2 puzzles to mind-bending 9x9 configurations, this addictive puzzle game lets you test your cube-solving skills across multiple difficulty levels. Start your journey with the classic 3x3 cube or ease into the challenge with a simple 2x2. As your confidence grows, push your limits by tackling increasingly complex configurations - 4x4, 5x5, and all the way up to the ultimate 9x9 challenge. With customizable cube sizes and intuitive touch controls, youre in complete control of your puzzle-solving adventure</description>
<instructions>Use mouse to swipe. Use buttons to set dificulty. </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Best Games, Memory, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/kp7dtwrtwqit27koyn6a7nqr5g2mfbkq/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/kp7dtwrtwqit27koyn6a7nqr5g2mfbkq/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61360</id>
<title>Here Your Pizza</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the world of fast-paced pizzeria management Game where your task is to hire employees, serve customers through drive-thru windows, and keep the orders coming at the counter.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, unity, unity games for your website, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/9m47g8jzt63cl1q9t0fpvvgun4hsfp1d/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/9m47g8jzt63cl1q9t0fpvvgun4hsfp1d/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61470</id>
<title>Truck Parking Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Game Play: Use arrows for moving truck: To Front: Press Up Arrow to move forward the truck To Back: Press T to shift the gear to reverse and press Up Arrow To left : Left Arrow To Right: Right Arrow Cargo truck parking games 2025 suits you perfectly. This heavy truck parking simulator 2025 is the ultimate simulation &amp; truck parking game with highest graphics ever! If you think that you have all those pro skills of the best driver, then you can enjoy the game must.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, Action, Truck, trucks </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/tjw89z184yogv8z2plfdectizq4ew1t0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/tjw89z184yogv8z2plfdectizq4ew1t0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61472</id>
<title>Flip Shoot Control</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Flip Shoot Control is an action-packed arcade game that takes you on an exciting journey to face off against relentless enemies. Key Features: Gunplay: Take control of a powerful gun as you face waves of formidable foes. Sharpen your shooting</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>3D Games, Action, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/eokru2poii2000uh1ln1tigqmpfdw6mq/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/eokru2poii2000uh1ln1tigqmpfdw6mq/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61377</id>
<title>Coffee Run 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Coffee Run 3D is a fun and fast-paced arcade game where you collect coffee items like cups and green coffee liquid while avoiding traps. Slide the collector along a conveyor belt, grow your coffee stack, and test your timing and precision in this exciting challenge!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>run, Stack </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/jcjbmx9y210lhscinm8zn0e925475319/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/jcjbmx9y210lhscinm8zn0e925475319/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61345</id>
<title>Queen Be</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Live a royal life, manage your duties, and rule your kingdom with grace and rule your kingdom with grace and rule your kingdom with grace </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D Games, Girl </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/414ks2etqa96w3wu5hgivfuocmp5jaft/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/414ks2etqa96w3wu5hgivfuocmp5jaft/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60606</id>
<title>Wood Nuts Bolts Screw</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the world of Wood Nuts &amp; Bolts: Screw Game, where every twist and turn will put your brain to the test! This games creates your thinking world in a unique way of solving puzzles and unscrewing, screwing the nuts &amp; bolts. Each level is more tricky than you experience in the previous level.</description>
<instructions>Tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D Games, unity games, unity games for your site, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/jaqqv93i49xn0g4s3rflkp08zh9w0wk5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/jaqqv93i49xn0g4s3rflkp08zh9w0wk5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61371</id>
<title>Car Parking Master Puzzle Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is the best puzzle game you will ever play! This Car Parking Master Puzzle Game is so much fun. at a time you can feel happy and playable. best 3D controllers arking.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D Games, Puzzle, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/c4y1r68ih9vo1zjhsn83u45r5t6ay75h/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/c4y1r68ih9vo1zjhsn83u45r5t6ay75h/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>