This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</title>
<link> https://gamemonetize.com</link>
<description>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<atom:link href="https://gamemonetize.com" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<id>68362</id>
<title>Screw Sort Puzzle Pin Jam 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Want a fun 3D puzzle that&rsquo;s strangely relaxing? In ScrewSortPuzzle:PinJam3D, you&rsquo;ll remove every screw, sort colorful pins, and match them to the right slots without causing a jam! You will have to keep matching the screws of the right color and put them in the box of the corresponding color. Rotate the board to spot the screws you can safely loosen first. You can experience remove screw mode.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Matching, Relaxation, Strategy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7hih363nnbpbp77p9818x6i79tfp6yjr/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7hih363nnbpbp77p9818x6i79tfp6yjr/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68361</id>
<title>Animal Racing 2</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Face the wildest race of your life in Animal Racing. It&rsquo;s a full-blown arcade adventure filled with running, transforming, and brain-tickling puzzles! Youll be running on platforms with your opponents. Outsmart your opponents in epic simulator-style racing challenges. Quick response to transform into different animals on different platforms. For example, transforming a shark to cross the sea, an eagle to fly over a gap, an orangutan to run up a flight of steps.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Adventure, Animal, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/0nhrb2tzz0oglo3bj9oqs4zjxebt32yj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/0nhrb2tzz0oglo3bj9oqs4zjxebt32yj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1560</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68358</id>
<title>Fun Mini Games For Princess</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Fun Mini Games For Princess, a collection of mini casual games for kids. Dive into the gaming world and enjoy the fun of playing at your fingertips! Whether you are a casual gamer who looks for relaxation or a skillful player with a purpose, you will find your favorite game and enjoy endless fun in our mini games. Our mini games cover a large range of categories.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Fun, Girls, Princess, Relaxation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2ttf1h89mqgcrg2soigeh3c9dp3wa7d3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2ttf1h89mqgcrg2soigeh3c9dp3wa7d3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>945</width>
<height>1680</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68356</id>
<title>Moe Kittens Cat Avatar Maker</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Have you got the idea of raising a pet? Do you like playing with lovely cats? Welcome to Moe Kittens: Cat Avatar Maker, a cat avatar simulator game online. You can create your own kitten in every detail, from colors, shapes, tails, to patterns. Various colors and patterns for you to choose from. Never stop creating new fashion! Easy control allows players of all skill levels to enjoy.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Cat, Love, Simulator </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ddmjdac5v0whn4vsg1us6jmv3zg10ier/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ddmjdac5v0whn4vsg1us6jmv3zg10ier/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68334</id>
<title>Skibidi Toilet Melon Sandbox</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Skibidi Toilet Melon Sandbox, where youll embark on a journey in epic battlefield with brave warrior. These Casual Merge Games bring exquisite model and scene, immersing battle master in the strategic challenges between monsters and warriors. In Monster Battle toilet games, take on the role of a strategic Battle Master, defeating toilet warriors by synthesizing fight monster! Toilet games emphasize thinking, make key decisions that affect victory or defeat!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>Poppy Playtime, Sandbox, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/u1xads6x3swgts3gnmgdevln4ppa92qg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/u1xads6x3swgts3gnmgdevln4ppa92qg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68316</id>
<title>Candy Monster Raffi</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Help the candy monster Raffi eat all the candies! He absolutely loves them &ndash; all he wants is to eat candy. But be careful while collecting them! If you jump in the wrong direction, you might hit dangerous spikes. This cute little monster is hungry &ndash; run and feed Raffi with as many candies as you can!</description>
<instructions>*Click on the candy just in time to eat the candies. *watch out for obstacles. *collect coins, buy other costumes. *The game is available to play on both mobile devices and desktop computers.</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Arcade, Baby, Baby Games, Candy, Cute, Monster </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/83norf6r3the27ijyignzve2eskynpfo/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/83norf6r3the27ijyignzve2eskynpfo/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>33854</id>
<title>Stupid Arrow</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Blunt Arrow is a one&ndash;of-a-kind action game that can train your reflexes to perfection. Try to walk to the end of the rapidly narrowing circle. The arrow cannot penetrate several objects, you will have to make a lot of accurate shots, and then reach the end. The game offers: Unique gameplay Good graphics Development of reaction and precision Hurry up and start playing, beat your friends high score and collect the rewards!</description>
<instructions>You start the game in the center of the circle, your task is to get out of the circle by shooting accurately at the platforms, the circle is constantly narrowing. Can you get out of it?</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Arcade, Casual, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/mbqhd9nuimy0h206tvz1i6w83qhevw1r/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/mbqhd9nuimy0h206tvz1i6w83qhevw1r/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68168</id>
<title>Fruit Merge: Juicy Drop Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive deep into the vibrant and enthralling world of fruit-matching with our exciting game, Fruit Merge: Juicy Drop Game! When the same fruits collide, they merge into a larger fruit. Your mission is to smartly pair the same types of fruits to make the biggest possible fruits without letting them overflow from the container. However, as the fruits grow in size, space becomes a premium - managing it effectively is your key challenge. Can you strategize and solve this fruity puzzle?</description>
<instructions>Challenge yourself and create a giant fruit! Start by merging two smaller fruits to eventually form a gigantic one. It&rsquo;s a feat only 1% of players have achieved. Are you ready to join that elite group?</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Fruits, Puzzle, watermelon </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rgz7sjhynwsheffgv4ijzz1nj2oa1nur/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rgz7sjhynwsheffgv4ijzz1nj2oa1nur/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66286</id>
<title>HoppyRushy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The character moves back and forth on the platform, controlling the characters upward jump to the safe platform. Coins are awarded during the game, and coins can unlock other characters. Lets see how many platforms you can skip.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, Adventure, Best Games, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/j7jweje9x9572zn26ozqlg7ddkd2fsjt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/j7jweje9x9572zn26ozqlg7ddkd2fsjt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68246</id>
<title>Labubu Zombie Miner</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Labubu got lost in the mine while searching for gold and valuable minerals. The mines owner, a zombie miner, is chasing Labubu. Labubu must escape safely. Help him escape and reach the parchment at the end of the mine. The parchment is very important &mdash; it contains the way out of the mine. Reach the parchment safely!</description>
<instructions>*Press W the key to jump *Playable on both mobile and PC *Double jump available</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Mine, Miner, Platform </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/t85v3af7y1yzwrpikrqr1zobpb3udk69/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/t85v3af7y1yzwrpikrqr1zobpb3udk69/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68324</id>
<title>Martial Artist</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This time, you are a martial artist, and you will experience the combination of killing and strategy. See how far you can last! Simple click controls and pixel graphics make this game perfect for casual players!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Clicker</category>
<tags>RPG, Superhero, Turn Based </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rhcgv1e11i4b969i0me6m3hgxn99295d/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rhcgv1e11i4b969i0me6m3hgxn99295d/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>854</width>
<height>480</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67992</id>
<title>Bubble Pop Frenzy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Bubble Pop Frenzy is a fast-paced arcade game where you pop bubbles to score points while avoiding dangerous bomble traps. The game speeds up the longer you play, testing your reflexes and focus. With retro-inspired visuals, smooth controls, and a catchy synthwave soundtrack, its easy to pick up and hard to put down. Try to beat your high score and survive the frenzy!</description>
<instructions>Click or tap on bubbles to pop them. Avoid clicking on the bomble! That&rsquo;s all you need to know &mdash; fast reactions are key!</instructions>
<category>Clicker</category>
<tags>Arcade, Casual, Clicker, Point And Click </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/g7uysbgy2gxhui81qftkqyewt7rmdv0h/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/g7uysbgy2gxhui81qftkqyewt7rmdv0h/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67118</id>
<title>Mickey Run Adventure Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to the great kingdom craft! prepare yourself brave mickey, get ready to run, jump, dash and rush through the kingdom. In this craft game, you will be a runner who has to run and collect coins in an endless runner game mine. You need to be very careful as there will be many mouse in your way. You will need to use your craft Mickey and reflexes to avoid them and keep running. There will also be power-ups that you can collect to help you in the craft game. </description>
<instructions>Up Arrow - Jump Left Arrow - Move Left Right Arrow - Move Right Down Arrow - Slide</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Minecraft, running, subway </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cji6t48llsv4hcym69m6xvt4sbdxg741/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cji6t48llsv4hcym69m6xvt4sbdxg741/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68253</id>
<title>Roblox In Barbie Style</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Barbie meets the world of Roblox in this fun fashion game that lets you mix high-style outfits with blocky avatars. In Roblox in Barbie Style, your job is to style your Roblox character in pinks, sparkles, heels, and iconic Barbie-inspired outfits that pop.</description>
<instructions>Left Mouse Button Click or Tap to Play</instructions>
<category>Girls</category>
<tags>Dress Up, Fashion, Girls, roblox </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/xvuu8k046og4ofvsppbyvq0u995tsh62/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/xvuu8k046og4ofvsppbyvq0u995tsh62/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68282</id>
<title>Run Guys: Knockout Royale</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Enjoy chaos, laughter, and action in Run Guys: Knockout Royale. A running and multiplayer royale game. In seesaw mode, run over one seesaw after another, keep balance and rush to the finish line. Racing at breakneck speeds through spinning wooden columns, trap floors and trap obstacles. Each level will knock out the slowest players. In mountain climbing, be the first to reach the summit and jump onto the crown.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Funny, jump, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bivqu9s6efq0gk7rknnqlad3qw0ncizt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bivqu9s6efq0gk7rknnqlad3qw0ncizt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68272</id>
<title>Construction Simulator</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ready to build big and drive even bigger. Construction Simulator brings you into the most realistic world of construction driving simulation. Designed for boys who love mechanics, speed and challenges.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>build, Driving, Simulation, vehicle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1ci7q4hq9q105lp1y1vxcar3rmccjuvt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1ci7q4hq9q105lp1y1vxcar3rmccjuvt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1630</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68254</id>
<title>Ballerina Cappuccina First Date</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Tonight&rsquo;s a big night&mdash;Cappuccina and Tung Tung Sahur are heading out on their very first date, and they want to look perfect. In Ballerina Cappuccina First Date, you&rsquo;re the stylist behind their special evening. From choosing outfits to adding finishing touches, it&rsquo;s up to you to make sure both of them shine.</description>
<instructions>Left Mouse Button Click or Tap to Play</instructions>
<category>Girls</category>
<tags>Dating, Dress Up, Fashion, Girls </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cqws3qg4cs5lpckma16j68fi3mou5dwe/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cqws3qg4cs5lpckma16j68fi3mou5dwe/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60618</id>
<title>HexaPuzzleNew</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Drag the blocks and place them in the container above to assemble them. Its very fun and has multiple exquisite levels. Come and experience it now.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Arcade, Best Games, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ywbb5779vnbfvxiz7oaj55ax0o2twj5y/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ywbb5779vnbfvxiz7oaj55ax0o2twj5y/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67679</id>
<title>Geometry Jump Dash</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Jump, dash, and fly through a pulse-pounding obstacle course where one wrong move means disaster! This fast-paced, high-energy arcade game challenges players of all skill levels with precision platforming, rhythmic obstacles, and adrenaline-fueled gameplay.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Action, Adventure, Dancing, dash, Geometry, jump, Jumping, Rhythm </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8b8k4g56cc57x0ju186x94jq8emgqn4b/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8b8k4g56cc57x0ju186x94jq8emgqn4b/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68217</id>
<title>Anime Couple: Avatar Maker</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Anime Couple: Avatar Maker, the ultimate anime avatar character creation experience! Dive into the world of anime with our cutting-edge app that lets you design anime avatar faces, dress up girl avatars, and create the coolest anime couple characters youve ever seen.</description>
<instructions>Whether youre into cute and sweet anime couples or edgy and mysterious ones, Anime Couple: Avatar Maker has you covered. With our comprehensive selection of features and customization options, youll never run out of possibilities.</instructions>
<category>Girls</category>
<tags>Anime, Dress Up </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/4d0lpu1afdv2u95rzunih13rii3z13mh/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/4d0lpu1afdv2u95rzunih13rii3z13mh/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68251</id>
<title>Tung TungBall and Labububall</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You must survive in the world of balls. Two friends, Tungball and Labububall, need your help. They must collect all the coins, escape from the forest, find the key, and unlock the castle gate. Both friends must reach the castle safely. Reach the castle safely and earn the right to move on to the next level. Be careful &mdash; if the shelled monsters catch you, you&rsquo;ll lose.</description>
<instructions>*Move to WASD + Arrow Keys *Double Jump available *Mobile Touch Control *Collect all the coins and the golden key, then reach the gate.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 2D, Adventure, Arcade, Ball </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/t8cff8dsfvu1mrtphdb8jl7nkj9yjbxp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/t8cff8dsfvu1mrtphdb8jl7nkj9yjbxp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68259</id>
<title>Pixel Draw</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Unleash your creativity by crafting unique pixel art from scratch. In Pixel Draw, there are no templates &mdash; only your imagination and a grid waiting to be filled. Whether youre sketching a hero, a symbol, or something abstract, this is your chance to become a true pixel artist. Save your masterpiece and share it with friends to showcase your talent.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Block, Board, Color, Coloring, Creation, Draw, Drawing, free html5 games for your website, Number, Pixel, Skills </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/9w69vw0kvi9q6bz9zd5rrsp3den3l3fs/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/9w69vw0kvi9q6bz9zd5rrsp3den3l3fs/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>320</width>
<height>180</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68271</id>
<title>Amazing Paper Doll Diary</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Amazing Paper Doll Diary, a collection of casual mini-games, exclusively for girl players. If you are searching for relaxation online, do not hesitate to join our amazing game selection! Whether you prefer fashion design, doll dress-up, or animal games, you can enjoy a relaxing and refreshing gaming experience with our mini-games. Play the paper doll game in an easy and reactive way.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Cute, Dress Up, Relaxation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/w2x1562hsvjf8nco9ko301zjpjxglv6l/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/w2x1562hsvjf8nco9ko301zjpjxglv6l/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68278</id>
<title>Snake 2025</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Snake 2025 is a modern remake of the classic snake game with sleek graphics and smooth controls. Navigate the snake to collect orbs, grow longer, and compete for high scores. Featuring updated mechanics, retro-inspired visuals, and fast-paced arcade action. A perfect mix of nostalgia and challenge!</description>
<instructions>Arrow Keys or WASD to move Avoid hitting yourself or the walls</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Snake </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/lyjm245mz7i1tcryloatgl8nq739g08c/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/lyjm245mz7i1tcryloatgl8nq739g08c/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68281</id>
<title>Volleyball Fun Coloring</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Dive into the colorful world of Volleyball Fun Coloring: a cheerful and free online coloring game where kids can spike their creativity and serve up bright beach vibes one crayon at a time!</description>
<instructions>Mouse to play.</instructions>
<category>Girls</category>
<tags>Boys, Coloring, Educational, Fun, Girls, Hypercasual, School, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rgcxnhuoej7i3iqsntrctbsajvc1vfvb/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rgcxnhuoej7i3iqsntrctbsajvc1vfvb/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>854</width>
<height>480</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68214</id>
<title>The Ink Shop Tattoo Art ASMR</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the evocative world of tattoo artistry with The Ink Shop - Tattoo Art ASMR. Designed to offer a unique blend of creativity and relaxation, the application puts you in the role of a skilled tattoo artist, responsible for turning clients visions into stunning inked realities. This immersive game not only allows you to explore artistic expressions but also provides the soothing ambiance of ASMR through every phase of the tattooing process.</description>
<instructions>At the heart of the app, you will encounter customers each with a unique backstory and tattoo ideas. Your task is to guide them through the tattoo journey - from preparing the skin with shaves and antiseptics to the meticulous inking. With hundreds of des</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>Coloring, Drawing </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e7wae4uvniaucl2txzi4h0di7t680amw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e7wae4uvniaucl2txzi4h0di7t680amw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68218</id>
<title>Super Robot Chogokin</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play a relaxing destruction game in Super Robot Chogok. You control a giant robot. Smash, crash, and destroy everything in your path. This game is perfect for any boy who dreams of robot domination! The gameplay is super simple and satisfying. Guide your robot through the city, crash into cars, buildings, etc. Unleash powerful moves to destroy and avoid damage!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>destroy, Robot, Super </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ilrgmbbz9iahzagncq6oamsbmgktufph/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ilrgmbbz9iahzagncq6oamsbmgktufph/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68219</id>
<title>Zoo Anomaly Simulation</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Experience a zoo mutation crisis like no other. In Zoo Anomaly Simulation, a peaceful zoo has turned into a nightmare filled with mutated animals, and you&rsquo;re the only one who can stop the chaos! Enter a first-person shooting experience like no other. Explore the eerie zoo environment, grab your weapons, and fight back against giraffes, zebras, elephants, etc.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Animal, Fun, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/u2oar7g2hbolp2qkm5okuqa6nnfcmuty/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/u2oar7g2hbolp2qkm5okuqa6nnfcmuty/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66980</id>
<title>Swing Hero</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Swing Hero is an action-packed adventure game where a monkey swings down a cliff using a rope! As the monkey slides down, obstacles like rocks and snakes block the way. You need to swing left and right to avoid hitting them. It&rsquo;s a thrilling and fun game that tests your timing and reflexes. How far can your monkey swing?</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Mouse Drag = Swing Rope Mobile: Click and hold = Swing Rope </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Adventure, Casual, Clicker, HTML, HTML5, Hypercasual, NapTech Games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/czcr4z403xj0fdtaqc8ilxvlvzvj3v1r/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/czcr4z403xj0fdtaqc8ilxvlvzvj3v1r/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68242</id>
<title>Where is my Water</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Help Swampy by guiding water to his broken shower. Each level is a challenging physics-based puzzle with amazing life-like mechanics. Cut through dirt to guide fresh water, dirty water, toxic water, steam, and ooze through increasingly challenging scenarios! Every drop counts!</description>
<instructions>Use the mouse or touch to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, Adventure, Cute, free html5 games for your website, HTML5, Hypercasual, Kids, Maze, Physics, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1g5cp5vlxs5vbbvfj5965fd119k19fqv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1g5cp5vlxs5vbbvfj5965fd119k19fqv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>480</width>
<height>800</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67930</id>
<title>Cinema Empire Idle Tycoon</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Cinema Empire Idle Tycoon! Do you dream of owning your own movie theater empire? Nows your chance! In this super fun idle simulation management game, youll start with a small screening room! Build your own cinema empire! As a theater owner, you need to manage every aspect of the theater. Unlock the theaters facilities, ticket booths, movie halls, dining areas, and more. Hiring employees to help you get more bang for your buck.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Fun, idle, Movie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7en169urbumxr5ii05udu97ucun00t0n/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7en169urbumxr5ii05udu97ucun00t0n/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>34592</id>
<title>Fish master</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Master of Fishing - a new project for fans to sit with a fishing rod, and just relax. The game will give you extremely positive emotions, here you will be able to catch the fish you want, but you have to try. The game offers: - Meditative gameplay - Nice drawn graphics - Realistic fishing Are you ready to cast your rod and pull in your biggest catch? Then go for it!</description>
<instructions>Your character is in a boat, and all you have to do is fish! Cast your line and fish, gradually upgrade your equipment and pull in more and more fish, good luck!</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, Fish, Fishing </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1xhcqbonnmw8i8zn6kovy66mk3u1b15i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1xhcqbonnmw8i8zn6kovy66mk3u1b15i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67371</id>
<title>Great ZigZag Game 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hello! Change the direction of the ball by clicking on the screen and try not to fall! You earn points with each click! Try to get the highest score! Be careful, if you accidentally fall, you lose! Be the one who gets the highest score among your friends! Are you ready to have fun with this zigzag game played with simple logic? If you are ready, why are you waiting! Start playing this zigzag game suitable for all ages right away! Be careful, the game will get faster and harder! But we have no doubt that you will get the highest score thanks to your skills!</description>
<instructions>When you click on the screen the direction of the ball changes</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>3D, Casual, Click, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/irxqhf16k9lw6miolq132b9a5effvfc9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/irxqhf16k9lw6miolq132b9a5effvfc9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>480</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68134</id>
<title>Geometry Rash</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Geometry Rash is a high-speed action platformer where every move counts. Jump your way through 8 challenging levels filled with spikes and traps. As you progress, you&rsquo;ll unlock new gameplay forms, fly with the ship or boost with the rocket. Mastering each style is key to surviving later levels. Along the way, collect coins to unlock fresh character looks in the shop. With tight controls and tough level design, this game will test your reflexes and rhythm!</description>
<instructions>Tap or click to jump. You begin with the cube form. As you beat levels, you&rsquo;ll unlock the ship and rocket forms, each with different movement. In rocket form, hold to fly upward and release to fall. Time your moves to dodge traps and collect coins</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>Avoid, dash, Geometry, Obstacle, Platform, running, Skill </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/izlut8sr8h9k4lz0p0cg3t07wlj0adok/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/izlut8sr8h9k4lz0p0cg3t07wlj0adok/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68173</id>
<title>Bitcoin.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>&lt;Chomp your way to the top in Bitcoin.io &ndash; the crypto-themed multiplayer madness! Munch coins and energy to grow bigger, dodge rivals, and dominate the leaderboard in this fast-paced online arena. It is free, frantic, and super fun. Are you ready to become the biggest Bitcoin in the blockchain?</description>
<instructions>Mouse to play.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Arena, Avoid, Boys, Collecting, Hypercasual, Kids, Multiplayer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m6zjbir993y0jreqoja76d0gub0u8une/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m6zjbir993y0jreqoja76d0gub0u8une/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68203</id>
<title>Dinosaur Shifting Run</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Imagine sprinting across a scorching desert as a human adventurer, then transforming into a mighty dinosaur to smash through obstacles in a lush jungle! Unlike other runner games, Dinosaur Shifting Run offers unique challenges in every level, keeping the gameplay fresh and exciting.</description>
<instructions>- Transform the character to suit the environment. - Make sure you choose the right one to become the winner. - The higher level it is, the more difficult game-play it is.</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>dino, Dinosaur, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ok4q1z95gioil2getwab0s9atkxovc4x/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ok4q1z95gioil2getwab0s9atkxovc4x/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68207</id>
<title>Unblocked Forest Fireboy And Watergirl</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Want a mind-bending and action forest adventure in Unblocked Forest Fireboy And Watergirl? Play alone or with friends and join adventures! This classic multiplayer puzzle game brings the iconic Fireboy and Watergirl duo back into a mysterious Forest temple. Silent cooperation is the only way to get through! Each collects gems and gold coins of the corresponding color. Push the boxes, press the switches, and cooperate with each other to pass the level successfully.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Arcade, Fire, Multiplayer, water </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1xvemgqh10s5oag3rrvukaeny2fd7ekk/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1xvemgqh10s5oag3rrvukaeny2fd7ekk/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67934</id>
<title>The Long Drive</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Love driving games? Love car simulation but keen on racing? Then you definitely cant miss The Long Drive! This is a real and crazy driving simulation game for boys who love adventure! In this open world, you drive a car and start your challenge. In Free Mode, you can complete various challenges and earn rewards.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Adventure, Car, Driving, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bsd3wzjpyo42ju9u2a3rngru0q28r1jy/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bsd3wzjpyo42ju9u2a3rngru0q28r1jy/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67415</id>
<title>Online Cats Multiplayer Park</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Come to run, jump, guess, and race as a cute but competitive kitty in Online Cats - Multiplayer Park. It&rsquo;s a real-time multiplayer chaos arena. Here are seven modes you can choose from. In Grab A Shabby Ball, for example, you will have to compete with your opponents and try to touch the ball to get points. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Arcade, Cat, jump, running </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2zzd4eaozs2hipxphec84xoac3sagofk/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2zzd4eaozs2hipxphec84xoac3sagofk/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68081</id>
<title>Fruit Memory Extravaganza</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Fruit Memory Extravaganza is a vibrant and juicy card-based memory game that challenges your brain and sharpens your recall skills! Flip cards one by one to find matching fruit pairs &mdash; from bananas to berries &mdash; all within a limited time. With 6 increasingly tricky levels, each round gets faster and more challenging, testing how quickly and accurately you can match the fruity duos. Can you conquer the fruit frenzy before the clock runs out? Key Features: Flip-and-match fruit cards in a race against time Boosts memory and concentration skills Time-limited challenges across all levels Colorful fruit-themed visuals</description>
<instructions>Match the cards, click to flip!</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Card, Matching, Memory </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/idlyjbyn8fsu8zus5o3qkvovxogm9dtj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/idlyjbyn8fsu8zus5o3qkvovxogm9dtj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>33853</id>
<title>Fide The Hole</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Continuation of the successful game Physical Maze, updated graphics and sounds have been added in the new part. The number of levels has also almost doubled! Now you need to complete the levels, avoiding obstacles. The levels have become more difficult, and the physical model will delight sophisticated players with its sophistication. Start playing, get rewards and unlock new levels! Develop spatial thinking!</description>
<instructions>To play, you will need a mouse or the screen of your smartphone. Start completing the first level and discover a new physics model. The game is made with an emphasis on developing your spatial thinking. Therefore, its not just entertainment, its also a gr</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Ball, Logic, Logical </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fjidc6224f2ob7jptc7fp88bvrjwmell/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fjidc6224f2ob7jptc7fp88bvrjwmell/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68111</id>
<title>ROAD CROSSER</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is a 3D casual game. You can control the character to eat coins while avoiding cars. Coins can be used to buy new and cuter skins.</description>
<instructions>Keyborard</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>3D, Bird, Cars </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/a2039w4pyybxc19zxs2qiiy4gpnpwyv4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/a2039w4pyybxc19zxs2qiiy4gpnpwyv4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68138</id>
<title>Physical Ball</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Physics Balls is Suit for all age and completely FREE to play! Now become the master of the Physic Balls! Features: Perfect physic ball bouncy engine Fully automatic progress save Endless game mode Tablet support </description>
<instructions>Aim at breaking all bricks by one shoot: Swipe your finger and throw balls,Make them roll among the bricks. Hit items to make extra balls or double size ball. Prevent the bricks to reach the check-line!</instructions>
<category>Clicker</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2048, 2D, amazing, Ball, Best Games, Physics </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/2er4hiizbdlsbszayxfnc0jyymxnawxe/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/2er4hiizbdlsbszayxfnc0jyymxnawxe/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68186</id>
<title>Mahjong Fruit 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Before you on the screen will be seen a three-dimensional image of cubes on the faces of which you will see various images of fruits. You will need to carefully examine everything, find the same fruits completely and clicking on them to highlight the cubes on which they are applied. Having done this, you will see how these objects will disappear from the game field. For this, you will accrue points and you will make the next move. Your task in the game Mahjong Fruit 3D in the minimum time and the number of moves completely clean the field of cubes.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Best, Brain, Fruit, Fun, Logic, Mahjong, Mobile, Skill </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/abcd3b9hjuolfjqliv646ckgph1c961c/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/abcd3b9hjuolfjqliv646ckgph1c961c/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68196</id>
<title>Quick Shot</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Quick Shot is a fast-paced online shooting game where precision is everything. Your goal is simple: hit each target exactly in the center to score the highest points. But be careful &mdash; you can only miss five times before the game ends. With quick reflexes and sharp aim, you&rsquo;ll need to stay focused as the targets appear faster and more unpredictably. How long can you keep your streak alive? Test your skills and aim for perfection in Quick Shot!</description>
<instructions>Tap on the game screen to play this game.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>Arcade, Kids, Shoot, Skills </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/p30bd06tsk4xsta5lqqeyw0139voa5bx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/p30bd06tsk4xsta5lqqeyw0139voa5bx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68187</id>
<title>Tap Cute Animals</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Get ready to unwind in a cheerful clicker adventure where every tap brings rewards. In Tap Cute Animals, you&rsquo;ll collect coins, unlock adorable creatures, and dress them up in all sorts of quirky hats. Combine animals and outfits to craft delightful styles, explore charming new worlds, and upgrade your clicking power to progress faster. Its a fun and cozy way to spend your time!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>1 Player, Animal, Clicker, Cute, free html5 games for your website, Fun, Hot, Hypercasual, idle, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ycmhmx85vqq1lzfehe72kt8bz2erk1ds/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ycmhmx85vqq1lzfehe72kt8bz2erk1ds/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68195</id>
<title>Tung Tung Tung Sahur VS Bombardino Crocodilo</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The two greatest enemies meet on a long road. Although one is strong, the others powerful stick blows are breaking through the air. Will you be able to carry the true hero to victory?</description>
<instructions>W or Up Arrow or Spacebar or Slide up for jump. D or Right Arrow or Slide right for right. A or Left Arrow or Slide reft for left. Left Mouse Button or Fire Button for throw bat. </instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, Adventure, Brainrot Italian, Italian Brainrot, running, Tung Tung Tung Sahur </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/c3a4z7osw0f0ywsr1xo49dhed1knukin/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/c3a4z7osw0f0ywsr1xo49dhed1knukin/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>540</width>
<height>960</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68209</id>
<title>COD Duty Call FPS</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the war-torn battlefield in COD Duty Call FPS, a fast-paced first-person shooter that throws players into the heart of modern warfare. Set in a near-future conflict, you assume the role of an elite special forces operative deployed across volatile regions, urban warzones, and covert enemy facilities in a campaign filled with explosive action and immersive storytelling. COD Duty Call FPS delivers an adrenaline-fueled experience where your reflexes, tactics, and precision will determine survival. The game features a gripping single-player campaign that follows a high-stakes mission to prevent global catastrophe. As a member of Shado</description>
<instructions>WASD - move Space - jump mouse - aim and shoot shift - run</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>3D, Action, Adventure, apocalypse, Army, assassin, Best Games, First Person Shooter, Shoot, Shoot 'Em Up, Shooter, Shooting </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rc0aptuuleju6xnlpeds38lisqpz1hzu/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rc0aptuuleju6xnlpeds38lisqpz1hzu/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67939</id>
<title>Otr Off Road Driving</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Love car games and a true off-road driving adventure? In OTR Off-road Driving, you will have a real vehicle simulation experience. Enter off-road mode, choose different levels to start your challenge. Challenge your driving skills in the mountains. Work your way up the steep hill to your destination. Enter the Flyover Bridge Mode, control your car to the bullseye and win. Pay attention to finish the task within the time.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>Car, hills, offroad </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/vpzq3xlp2ff0238wccv4nx91334kkpd6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/vpzq3xlp2ff0238wccv4nx91334kkpd6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67412</id>
<title>Tank Attack 2</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ready, warrior. Tank Attack will bring you to the most explosive battlefield ever. Control your tank and straight into chaos! Your goal is to attack, destroy and survive. Use your cannon to shoot at the enemys tanks and take advantage of the terrain to avoid their attacks. Simple controls, epic action, perfect for every boy who loves driving games! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Battle, destroy, survival, Tanks </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/4zbu48bx93xhmvjyqpuo0o9rj0zpgxf1/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/4zbu48bx93xhmvjyqpuo0o9rj0zpgxf1/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>