This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</title>
<link> https://gamemonetize.com</link>
<description>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<atom:link href="https://gamemonetize.com" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<id>68278</id>
<title>Snake 2025</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Snake 2025 is a modern remake of the classic snake game with sleek graphics and smooth controls. Navigate the snake to collect orbs, grow longer, and compete for high scores. Featuring updated mechanics, retro-inspired visuals, and fast-paced arcade action. A perfect mix of nostalgia and challenge!</description>
<instructions>Arrow Keys or WASD to move Avoid hitting yourself or the walls</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Snake </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/lyjm245mz7i1tcryloatgl8nq739g08c/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/lyjm245mz7i1tcryloatgl8nq739g08c/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>68173</id>
<title>Bitcoin.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>&lt;Chomp your way to the top in Bitcoin.io &ndash; the crypto-themed multiplayer madness! Munch coins and energy to grow bigger, dodge rivals, and dominate the leaderboard in this fast-paced online arena. It is free, frantic, and super fun. Are you ready to become the biggest Bitcoin in the blockchain?</description>
<instructions>Mouse to play.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Arena, Avoid, Boys, Collecting, Hypercasual, Kids, Multiplayer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m6zjbir993y0jreqoja76d0gub0u8une/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m6zjbir993y0jreqoja76d0gub0u8une/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67238</id>
<title>Tung Sahur IO</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Join up to 100 players in this hilarious viral meme-inspired multiplayer mayhem! Start as an innocent school kid, but watch out, the legendary Tung Sahur infection is spreading fast! Experience tiktoks most beloved bombardino crocodilo and tung tung tung sahur memes come to life in an epic infection game that will have you laughing and screaming at the same time along with your friends. Play as a school kid trying to survive the chaos, or get infected and join the Tung Sahur army to hunt down your former classmates.</description>
<instructions>WASD / Arrow keys: Move your character. LEFT MOUSE: Action (jump as a kid or attack as a Tung Sahur). MOUSE: Move camera. * Mobile * DRAG with your LEFT FINGER to move around. DRAG with your right finger to look around. TAP the GREEN BUTTON to Action (jum</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>airplane, Avoid, Battle, Collecting, Escape, fly, Helicopter, jump, run </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/oddet3vf59i0den8dikuc3us81aby79z/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/oddet3vf59i0den8dikuc3us81aby79z/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66128</id>
<title>Ghost Jump</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ghost Jump has you navigating a maze as a ghost leaping through colorful challenges. Each jump tests your timing and reflexes, as you adapt to new obstacles. Quick reactions are essential to maintain your streak, making each moment a thrilling challenge in this endlessly entertaining experience.</description>
<instructions>Tap the screen to propel your ghost. Align the ghosts color with the barriers to progress. Begin with basic challenges and advance to harder stages. Mistakes mean starting over. Helpful hint: Prioritize timing to gradually master the gameplay.</instructions>
<category>Clicker</category>
<tags>1 Player, Arcade, Casual, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7iiy02z33u6fk19atrfe80gx7wkny4nt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7iiy02z33u6fk19atrfe80gx7wkny4nt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1024</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>54069</id>
<title>World Conqueror</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>World Conqueror is an epic strategy game where players step into the shoes of historic leaders, commanding armies and shaping the course of history. From ancient empires to modern conflicts, players navigate through pivotal moments, making critical decisions that determine the fate of nations. Web Dev <a href='https://www.crazygamesonline.com/'>https://www.crazygamesonline.com/</a></description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>.IO</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Action, Mentolatux, Skill, unity, Unity3D, WebGL </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/x5tq0rvqvv1uh18llbk270dqvr2fvvry/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/x5tq0rvqvv1uh18llbk270dqvr2fvvry/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64781</id>
<title>SquidGame Multiplayer</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Engage in free multiplayer survival! Compete in 7-minute minigames against 30 rivals. Based on the hit Netflix show, test your skills and strategy. Fail a challenge, get eliminated by Pink Soldiers! Adapt and outmaneuver to survive. Will you be the last one standing?</description>
<instructions>WASD = Move Space = Jump</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 2 Player Games, Collecting, Escape, Multiplayer, Rescue, run </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yui95x7so3o70xphcge1hqh4adlsgqzg/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yui95x7so3o70xphcge1hqh4adlsgqzg/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>900</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65489</id>
<title>Snake War Multiplayer</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Enter the arena in Slither Battle: Snake War, the ultimate snake survival game! Start as a small slither and eat glowing orbs to grow larger. Outsmart other snakes, trap them, and collect everything they drop. But be careful, one wrong move and it&rsquo;s game over! Whether youre a casual player or competitive survivor, this addictive snake war will test your reflexes, strategy, and speed! Key Features: - Eat and grow to dominate &bull; Outsmart and trap enemy snakes &bull; Simple, smooth controls &bull; Fast-paced slither gameplay &bull; Offline mode and daily rewards &bull; No time limits &ndash; play your way! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, 3D Games, Action, Arcade, Best Games, Mobile, Slither, Snake, unity games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qf4hzartah4bf6ewbpelfx4dmz1qql4a/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qf4hzartah4bf6ewbpelfx4dmz1qql4a/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64623</id>
<title>snake eat food game </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>: Classic Snake, Modern Fun! Guide the rainbow serpent, eat apples, and aim for the high score. Simple, addictive, and colorful! Relive the arcade classic! Eat, grow, and survive as the Rainbow Snake. How long can you last? The ultimate HTML5 Snake challenge! Smooth controls, vibrant visuals, and classic addictive gameplay. Get your high score! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>.io Games, 1 Player, 2D, battleship </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bwpzprwsx24h3n2uanhr5kl7qxqz9m5n/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bwpzprwsx24h3n2uanhr5kl7qxqz9m5n/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63933</id>
<title>Twerk it! body Race 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to the wildest racing game and a twerking simulator in one&mdash;Twerk Race 3D &mdash; fun run game! Get ready to shake your body in a twerk battle, dash across the racing track, and chomp your way through some fun racing challenges in the world of exciting 3d race games! Ready, set, go! &zwj;</description>
<instructions>use joystick</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io, Ballon, Fairy, Girl, Machine, Race, running, two player games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/q0g2r6rxhqmfnjxjrwxe6de2ercjotqi/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/q0g2r6rxhqmfnjxjrwxe6de2ercjotqi/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63125</id>
<title>Hungry Fish Saga </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hungry Fish Saga is casual water game where you swim around the ocean, munching your way through smaller fish to grow in size! This classic IO gameplay dynamics can be quite addictive, so prepare to challenge yourself to eat or be eaten. Gather your friends and engage in local multiplayer mode with up to three players! How to Play Fish Eat Getting Big Hunt the sea for fish Explore the oceans depths and encounter a wide variety of fish species. You can eat any fish with a smaller number than yours. If you try to eat a fish with a higher number, you&rsquo;ll die and have to start again. Grow into a fearsome predator As you progress, your fish </description>
<instructions>Player 1 Use WASD to move. Player 2 Use arrow keys to move. Player 3 Drag the left mouse button to move.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 2D, Animal, Arcade, Casual, Fish, Fun, grow, Shark, water </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/dgfdyifxbqemny4iodmwox152e7t5ij2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/dgfdyifxbqemny4iodmwox152e7t5ij2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63969</id>
<title>Territory.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Territory.io is an exciting territory capture game where players compete to control the largest area of the map. Features: &bull; Capture territory by creating loops with your trail &bull; Compete against AI opponents for dominance &bull; Collect power-ups for special abilities &bull; Simple controls: use WASD or arrow keys to move &bull; Real-time leaderboard shows whos winning &bull; Fast-paced gameplay with strategic elements Can you become the territory master? Play now and claim your space!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Arcade, Battle, Casual, Snake, Strategy, survival </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/z1tr0vb7m6qx9thl63e91rxy07u1mklx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/z1tr0vb7m6qx9thl63e91rxy07u1mklx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62056</id>
<title>Driver fast</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>A car game, in development, for now it only has 1 car and a limited map, this will change on March 3, 2025, hugs! </description>
<instructions>W - Accelerate S - Brake A - turn left D - Turn right Space - Handbrake E - Up shift Q - Down shift</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>2D, Car, drift, Driving </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1c3ko6qs3plggl0a3cy9abpj0hmlk8lw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1c3ko6qs3plggl0a3cy9abpj0hmlk8lw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62152</id>
<title>Renovation!</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>You need to control workers, first move furniture into messy houses, and then sell them for money. Use the money you earn to build a brand new house!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zbu7imnkmtb90kevp0u92rwmgl2d1ap8/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zbu7imnkmtb90kevp0u92rwmgl2d1ap8/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61418</id>
<title>tinywar.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Tinywar.io throws you into a ruthless sword-fighting free-for-all where a single hit means defeat. Fight to unlock all 10 character evolutions and boost your speed with each upgrade. Can you dominate the leaderboard and survive the longest?</description>
<instructions>* Move the mouse to guide your character * Click left mouse button - Attack * Hold right mouse button - Speed Boost</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, Action, attack, Casual, Fight, Sword </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fpegl6hk176yz1w1suj7fkw8g2ifi86o/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fpegl6hk176yz1w1suj7fkw8g2ifi86o/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60138</id>
<title>Ghostly Sniper</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>1. Leisure chicken eating game, pixel shooting brings more fun than simulating real FPS game; 2. Players can easily start the chicken eating King challenge at their fingertips and shoot against experts at their fingertips; 3. Use the bunker to avoid and see who is the strongest king. Only in the end can you get honor.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>3D Games, Crazy, CSGO </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/kb9sonfnm4zway8it5fw59lhzwhlipx3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/kb9sonfnm4zway8it5fw59lhzwhlipx3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59876</id>
<title>Greedy Snake Multiplayer Duel</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is a very classic and fun Snake game. With Q Mengs lovely cartoon style, players can experience new interfaces and new Snake game playing methods, more vivid and interesting snake shapes and more mode levels. You can play anytime, anywhere. Its very suitable for killing time. Dont miss it!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, Battle, Best Games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fzxidkarnp7ykiii4mot05y6nfwt8h3w/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fzxidkarnp7ykiii4mot05y6nfwt8h3w/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59414</id>
<title>Survev.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Survev.io Battle Royale is a thrilling multiplayer game where you fight to be the last character standing on a shrinking island. Start with nothing but your fists, scavenge for weapons and supplies, and stay within the safe zone. Choose between solo, duo, or squad modes, and use strategy and skills to outlast up to 50 opponents. </description>
<instructions>Movement = W, A, S, D Aim = Mouse Melee/Shoot = Left-Click Change Weapons = 1 through 4 or Scroll Wheel Stow Weapons (Melee Mode) = 3 or E Swap to Previous Weapon = Q Switch Gun Slots = T or drag gun to other slot Reload = R Scope Zoom = Left-click on Zoo</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, Battle, Multiplayer, Shoot 'Em Up, Shooter </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/q9xrmuceu30pey8llzop5cr0p1p2fbx9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/q9xrmuceu30pey8llzop5cr0p1p2fbx9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58068</id>
<title>Battle Jitsu</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In Battle Jitsu, you enter intense multiplayer online battles where strategy is everything. Carefully choose your cards and play the right element to beat your opponent. Fire, water, and ice face each other in a fast and dynamic duel. Master the elements, predict your opponents movements and prove yourself to be the true master of Battle Jitsu!</description>
<instructions>Use the mouse to select the cards, fire beats snow, snow beats water and water beats fire!</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>Battle, Card, Multiplayer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cxu4dpr5uspgzim70lf6t4p6milazwr0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cxu4dpr5uspgzim70lf6t4p6milazwr0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57679</id>
<title>Noobik Battlegrounds</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The tactical shooter Noobik Battlegrounds is waiting for you in its ranks, fighter. Online game in which you appear at a random point on the map, and then collect weapons and equipment, after which you kill the other players on map along the way. Game tasks: 1) Find weapons, equipment. 2) Gradually the zone will narrow to the center, you need to go to the center, otherwise you will be killed by zone that narrows. 3) There will be other survivors on your way, you will need to kill them all to win. 4) If you are killed, you can either watch other survivors or find a new session. 5) Winner is the one who remains the only one alive on map.</description>
<instructions>Walking is W,A,S,D, and on a smartphone there is a joystick on screen. Shooting and aiming is a mouse, and on a smartphone there is a button on screen. Exit the transport - F, or a button on screen.</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io, Arena, Battle, Battlegrounds, Cool, Enemies, Enemy, Minecraft, Multiplayer, Online, onlinegames io, Shoot, Shooter, Shooting </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/5zf2l6ec0cef43uo7ftxbr0l386h0o6i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/5zf2l6ec0cef43uo7ftxbr0l386h0o6i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56914</id>
<title>Color Path IO</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Color Path.io! Get ready to run and draw your color path to claim the biggest area. Strategize by drawing paths around your opponents to trap them and secure your victory. Can you outsmart and outmaneuver your rivals to become the ultimate champion?</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 3D, 3D Games, Color, Multiplayer, running, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/993brpbfu5u9o090ik0khqjsgf8t0kg6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/993brpbfu5u9o090ik0khqjsgf8t0kg6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56058</id>
<title>FLOORLAND CREATOR</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The void is a game where you manage the cards of famous players, you can win prizes from the game, join now and play to win incredible rewards</description>
<instructions>Analog mobile, click button</instructions>
<category>Soccer</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Card, Football, Letters, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/suba12vwfb7y6adfy4dbtxmef0sekzl2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/suba12vwfb7y6adfy4dbtxmef0sekzl2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1020</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>56057</id>
<title>Hole Io 2</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hole.io is a super addictive free arcade game. If you were to ask what game is the most popular these days? Then its the black hole devouring game that has exploded in popularity worldwide. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, Battle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/77h4sbaucufl8hc03nna7anwjem7mtop/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/77h4sbaucufl8hc03nna7anwjem7mtop/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55254</id>
<title>Zombie Royale Io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Zombie Royale io is a collecting survival arcade IO game. With 3D cartoon survivors, you need to help them rescue more survivors and shoot down as many zombies as you can. As the time goes on, you will meet more and more strong zombies. They will come and chase the last survivors randomly. You can summon more soldiers and bombs in the game. After each round, you can use the gold coins to upgrade your survivors.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Stickman</category>
<tags>.io Games, 1 Player, Stickman </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/d3zex3l2rordlog1xeiq4id7521xskby/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/d3zex3l2rordlog1xeiq4id7521xskby/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55652</id>
<title>Bitcoin Mining Simulator X</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Bitcoin mining simulator game. Build up your bitcoin balance and get rich. Buy different pcs to keeps getting richer and build up your bitcoin empire. [This game does not give bitcoin]</description>
<instructions>Click bitcoin to earn!</instructions>
<category>2 Player</category>
<tags>1 Player </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/glarfn6gagok3igj8v2mqz5h9isrm7v3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/glarfn6gagok3igj8v2mqz5h9isrm7v3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55542</id>
<title>Bridge Fun Race</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Bridge Fun Race is an IO battle arcade game like Mr Bean series. With 3D cute roles, you can join different knockout battles with several AI opponents. Only the first 3 places players can win and join into the next battle. In Racing levels, you need to collect items and push the obstacles to the finish line. In Survival levels, you need to roll and launch snowballs to hit the other players onto the platform in a limited time.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io Games, Battle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/d55mz3ys0ne1682kzxj5v9maq8grsuy9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/d55mz3ys0ne1682kzxj5v9maq8grsuy9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>55544</id>
<title>Blockapolypse Zombie Shooter</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Blockapolypse: Zombie Shooter is a defense shooting simulation game with 3D pixel undead creatures. To defend this position, you need to use weapons to defend incoming zombies from 3 directions. After you kill all zombies, you still need to defeat a giant undead creature. As long as you lose all of your HP, you will lose the game. When you earn enough gold coins, you can buy better weapons in the gun shop. Good luck and survive!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Girl, Shooting, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1j0t5mfnpgw2ggvltucvoe5l1g0ny5ze/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1j0t5mfnpgw2ggvltucvoe5l1g0ny5ze/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>54950</id>
<title>King of Crabs</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Easy to operate the krab,The Shell Gallery will show each roles armor, speed, skill, and pelt,The Equipment shop sells 5 Claws, 5 Bodies, and 5 Legs, Claim extra claw coins in the Sign and Spin,The Quick Match will make a fight with 24 players.The Ultimate Guide to Winning Tactics and Tips,Find a shell first. Collect and eat fish on the ground to grow up, Attack the weaker opponents.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>Battle, Fight </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7qd3n9dqksf5kv9melr3cx96oo8rmjws/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7qd3n9dqksf5kv9melr3cx96oo8rmjws/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52053</id>
<title>Shark Dominance io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Survive as long as possible and collect the baits to rank high on the leaderboard. You can level up by eating rival worms to save your best score. Surround and hunt your opponents with sharp maneuvers. If the worms head touches another worms tail, you lose the game. Tap the screen to control the worm. Tap the screen with your second finger to speed up the worm. Developer: odgameinfo@gmail.com</description>
<instructions>PC: Movement: mouse Speed: D key Mobile: Movement: touch Speed: second touch</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Multiplayer, Shark, Slither, Snake, Worms </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ecmolbepwgsxn2fhmez6p0cx3mva1dap/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ecmolbepwgsxn2fhmez6p0cx3mva1dap/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>51521</id>
<title>Which game is this</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Do you master all the games in the world? Test yourself and see the best result. This way, you can both learn more games and test a new game. enjoy.</description>
<instructions>Select correct option with mouse</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Best Games, Puzzle, Quiz </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/g02snugmrkpvoaqk3iswazqm57robhf4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/g02snugmrkpvoaqk3iswazqm57robhf4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>54406</id>
<title>FruitBasket</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Fruit Catcher is a simple and engaging 2D game where players control a basket to catch falling fruits. The objective is to catch as many fruits as possible to increase the score. The game offers a fun challenge by requiring players to time their actions and navigate the basket efficiently to catch the fruits before they fall out of reach. Gameplay: Movement: Players can move the basket left and right using the arrow keys or A and D keys. Fruit Drop: Fruits move horizontally across the screen. Players must click the mouse to make the fruit fall. The goal is to catch the falling fruit with the basket. Scoring: Each time a fruit is success</description>
<instructions>click or tap to shoot the fruit</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io Games, 1 Player, Hypercasual </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qd13183e4tdr46d7a6gqdhpq5c7k60l5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qd13183e4tdr46d7a6gqdhpq5c7k60l5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53814</id>
<title>Block Team Deathmatch</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Block Team Deathmatch is a first-person shooting simulation game. All models are made of pixel blocks including scenes, characters, and weapons. We have 4v4 Team Mode, Individual Mode, and Sniper Mode for you to select. If I were you, I would play the Team Mode first for better equipment, then challenge the other 2 modes when the rank levels up. If you never played any shooting games, I recommend you buy an auto-rifle to fight at any distance. Keep calm and shoot first!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io Games, Shooting </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6viikkt1bjfynvfk6u6hn4v16m5h3063/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6viikkt1bjfynvfk6u6hn4v16m5h3063/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1624</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53539</id>
<title>GrowWars.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The battle between the heroes is beginning in the battle arena with superheroes evolving! This battle is between the evolution heroes. Step into the arena and start slashing your opponents. Earn coins and buy new equipment or heroes in the shop. This battle can be played either single or 2 player. Call a friend and start playing together!</description>
<instructions>Player 1: Move: W, A, S, D Attack: F Dash: G Player 2: Move: ARROW KEYS Attack: K Dash: L</instructions>
<category>2 Player</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, Action, Arena, Battle, grow, Superhero, Sword, War, Warrior </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8jlqczqdhyd1jod55sl8xbttg1w5nh34/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8jlqczqdhyd1jod55sl8xbttg1w5nh34/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53586</id>
<title>Snake Train Zone</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Snake Train Zone is an exciting shooting combat game. If you are a big fan of the Snake series of games, then this game is for you! Your task is simple, enter the arena, collect colored balls and when the number bar is full you can add a soldier that follows you. Here you can not only experience the joy of shooting but also the fun of breaking through and upgrading! Are you ready for this combat?</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io Games, Shoot </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6aci346224wl1kjxyc4oo681k4wxylhl/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6aci346224wl1kjxyc4oo681k4wxylhl/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53606</id>
<title>Snake Color Race</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In Snake Race, navigate a vibrant arena as a colorful snake. Your mission: eat balls matching your snakes color to grow bigger. But growth is just the start &ndash; as you get larger, so do the challenges. Tackle the thrilling bridge challenge by using your collected balls to shoot and break through blocks. This requires not just growth, but strategy and precision. Compete against other players in real-time. The race isnt just about size, its about outsmarting and outmaneuvering your rivals. Can you become the most dominant snake in the arena? Simple to learn yet challenging to master, Snake Race offers an engaging experience for players of a</description>
<instructions>Use the mouse to control the direction of your snake and collect the balls that are the same color as your snake.</instructions>
<category>Racing</category>
<tags>3D, Ball, Bridge, Color, Race, Snake, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/3xse34phrgljynh51benwcuglaqf4v92/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/3xse34phrgljynh51benwcuglaqf4v92/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>960</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53424</id>
<title>Treasure of Alognov</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In the distant past, the great castle lost its grandeur and became an abandoned place. Legends said that the treasures of the Alogons were hidden inside the castle. One day, a group of archaeologists decided to explore the castle and uncover its secrets. They set off on a dangerous journey through the intricate corridors and dark caves of the castle. After several hours of research, they came across a secret room that contained an ancient treasure chest. However, the chest was closed and placed in a cage to protect it from outsiders. The archaeologists had to use all their knowledge and dexterity to solve the puzzles that guarded the chest</description>
<instructions>Control of the game with the mouse.Moving blocks using the keyboard.</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Arena, Best, Best Games, Block, Boys, Game, games for your website, Maze, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fcvjl5vflavc5gljapeubtuxt9oidzpr/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fcvjl5vflavc5gljapeubtuxt9oidzpr/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53203</id>
<title>Marble Match Origin</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Marble Match Origin is an exciting shooting game where you can experience unique challenges and surprises. The game features multiple difficulty levels , and players need to master the direction and speed of shooting balls to complete level objectives. As the game progresses, you will face more and more challenges and difficulties, and you need to constantly improve your skills and reaction speed to complete each level. Download Marble Match Origin now and start your adventure!</description>
<instructions>&bull; Game with different difficulty levels and levels &bull; Gorgeous graphics and animation effects &bull; Various props and rewards &bull; Various achievements and leaderboards &bull; Unique challenges and surprises &bull; Support offline games</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io, 1 Player, angrybirds, arrow, Candy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/iipbsb2vnjuclzn4jf7fexz85c0d3ogl/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/iipbsb2vnjuclzn4jf7fexz85c0d3ogl/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53209</id>
<title>Guerrillas.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Guerrillas io is an online multiplayer combat game. The games maps draw inspiration from Counter-Strike, the most famous video game, and might seem recognizable to you! The clock is ticking. If youre prepared, lets get going! Website Developer <a href='https://www.onlinegames.io/'>https://www.onlinegames.io/</a></description>
<instructions>Move using the WASD or Arrow keys. Fire with a Left mouse click. Aim with a Right mouse click. Jump using the Space key. Slide while running by pressing the Q key. Run by holding down the Left Shift. Change weapons using the 1, 2, 3 keys.</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>free games for your website, FreezeNova, Multiplayer, Shooting </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/112rtu0i5bxhf66h19pdgzxzqj0uhxzz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/112rtu0i5bxhf66h19pdgzxzqj0uhxzz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53097</id>
<title>Grind io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Grind io offers a fun and challenging game where you must get power in order to climb in the global leaderboard! To do this you must mine ores and beat players for coins! Use these coins to get more power and health in order to be the strongest and most resistant player!</description>
<instructions>WASD, Arrow keys or joystick to move. Tap/Click to attack!</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Battle, Multiplayer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/oilojh3yxoenhphbpt70udjdvkvis77w/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/oilojh3yxoenhphbpt70udjdvkvis77w/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52971</id>
<title>State Wars</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>State io Wars is an online strategy game that involves directing your forces to expand your territory. The primary objective is to capture both neutral and enemy territories under your dominion.</description>
<instructions>Left-Click (drag): Send Troops Touchscreen: for Mobile Devices</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>onlinegames io, Strategy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ow2v99y6plh0nq6c7zsmrqahfq9avaam/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ow2v99y6plh0nq6c7zsmrqahfq9avaam/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>53047</id>
<title>Rolling Balls.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>welcome to Rolling Balls io game! !use the joystick or mouse click to control you ball and start to crush everything in your sight! Dont forget to avoid huge balls because they can destroy you! How big it can get?</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 2 Player Games, 3D, 3D Games, Avoid </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yt9ftxxqnka7n959cc1qnmoqfrj4calv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yt9ftxxqnka7n959cc1qnmoqfrj4calv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52528</id>
<title>Snake Wars</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Embark on a slithery adventure in Snake Wars, the captivating io game that puts you in the scales of a charming serpent on a quest for growth. Devour tasty morsels to expand your size and reign supreme in the pit. Beware, for in this cutthroat world, only the largest survive, while the rest become fodder for their rivals. Navigate with skill and precision, dodging collisions with fellow serpents to ascend to victory in this exhilarating snake showdown! Website Developer <a href='https://www.julgames.com/'>https://www.julgames.com/</a> </description>
<instructions>Mouse: Steer Left-Click/Space Key: Boost Mobile Controls: Tap and drag</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, free games for your website, FreezeNova, Snake </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/0t0kyeqddg5haa8l91aoi2b98qeier71/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/0t0kyeqddg5haa8l91aoi2b98qeier71/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52510</id>
<title>CobraZ io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to CobraZ.io Classic, a cutting-edge FPS game that sets the bar for online multiplayer warfare. Dive into the adrenaline-pumping action as you customize your soldier, arming yourself with the finest gear to dominate the battlefield. With four exhilarating game modes at your fingertips, CobraZ.io offers endless thrills and strategic challenges. Engage in intense Team Deathmatch battles, test your skills in the chaotic Free For All mode, strategize and coordinate with your team in Capture The Flag missions. Website Developer <a href='https://www.onlinegames.io/'>https://www.onlinegames.io/</a></description>
<instructions>WASD or the Arrow keys to move. Left Mouse button to fire. Right Mouse button to aim. Space key to slide while moving. Left Shift key to run. 1-2-3 number keys to change weapons. E key or the F key to interact with a gun. G key to throw grenade. H key to </instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io, Action, First Person Shooter, free games for your website, Multiplayer, Shooter </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zq8jygdk9xuwh7puv21h1hvtn2m7xff9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zq8jygdk9xuwh7puv21h1hvtn2m7xff9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49511</id>
<title>Armed Forces.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to ArmedForces.io, where adrenaline-fueled action, intense shooting, and thrilling adventures await! Embark on a mission to locate and eliminate enemies scattered across the map. With every corner hiding potential threats, stay on your toes, employing a mix of stealth, hunting prowess, and precise marksmanship to outmaneuver your opponents. Developed <a href='https://freezenova.wordpress.com/'>https://freezenova.wordpress.com/</a> </description>
<instructions>WASD or arrow key to move Left mouse click to fire Right mouse click to aim Space to slide while moving Left shift to run 1, 2, 3 to change weapon E or F to interact / pick up weapon G to throw available dynamite H to use available medkit T to chat L to t</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io, 3D, Army, Best, Best Games, First Person Shooter, fps, free games for your site, Gun, Multiplayer, Shooting, Sniper, Unity3D, weapons </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/31sze1xgnq00dw16hvmett3re4q2qx9w/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/31sze1xgnq00dw16hvmett3re4q2qx9w/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>540</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52216</id>
<title>Connect Fruits</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Juice Fresh - is a fruit connect game to where you have to connect fruits and make yourself a juice in limited moves. Get ready for a new Jurney. With more then 100 level. </description>
<instructions>Connect same fruits.</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Collecting, Collection, Color, free games for your site, Fruit, Fruits, Match 3, Match-3, Match3, Matching </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/dj1jwzufate2bey9osne9ikqvhxu40hd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/dj1jwzufate2bey9osne9ikqvhxu40hd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50000</id>
<title>Swordbattle.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Swordbattle.io is a multiplayer game where players fight each other with different 2D swords, and try to gain coins. The more coins you have, the bigger and powerful you get! Try to become the biggest of them all. Upgrade your character, fight with friends, and rule the land!</description>
<instructions>Keyboard + mouse (default)- WASD or Arrow keys to move, click and point mouse to swing and C to throw sword! Mouse mode (you can enable this in settings) - click to swing, right click to throw, and move your mouse to move &amp; point. Enter - chat with ot</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 2 Player, 2D, Action, Adventure, Arcade, Arena, Battle, Boys, Clash, Fun, IO, Sword </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m2yzvbmyf75dl11i5lrtzlykjkzrgb85/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m2yzvbmyf75dl11i5lrtzlykjkzrgb85/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>52057</id>
<title>Only Up Parkour 2</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Only Up Parkour 2! is an exciting arcade game in which you have to overcome obstacles and conquer heights of 500M. Inspired by the popular game Your task is to guide the character through a vertical labyrinth full of various obstacles. You must react quickly, jump accurately and climb up dexterously to avoid crashing into obstacles and falling down. As you progress through the various levels, you will encounter increasing difficulty and new challenges such as Jumping platforms and obstacles.</description>
<instructions>WASD = Move Space = Jump</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, Adventure, Balance, Cartoon, Collecting, endless, Fun, Funny, Highscore, HTML5, Jumping, WebGL </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/853a4737nzy6vvrou31upd0nd41rbg2b/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/853a4737nzy6vvrou31upd0nd41rbg2b/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>51476</id>
<title>Bricks Breakers Infinity</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Relax your brain and play the best brick breaker game of the year. control the paddle and dont let the ball fall, break all the blocks to achieve a higher score</description>
<instructions>shift the paddle</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Ball, Bounce, Bricks, Pinball </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/mrw2d8le69jdofc3ngcskkp4x6zobmr4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/mrw2d8le69jdofc3ngcskkp4x6zobmr4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49889</id>
<title>Christmas Snowball Arena</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Christmas Snowball Arena is a 3D stickman snowball IO game that challenges you to an icy battle. You have to compete with nine other players in collecting snow blocks and making your snowball bigger. The goal is to be the last player standing by defeating and collecting other snowballs. You can also collect blank snowballs that are free for anyone. You can use two power-ups in the game to boost your snowball: one that makes it twice as big and another that makes it twice as fast. If you are looking for some fun and exciting snowball action, then play Christmas Snowball Arena today!</description>
<instructions>Drag and swipe to control your snowball</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>Battle, Boys, Casual, Christmas, Girl, Kids, Stickman </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8xzlb8k42m6kl77vd2mplzq63poxavui/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8xzlb8k42m6kl77vd2mplzq63poxavui/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>51162</id>
<title>Worms Arena iO</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>A great Snake IO game is beginning with the Worms Arena IO game! The baits are all around the map and collect them to make your snake the largest of the arena. Make strategic moves and trap your opponents to make them fail. Try to achieve the highest score and wear the crown. Unlock new snakes at the marketplace with coins. Let the super snake adventure begin!</description>
<instructions>Move: MOUSE or LEFT-RIGHT ARROWS or A, D Boost: SPACE or LEFT-CLICK</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, Animal, HTML5, Kids, Skill, Slither, Snake, WebGL </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/kd06w83c3m9ljk56i72bxumj18dd93in/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/kd06w83c3m9ljk56i72bxumj18dd93in/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>51236</id>
<title>Would you Rather?</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Would You Rather is the ultimate group game to play with friends! This party app contains over 120 of the best Would You Rather questions. * Perfect group party game to play with friends. * Great game for playing with groups of friends and family * Works offline making it the perfect road trip game to play in the car *Hundreds of difficult Would You Rather clean and dirty questions await for your friends and family! Can you answer them all? </description>
<instructions>Just Sellectv a Question.</instructions>
<category>2 Player</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 2 Player, Adventure, amazing, Android, Arcade, Best Games, Fun, Funny, New, Quiz, Word </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ixvzq0t2ry6tuekdtiih6fio7rur9scx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ixvzq0t2ry6tuekdtiih6fio7rur9scx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50966</id>
<title>Ducklings.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Its time to relax, youre a duck now, Quack! Swim around and rescue as many ducklings as possible. Dodge the reckless boats, they will hurt you. Upgrade your home by retrieving more ducklings and get the coolest looking nest in the pond.</description>
<instructions>Mouse / Keyboard Arrows / Joypad</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io Games, 3D, Animal, Collecting, Cool, Cute, Kid, Kids, Simulation, Skill, Slither, touch </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e1whjwhbyjsiaj82vmd60sgw9tk5370l/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e1whjwhbyjsiaj82vmd60sgw9tk5370l/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50683</id>
<title>Cube Arena 2048 Merge Numbers</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Cubes 2048.io is an addictive online game that fuses Snake and 2048. Get a bigger number by collecting free cubes and eating other players with a smaller number than you. Your cubes with the same value that bump into one another will merge. </description>
<instructions>Cubes 2048 turns 2048 into a 3D .io game! Slide around the arena picking up blocks to get bigger. Picking up two of the same number will merge them into a single block as the total sum of both.</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 3D Games, Friv </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/83up5y2u78nvd5ngywugy6j4g3im4lda/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/83up5y2u78nvd5ngywugy6j4g3im4lda/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50609</id>
<title>Island Battle 3D</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Jump and survive in Island Battle 3D, a 3D IO game that will keep you on your toes. You will play as a jumper who must avoid falling off the island. You will also have to knock back your enemies and be the last one standing. You will face a strategic challenge, as the island&rsquo;s surface is constantly breaking and changing. You can use this to your advantage and push your rivals into the gaps. But watch out, they can do the same to you. You have to stay in the safe zones and avoid getting knocked off. Island Battle 3D is a game that will test your skills and reflexes. Don&rsquo;t miss this fun game!</description>
<instructions>On PC WASD = move Space = jump On Mobile Tap the buttons or swipe wheels on the screen</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>3D, Arcade, Battle, Boys, Girls, Jumping, Kids </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/xt2j7aqkio7orm6km73231nh06tnmv9q/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/xt2j7aqkio7orm6km73231nh06tnmv9q/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1334</width>
<height>750</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50335</id>
<title>BINGO Real</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Bingo Real is a 75 ball game that could you make you play bingo with house card with different closing patterns as real one, the one who will close and click bingo first is the winner. Furthermore, there are 35 balls and 45 ball options which could make you play before 35 and 45 ball bounced up. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>.IO</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Board, Card </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/w7w5gwfb43usxnt3v70zhmtynywxfsam/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/w7w5gwfb43usxnt3v70zhmtynywxfsam/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50264</id>
<title>Eat Small Fish</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Eat Small Fish is a game where you must eat small other fish to survive and become bigger. Eat Small Fish include all kinds of hungry fishes in the undersea water. They tanked and attacked smaller fish to become the ocean most powerful fish eater. Big fish eat small fish to be giant fish. Giant fish eat big fish and turn over the Mega fish. Mega fish eat giant fish and finally become fabulous fish in the underwater sea. </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Fish, Fishing </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/5h7odu5oyzgdzo77493utlamcoz43wlj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/5h7odu5oyzgdzo77493utlamcoz43wlj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>50224</id>
<title>Protect Emojis</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Protect Emojie - The Ultimate Emoji Protection Challenge! Get ready to embark on an electrifying journey in Emojie Defense, a thrilling game where you are the guardian of emojis, tasked with creating an unbreakable line of defense to shield them from harm. Your mission is to safeguard these adorable emojis from damage using your strategic prowess. Erect an impervious barrier, comprised of unique shapes and obstacles, to fend off threats and keep your emojis safe from harm. As you progress, youll face increasingly challenging levels that will test your tactical skills to the max. Become the ultimate emoji protector and prove your mettle in t</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>.io, 1 Player, 2D, Fun, Funny, Game, Games, HTML, HTML5, Kid, Kids, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/0axk51a0a4xdeubeu45bl0x8mu7zfllb/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/0axk51a0a4xdeubeu45bl0x8mu7zfllb/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49386</id>
<title>Sumo Battle!</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Sumo wrestlers break all the canons of the sport; they do not look slender, muscular and fit; on the contrary, they are large fat men who are more round than slender. These are the rules and requirements for sumo wrestlers. To gain weight, athletes follow a special diet in the game Sumo Battle! You will help your character collect as many pieces of sushi as possible in order to become larger in size. And that means stronger. The goal is to throw your opponents off the podium by approaching them and pushing them into targets attached to their fat bellies. Please note that they will also try to push your hero.</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Use WASD or ZQSD to move. Mobile: Touch and move your finger to move.</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>3D, 3D Games, Arcade, Battle, Fight, Fighting, Funny, sumo </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7mdskoub4xtdgvith418pqnpxjv1ewx3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7mdskoub4xtdgvith418pqnpxjv1ewx3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49720</id>
<title>Hole and Collect</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Try to collect all the objects in the area with the cute black hole before the time runs out! Group them and destroy them with smart moves. You can buy new black holes with the money you earn.</description>
<instructions>WASD or ARROW KEYS</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>Collecting, Fun, Funny </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/j005mth1swnpqsqo4bb0xcq3znf2zgkt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/j005mth1swnpqsqo4bb0xcq3znf2zgkt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>450</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49604</id>
<title>Skibidi Hero.IO</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Skidibi Hero: IO is an action game where you have to survive countless waves of monsters. Control your hero to move around, collecting all of the points from defeating enemies to leveling up. You will have 3 choices to upgrade your power so choose wisely to survive till the end of the game</description>
<instructions>- Use you joystick in sence - Smooth Graphics - Awesome hero</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io, Arcade, Battlegrounds, Fun, Gun, Skibidi Toilet, survival </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/4ks356oenpbqv9qz7artzrsz828nlh2b/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/4ks356oenpbqv9qz7artzrsz828nlh2b/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49022</id>
<title>Field of Dreams: Simulation Adventure</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hello farmers! In the world of farm simulation games, its an amazing day for an incredible adventure simulation. Make use of your vacant land and turn it into a fertile, productive farm that everyone will want to visit! Gain farming experience and expand your borders to get more resources, create western style crops and raise cute animals for an amazing peaceful village life simulation! Its time to remove the chaff from the fields of the wild Wild West! Experience the serene charm of rural village life; A beautiful location with a view of the flowing river awaits you. Design your dream farm with lots of buildings and decorations.</description>
<instructions>Mouse and Click</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>.io Games, 3D Games, Arcade, Baby Hazel, Best Games, Business, Farm, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/r459clg1msy6s04k8kfv1bdskk8gnql7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/r459clg1msy6s04k8kfv1bdskk8gnql7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48989</id>
<title>Meteor.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Collect the shards, dodge the meteorite! A simple and addictive casual game that will test your reaction and agility. Become the best shard collector and show how far you can reach without getting hit by a barrage of meteorites!</description>
<instructions>Control with joystick / wasd + spacebar Collect shards, dodging meteorites flying at you. Watch the time bar!</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io, 1 Player, Android, Best </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ou78d7yjy1fvg9ww5qd9228mjzyctdlh/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ou78d7yjy1fvg9ww5qd9228mjzyctdlh/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1920</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49246</id>
<title>Merge Room</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Merge Room is an addictive mobile game where players are tasked with filling a room with objects. The concept of the game is simple yet challenging, as players must merge objects together in order to make them grow and fill up the room. The game begins with a small, empty room and a few small objects scattered around. As players merge these objects together, they will grow in size and fill up more of the room. The larger the objects become, the more points the player will earn. Website Developer <a href='https://www.gamesmunch.com/'>https://www.gamesmunch.com/</a></description>
<instructions>Overall, Merge Room is a fun and addictive mobile game that is perfect for players of all ages. With its simple yet challenging gameplay, colorful graphics, and catchy soundtrack, it is sure to provide hours of entertainment and keep players coming back f</instructions>
<category>Girls</category>
<tags>.io, Girls, House, Kids, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ctu798dfdum75hgsv7l34gpc9ainsji4/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ctu798dfdum75hgsv7l34gpc9ainsji4/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49018</id>
<title>Grimace Matching</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Grimace Matching is a fast-paced color-matching game where you must pair Grimaces based on their hues. Swipe to connect matching Grimaces . With vibrant visuals and quick thinking required, its a fun and addictive challenge for players of all ages!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Color, Fun, Funny, Game, Games, Grimace, Grimace Shake, HTML, HTML5, Matching, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/5tg5veqg430p06bpuhm5awkis3g0f6ue/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/5tg5veqg430p06bpuhm5awkis3g0f6ue/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>49237</id>
<title>Sumo Smash!</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the ring and embrace the ancient art of Sumo&mdash; with a twist! Welcome to Sumo Smash! an exhilarating game where youll wrestle for supremacy while indulging in a sushi feast to grow your sumo size. Features: Grow to Dominate. Push to Win. Treasure Chests &amp; Skins: Unlock treasure chests found within the arena to collect unique skins</description>
<instructions>WASD or QZSD to move on desktop. Touch to move on mobile.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 3D, 3D Games, Action, Arcade, Arena, Avoid, Bounce, Fighting, Funny, sumo </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zyjcvyrbjdb4400t324nzijc1in3hi5k/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zyjcvyrbjdb4400t324nzijc1in3hi5k/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47878</id>
<title>Monsters Dungeon Battle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Fight against those monsters residing in the abandoned dungeon. Upgrade your stats, Collect classes, Wizard, Archer and more that can help you in your battle, and save the world by defeating them all!</description>
<instructions>Left Mouse Button / Touch Screen</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>2D, Arena, Battlegrounds, Enemies, Fantasy, Fighting, Magic, Mobile, RPG </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cb4lyqk01r8nugfoqxnaps191l2xvq9f/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cb4lyqk01r8nugfoqxnaps191l2xvq9f/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48847</id>
<title>Skibidi Online</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Skibidi Online is a multiplayer shooter game! Shoot attacking Skibidi Toilets in PvP or CO-OP mode. Fight on 10 different maps with melee and ranged weapons.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click to attack WASD to move Space to jump E to equip weapon TAB to view stats</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 3D, 3D Games, Action, Multiplayer, Shooter, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zsp6q6syr025l3eaypqw6rxm9myjqn39/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zsp6q6syr025l3eaypqw6rxm9myjqn39/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48550</id>
<title>Skibidi War Toilets Attack</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Skibidi War, a one-of-a-kind strategy shooter game set in the heart of Skibidi Toilet City. Here, the Skibidi Toilets face off against the innovative Camera Heads in a rousing war. Think youve experienced all shooter defense games? Skibidi war will redefine your expectations. Survive and defend your territory from a ceaseless attack of these dangerous rivals in a game that humorously mingles the epic with the everyday.</description>
<instructions>You need to control the toilet to run continuously and defeat other toilets to win. You can also pick up some weapons and use them to strengthen yourself.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet, survival </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/6nw0qptdh7pv9c6dv14rxserfbqqdoj5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/6nw0qptdh7pv9c6dv14rxserfbqqdoj5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47616</id>
<title>Clown Park Hide and Seek</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Clown Park - Hide And Seek is a camp against camp arcade game. It has beautiful graphic design and 3D space design. There are 3 modes: Survivor camp, and Chaser camp. Survivors need to collect enough keys to open the escape door within the time limit and escape successfully to win. On the contrary, the pursuer is to stop the survivors pace. Are you ready? Clown Park Hide and Seek: A Thrilling and Fun-Filled IOS Game In the world of mobile gaming, Clown Park Hide and Seek has emerged as a unique and captivating game that offers hours of entertainment to players of all ages. Developed for IOS platforms, this game has gained popularity due </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 3D, Action, Boys, Crazy </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/x89je06j8zmspnm8azsllfiylp8ervox/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/x89je06j8zmspnm8azsllfiylp8ervox/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48267</id>
<title>SurvivalPixel.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>We need you in a popular survival game. Help the Warrior survive and assist them in battling tougher monsters at each level. Be cautious, as monsters are coming from everywhere and you need to stay alive. Grab your sword, and eliminate all the monsters. The monsters you defeat will grant you health and power. Keep getting stronger and defeat the boss monsters.</description>
<instructions>*Move back and forth with the WASD keys to play! *Mobile control buttons available </instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Action, Adventure, Android, Arcade, Arena, Mobile </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/vbf4xpvfzbh03r17mnu662ifpwojhfvx/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/vbf4xpvfzbh03r17mnu662ifpwojhfvx/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48522</id>
<title>Among Us Arcade</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>(Among Us Arcade) Join your favorite characters on a precarious line! Keep them from falling in this thrilling arcade game where balance is key</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Fun, Funny, Games, HTML5, Kid, Kids, Space </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/g2woks3mcag5gl5poo60729lsd7y5dwa/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/g2woks3mcag5gl5poo60729lsd7y5dwa/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48286</id>
<title>Skibidi Toilet.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This is Skibidi.io, the ultimate fusion of Skibidi and io gameplay that provides players with an adrenaline-filled experience! This game set in the heart of Skibidi Toilet City Here, you will control Skibidi Toilets and Cameramen in a rousing war.</description>
<instructions>Your goal is to eat,grow, and evolve! As you grow and evolve, you will unlock special abilities and powers to help you in your quest for victory. What you have to do is just to swipe to control it to make you stronger. Until you are the Lord of the Skibid</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Adventure, Skibidi Toilet </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/dffeouwj1z8gq8h73ad88wmdlcl7knp3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/dffeouwj1z8gq8h73ad88wmdlcl7knp3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48467</id>
<title>Choo Choo Charles</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>All aboard Choo Choo Charles arcade game! Join Charles adventure as he navigates tracks filled with obstacles. Guide him to challenges, and set the high score in this thrilling railway journey.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>Arcade, Fun, Game, Highscore, HTML5, Kids, Train </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/iak5zotv7e7ijzyikjea2gdstdlxrh38/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/iak5zotv7e7ijzyikjea2gdstdlxrh38/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48449</id>
<title>Aquapark Balls Party</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Aquapark adventure is beginning with the rolling balls this time. Pass through the math gates and increase or decrease the ball number inside your group. Fly between the ramps and try to get your ball group to the finish pool before your opponents. Join this race in 2 player mode and double your fun by competing against a friend. Dont forget to visit the shop from time to time. New ball skins will be waiting for you. Let the roll begin!</description>
<instructions>Player 1: Move: A, D or LEFT-RIGHT ARROWS Player 2: Move: LEFT-RIGHT ARROWS</instructions>
<category>2 Player</category>
<tags>.io, 1 Player, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, 3D, 3D Games, Ball, Race, Racing, Skill, WebGL </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/5frcdrr0zclnzo0yla564znzsj8a73px/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/5frcdrr0zclnzo0yla564znzsj8a73px/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>450</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48424</id>
<title>Bubble Eyes</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Immerse yourself in Bubble Eyes, where colorful bubbles with adorable eyes float. Click and draw to match the same-colored bubbles, enjoying a relaxing yet engaging color-matching experience. Aim for high scores in this charming, visually pleasing game.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>Bubble, Color, Draw, Fun, Funny, Games, HTML5, Kids, Matching, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/muznftx6xr2jwcg1anaas1oyr8k1x4wj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/muznftx6xr2jwcg1anaas1oyr8k1x4wj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>40612</id>
<title>Stumble Survival Guys </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Stumble-Survival Guys is a very hot adventure elimination game. A variety of fun levels await your challenge, and the time has come to test your memory and dexterity! Run, sprint, and slide to overtake your opponents and dodge the obstacles that keep popping up. Can you survive to the end? Invite your friends to join you and kill them all! Stumble-Survival Guys: An Exciting Mobile Gaming Experience for iOS Users In the world of mobile gaming, Survival Guys has emerged as an exciting and addictive game that has captivated iOS users worldwide. Developed by a team of skilled game developers, Survival Guys offers a unique and challenging gaming</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 3D, 3D Games, Action, Adventure, Boy, Boys, Fall Boys, Fall Guys, Fantasy, Kid, Kids, Simulation </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ebzhf7uwcukpaeb1z4ma3yu0mm2g0hrm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ebzhf7uwcukpaeb1z4ma3yu0mm2g0hrm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>854</width>
<height>480</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48365</id>
<title>Face Punch.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step onto the ring to knock out all champions with your brutal punches for real boxing experience in io game universe! BECOME A CHALLENGER BOXER NOW! Attack with fierce face punches and combos to knock out others. Can you become the champion fighter of the boxing io game arena? EASY IO GAME CONTROLS! Smash everyone with your hits and make combos to knockout with only one button in the world of fighting! ULTIMATE FIGHTER SKILLS! Each hero has different special move to use in epic combat to knock out other fighting boxers.</description>
<instructions>COLLECTIBLES! Achieve objectives to unlock amazing heroes with skills and skins! Step onto the classical fighting ring with your favorite hero to survive the longest, make maximum combos or a great number of knockouts! </instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Android, Arcade, Battle, Cool, Hot </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/akub1gx5xgvtbhp6ozi3adxmwmmm6ej2/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/akub1gx5xgvtbhp6ozi3adxmwmmm6ej2/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1334</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48105</id>
<title>Cameraman Plunge</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Challenge your skills in this quirky game as you strategically shift cups to guide the camera into the hilarious Skibidi toilet. Test your precision and wit as you tackle each level, aiming for the perfect drop! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Puzzle</category>
<tags>1 Player, Fun, Games, HTML5, Kids, Puzzle, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet, Skills </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bdburx21inj6lioa9o1gm4t8lju47czj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bdburx21inj6lioa9o1gm4t8lju47czj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48060</id>
<title>Play In Mall</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play an 3D first person water gun game with your friends! During a game break, you can buy items from Amazon (through verified Amazon Associates Program). No download needed, play it in your browser on any device!</description>
<instructions>PC (keyboard + mouse): move: wasd or arrow keys rotate/shoot/select: mouse Mobile, tablet (touchscreen): move: bottom left touch joystick rotate: bottom right touch joystick shoot (with move): upper left touch joystick shoot (with rotate): upper right tou</instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 3D, 3D Games, Fun, Multiplayer, Shooter, Shopping </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/52g15pmd4ni6fcm12oit6r0rkcpj6niv/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/52g15pmd4ni6fcm12oit6r0rkcpj6niv/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>48024</id>
<title>Skibidi Snake.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Skibidi Snake.io is a fast-paced, action-packed snake game that will test your reflexes and strategy skills. In this game, you control a snake that must eat as many Skibidi as possible to grow in size. The longer your snake gets, the more difficult it will be to control, but the more points you will score. Website Developer <a href='https://naptechgames.com/'>https://naptechgames.com/</a></description>
<instructions>Desktop Use the Mouse left click button on the screen to Move Anywhere on the Screen. Mobile Tap on the screen to Move Anywhere on the Screen. </instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 2D, Action, Adventure, Fun, Game, Games, HTML, HTML5, Number, Online, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/88kisw889g91pa7fv6hwqzi0v3g2dbkw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/88kisw889g91pa7fv6hwqzi0v3g2dbkw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47911</id>
<title>Skibidi Toilet Vs Zombies</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Skibidi Toilet Slaughter: Zombie Annihilation is a fun mobile game where players must protect a magical toilet from hordes of zombies using hilarious bathroom-themed weapons on R1Games.com</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io, Fun, Games, HTML5, Kill, Killing, Skibidi, Skibidi Toilet, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bnuzvnrxzudpgvg0ls0xdlblw1x5fhs6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bnuzvnrxzudpgvg0ls0xdlblw1x5fhs6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47890</id>
<title>Freehead Skate</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Freehead Skateis a fast-paced, arcade-style game that challenges players to jump over obstacles using only their characters head. With simple controls and addictive gameplay, players must time their head-jumps perfectly to conquer increasingly challenging levels and achieve high scores. Dive into the exciting world of Freehead Skateand put your head-jumping skills to the test! on R1Games.com</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Action, Fun, Games, Highscore, HTML5, jump, Jumping, Kids, Obstacle, Play </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/museimxpj23qgd30oirvj1xlmc0vouem/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/museimxpj23qgd30oirvj1xlmc0vouem/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47548</id>
<title>Slash Dunk</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Splash Dunk is a captivating basketball puzzle game where players must strategically cut threads to direct the ball into the goal. With limited cuts and complex thread arrangements, your precision and wit will be put to the test!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Basketball, cut, Fun, Games, HTML5, Kid, Kids, Sport, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/r5q7wmk5mdoulxc1pjzpekh8mkcyrsun/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/r5q7wmk5mdoulxc1pjzpekh8mkcyrsun/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47462</id>
<title>Ragdoll Rise Up</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ragdoll Rise Up is an immersive game experience that takes you on a thrilling adventure through ingeniously designed puzzle levels. Fly through the air, avoiding obstacles and deadly traps, while unleashing your power to shatter anything in your path with a simple tap. Balloons will be your companions, but beware of the deadly spikes! Ascend to the top, ensuring the safety of the balloons, and brace yourself for excitement and tension in each level.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io, 1 Player, Arcade, Ballon, Boys, fly, Fun, Funny, Game, Games, HTML, HTML5, Kid, Kids </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/o89li8eh437jmxy3klcmeurj88sbvkib/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/o89li8eh437jmxy3klcmeurj88sbvkib/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47424</id>
<title>Zomblox.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Multiplayer zombie survival game! Invite friends and defeat waves of zombies. Destroy loot boxes to get more powerful weapons. Play on 3 different maps or create your own maps using the level editor. </description>
<instructions>Move - WASD / ARROWS Attack - MOUSE CLICK Jump - SPACE Pickup Weapon - E Show Stats - TAB</instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Action, Multiplayer, Online, Zombie </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rha2cyp1q8590dx3imb4gx8b7p74ilo3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rha2cyp1q8590dx3imb4gx8b7p74ilo3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47486</id>
<title>Depicting the Perfect Parking Spot</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Prepare yourself for a thrilling parking experience! Engage in an exhilarating game where your task is to skillfully park cars while steering clear of collisions. Immerse yourself in an incredible puzzle game with captivating gameplay. Utilize your finger to draw a path and skillfully navigate the car to its designated parking spot. Stay alert, as the risk of colliding with other vehicles is ever-present! Exercise caution and avoid crashing into walls or any other vehicles to successfully complete each puzzle. Plan your moves ahead of time and put your drawing skills to the test as you aim to safely park cars of various colors.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>1 Player, Arcade, Car, Cars, Driving, Fun, Games, HTML5, Kids, Parking, Supercars </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/autb243qdmik6hgy48ua2dbsi61aq73e/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/autb243qdmik6hgy48ua2dbsi61aq73e/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>47032</id>
<title>PAC PAC RUN</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Hello, in this excellent endless running game you will forget the clocks and get lost in time, dont hit the creatures, all your points will go back and you will not like it at all. If you dont crash and you set the highest record, you will set the highest record in Pac Pac Run history.</description>
<instructions>The controls are very simple, you will not have any trouble, if you are on mobile, click anywhere on the screen, if you say pc, just click anywhere with the mouse.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io, 1 Player, 2D, Adventure, Ball, endless, PacMan, running, Space </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ft4t61hdmqso9xy9nrt9728y3w1m2s3d/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ft4t61hdmqso9xy9nrt9728y3w1m2s3d/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>849</width>
<height>400</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>46307</id>
<title>Pixel Wars IO</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Collect pixels and draw beauty with them! The game has elements of hyper casual clicker and pixel art. Here you can not only collect pixels but also draw 2D images on the drawing arena with their help. This is a game for all ages and experience levels: clicker lovers, pixel art lovers and those who just want to draw will love it. Want to have more drawing pixels? Collect power-ups: slow down the movement of obstacles, doubling the won pixels, a magnet to attract bonuses and an extra life. </description>
<instructions>- Left Arrow/Right Arrow - Decrease/increase pixel - Click with the mouse/finger on an empty area of the screen on the game level - move the pixel / resize</instructions>
<category>Hypercasual</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Arena, Board, Draw, Drawing, Hypercasual, Pixel, Relaxation, Skills, Slither, WebGL </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cmb4ekw5gj5ljbl72ifbfw2dknlmy43l/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cmb4ekw5gj5ljbl72ifbfw2dknlmy43l/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>46348</id>
<title>Fish Eat Getting Big</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>These fishes are getting bigger once they start eating little fishes than their size. Call some friends and play the game with up to three players the Fish Eat Getting Big game. Many fishes and various fish types in the huge ocean are waiting for you. Try to hunt smaller fishes which are specified with their numbers and try to reach the biggest size. Each level will bring you some coins and you will be able to buy new fish types from the market. You can also dive into different oceans and keep your adventure in different places. </description>
<instructions>Player 1: Move: W, A, S, D Player 2: Move: ARROW KEYS Player 3: Move: MOUSE and LEFT-CLICK</instructions>
<category>2 Player</category>
<tags>.io Games, 2 Player, 2 Player Games, Animal, Arena, Fish, Fishing, Fun, Funny </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/k8if9upb0h9k96zqoys4yrrbvw9nfxg6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/k8if9upb0h9k96zqoys4yrrbvw9nfxg6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>920</width>
<height>520</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>45966</id>
<title>Game Station</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Mr. Robot has opened a new Game Station in city. Help him to grow the station. Different fun and interesting games to unlock. Fortnite, Forza Horizon, Mortal Kombat etc. Make money, buy waiters to help you, open new areas, find more games, be a millionare. </description>
<instructions>MOUSE DRAG &amp; CONTROL TOUCH DRAG &amp; CONTROL WASD - ARROW KEYS</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Android, Best, Crazy, Fun, Funny, Games, HTML5, Logical, Management, Mobile, Robot </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7zpaf3bjzvw8h03hk3xzb8n1etedtzh5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7zpaf3bjzvw8h03hk3xzb8n1etedtzh5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>450</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>45514</id>
<title>Horror Hide And Seek</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Horror Hide And Seek, Super exciting hide-and-seek game, Horror and thrilling hide-and-seek escape journey! The game takes hide-and-seek as the theme, and adds a variety of modes to choose from, including the classic hide-and-seek mode and the butcher mode where you can enjoy hunting.In addition, there are multiple modes such as single player, multiplayer, and transformed items to fight against the butcher. The game also adds some horror elements, whether it is from the screen or sound effects, it has a terrifying atmosphere. giving players a new hide-and-seek game experience!</description>
<instructions>Follow the game tutorial.</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io, Adventure </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1wb05eeb80ooxoas1qsxeuo2bqrxfqbl/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1wb05eeb80ooxoas1qsxeuo2bqrxfqbl/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>22364</id>
<title>Rollem.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Rollem.io is a free IOGame. If you love animals, and especially these tiny ones that are like little loving balls of fur, called Hamsters, you're going to love the protagonists of this online multiplayer io game. Cute hamsters, unique environment, and skill-based controls mix together to bring you the cutest of the io games out there. Prepare to embark in an adventure never seen before as you level up your hamster and unlock new stuff to make it unique and your very own! Rollem.io is the worldwide online multiplayer fast-paced hamster racing game, takes on races against people all over the world and try to beat the quickest records on each track! Noticed the golden coins over the level? Be sure to collect as much as you can, because in the game shop, you can unlock skins and trails which will make your hamster look unique, some skins & trails are also limited and exclusive, so be sure to keep an eye watching! Watch out for swinging hammers, as they will bump you out of your path so you fall and have to restart from the spawn area, and use fans and springs to get to higher places on the level, where there may be more golden coins to collect, or even the goal of the level. The levels for this online game are very tricky, so you have to always keep an eye where you're moving, as there can be holes and other kind of obstacles to prevent you from completing the level, jump, dodge and go very fast as you make your way through while seeing other players falling from the sky, what a fun experience! You can also notice that each time a game ends you get your Worldwide Position, this means the game can also be competitive, and you can show up in the largest of the leaderboards found in the menu, if you're good enough you could make your name last forever in this space, not only that; If you beat a time record on *any* level, you will get your name and time featured in the Leaderboards Panel in the spawn area, how cool is that? But keep on it, as other people will take it on and try to beat your times to kick you out of the board, how long will you last? It also comes with a level editor, so feel free to come up with your own tracks, and they will get added to the game automatically so other people will be able to race them. Rollem.io is playable on the browser, in a computer or in a mobile device, don't forget to try it out or you might miss out on an awesome game experience! I won't be keeping your attention for more, get in with your new cute hamster, race with him and other players online, and most importantly; Enjoy!</description>
<instructions>Controls: - W, A, S, D to move. - Mouse to look around and Jump. The game supports gamepads! So if you got an xbox360, PS4 or PS5 controller, you can connect it to your device and start playing as if it was a console game</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>Animal, Jumping, Multiplayer, Online, Race, Racing, Skill </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/8oqao5vefo041ymfs8wz9mqs3gudrj1k/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/8oqao5vefo041ymfs8wz9mqs3gudrj1k/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>9417</id>
<title>tankroyale.io</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Fight for glory in this cartoony fast-paced top-down online multiplayer shooter set in a small battle royale arena against players over the world! Be the last to die, get medals and gold. Unlock items and reach the top of the leaderboard to win the current Season!</description>
<instructions>DESKTOP: [W,A,S,D] / [ARROW KEYS] = MOVE Mouse = aim Mouse LEFT = fire Mouse RIGHT = activate ultimate MOBILE: First tap and drag to move your tank around! </instructions>
<category>Multiplayer</category>
<tags>.io, Battle, Cartoon, Multiplayer, Online, Shooter, Tank, Tanks </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/fn9vwjbz016gtopbym2ym8seotllh0kw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/fn9vwjbz016gtopbym2ym8seotllh0kw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>900</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>44656</id>
<title>Gun Shooting CS</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready for the ultimate adrenaline-fueled adventure in the desert? SandStrike is the game for you! This action-packed multiplayer shooting game is perfect for kids who want to experience the excitement of high-speed battles and outmaneuvering their opponents. With four different game modes to choose from, including classic team deathmatch and capture the flag, SandStrike offers endless possibilities for thrilling gameplay. And with a wide range of customizable weapons and equipment, you can tailor your loadout to suit your play style and dominate the competition. But the real excitement comes when you hop into one of SandStrike's awesome vehicles. From armored trucks to powerful helicopters, these vehicles are the key to gaining the upper hand in battle. Use them to outmaneuver your opponents, launch surprise attacks, and make your way to the top of the leaderboard. As you battle it out against other players, you'll be blown away by the immersive sound effects and stunning graphics that make you feel like you're really in the middle of the desert. And with a variety of challenging levels and objectives, you'll never get bored playing this game. So what are you waiting for? Grab your friends and get ready to experience the ultimate in multiplayer shooting excitement with SandStrike. The battle for supremacy in the desert is on  are you ready to emerge victorious?</description>
<instructions>Controls: WASD = move Mouse = aim / shoot / switch weapons Space = jump Shift = crouch E = enter / exit vehicle </instructions>
<category>Shooting</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Shoot, Shooter </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/iiw4c0f8956j6slme1qyllux2isfmaml/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/iiw4c0f8956j6slme1qyllux2isfmaml/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>46185</id>
<title>Go Penguine</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Go Penguine is an exciting top-view game where players take control of an adorable penguin character. The games perspective provides a birds-eye view of the action-packed gameplay. Your main objective is to guide the penguin through various environments and help it satisfy its hunger by devouring fishes. As you navigate through the game world, youll encounter schools of fishes swimming around. You must skillfully maneuver the penguin to catch and consume as many fishes as possible. This requires precise movements and quick reflexes to snatch the fishes before they swim away.</description>
<instructions>In Go Penguine, you control the penguin character using arrow keys. The arrow keys enable you to move the penguin in various directions - up, down, left, and right. Your goal is to navigate the penguin through the game world, collecting fishes and avoidin</instructions>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io Games, 1 Player, Collection, Game </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/4yragvbh699ncw5esah7vrtjbotcooa9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/4yragvbh699ncw5esah7vrtjbotcooa9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>42645</id>
<title>FNF Music Battle</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Music Battle is a rhythm music game to test your musical knowledge and reflexes where you have to feel the rhythm of the music.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Clicker</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, Clicker, Music </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/h93y4d3w0vomo32j381qvi5vgk7l76qr/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/h93y4d3w0vomo32j381qvi5vgk7l76qr/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>900</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>45655</id>
<title>Staire Race</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Stair Race 3D Game Get ready for one of the most challenging games and build your stairs as fast as you can! You have to compete in a large arena who is the best at building stairs against a variety of difficult enemies In order to win, you have to pick up the staircase plans and use them to build the stairs and reach the next platform But watch out, enemies with more boards collected than you can easily crush you when you bump into them which will cause you to lose all your collected plans But of course it works in reverse too, so try to collect as many plans as you can and beat your enemies to get a big advantage Winning rounds will not only give you the pleasure of being the best player in the world It will also unlock cool new skins for your character and plans Are you ready to compete in the worlds biggest stair building challenge? Get ready for one of the most challenging games and build your stairs as fast as you can</description>
<instructions>tap to run</instructions>
<category>3D</category>
<tags>.io, .io Games, 1 Player, 3D, 3D Games </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/cvyynje4d6s1kgrh6vwiazccb3eyr2uh/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/cvyynje4d6s1kgrh6vwiazccb3eyr2uh/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>45714</id>
<title>NabNab Imposter</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>NabNab Imposter - Fun io game is a super cool, easy and relaxing game. To win this, your mission is simple: Smash other crewmate by a huge hammer, Consume their power to become bigger and stronger, Be the only NabNab Imposter survival in the battlefield. However, be carefull and try to advoid bumping into other tricky impostors, otherwise, youll be smashed. You can choose among serveral roles to add more exciment: Hunter, Assasin, Captain, Trapper, Sword, Gunner... with unlimited skills and items. In this io game, where mutilplayer battle other to be the last one who survive, making yourseft a strong and smart one is crucial. Its super fun, check it out! </description>
<instructions>- Hold and drag to move - Get closer to crewmates and smash them - Run fast and dont be hit</instructions>
<category>Action</category>
<tags>.io Games, 1 Player, 3D, Action </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/w1voyhhgd4z7kgx9e4aid2iwjsr0qjec/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/w1voyhhgd4z7kgx9e4aid2iwjsr0qjec/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>960</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>45663</id>
<title>Pifflo</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Discover Piffle a cute arcade puzzle game full of adorable characters and...cats! Put your cat onesie on, quest through colorful worlds, stop the nefarious Doc Block and craft adorable Piffle balls to collect.</description>
<instructions>- Swipe or point with your finger to aim - Choose the best possible angle to shoot - Release to bounce around and break all the blocks</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io Games, 1 Player, 2D, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/4ylhli6ijr0lby3srncc3rremkalvfsz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/4ylhli6ijr0lby3srncc3rremkalvfsz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>960</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>44854</id>
<title>Impostor Royal Run</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Our category of Among Us Games is not really known for running games and obstacle course games, which is why we are delighted that such a 3d game online has now been added here for all of you to enjoy and have tons of fun with, a game called Impostor Run, where we've had tons of fun, so why would the same not be true for you as well? In each level of the game you are being chased by the impostor, who has a knife and wants to stab you, so your goal is to go across the course and reach its finish without being caught up by him, or you will die and be forced to start the level from scratch. There will be obstacles to avoid, as well as guns shooting at you, so avoid them too. Your crewmate is going to run forward by itself, but you will have to use the right and left arrow keys in order to avoid the obstacles and traps you encounter. Each new level will have a course more difficult than the one before it, so you should also step your game up so that nothing can stand in your way. Good luck!</description>
<instructions>Use the arrow keys.</instructions>
<category>Arcade</category>
<tags>.io Games, 2 Player, 3D Games, Action, Arcade </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/1sdn584r8j8nwhtnk4lkhzh6zjg2cebp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/1sdn584r8j8nwhtnk4lkhzh6zjg2cebp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>44567</id>
<title>rider 2023</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Perform insane stunts while you cruise through the never-ending world of Rider 2! Grab your motorcycle and start flipping to get unlimited coins! Make insane jumps and challenge your opponents with the best scores. You can buy your own favorite motorcycle and become master rider in flipping your bike.</description>
<instructions/>
<category>Adventure</category>
<tags>.io Games, 2 Player, 3D, Action, Adventure </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/q9vlc7cdbzuaphuebcriv09cq2f7l2td/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/q9vlc7cdbzuaphuebcriv09cq2f7l2td/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>