This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</title>
<link> https://gamemonetize.com</link>
<description>Game Feed From GameMonetize.com</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<atom:link href="https://gamemonetize.com" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
<id>68145</id>
<title>Formula Go</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Get behind the wheel of a high-speed Formula 1 car and challenge clever AI competitors on detailed tracks modeled after famous real-world circuits. Formula Go offers thrilling racing with responsive controls, intense competition, and a focus on driving skill. Fine-tune your vehicle, navigate sharp bends, and push your limits to secure a top spot on the podium.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, Cars, Driving, free html5 games for your website, Kart, Racing, Road, Sport, Supercars </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ss7hiku3sutu1jiftnohynx0d4nddhhm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ss7hiku3sutu1jiftnohynx0d4nddhhm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66975</id>
<title>Tennis Dash</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Tennis Dash is a fast and fun game where a cute cat plays tennis like a pro! The tennis ball comes from different directions, and your job is to move the cat left and right to hit it. Be quick&mdash;if you miss the ball three times, the game is over! It&rsquo;s easy to play but really hard to master. Try to beat your own high score and keep the rally going! </description>
<instructions>Desktop: Click and Drag Left or Right = Move the Cat/bear Mobile: Tap and drag Left or Right = Move the Cat/bear </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Casual, Fun, HTML, html5 games, Hypercasual, NapTech Games, Sports, Tennis </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/h8381esputdzb7w30swugmh9aufj4lrz/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/h8381esputdzb7w30swugmh9aufj4lrz/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1080</width>
<height>1920</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67874</id>
<title>Super Ball Juggling Remix</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Super Ball Juggling Remix is a fast-paced arcade game where you juggle a soccer ball without letting it drop &mdash; but with a twist! Travel across iconic locations like Paris, New York, Rome, Pisa, and Sydney, showcasing your freestyle skills in stunning backdrops. Simple to play, hard to master, and packed with global style &mdash; how long can you keep the ball in the air?</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ball, mapi games, Soccer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ocuawximv8s4omrwf7t8linvh4lsl9u5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ocuawximv8s4omrwf7t8linvh4lsl9u5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>1024</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67695</id>
<title>Super Motocross </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ride your dirt bike through challenging levels full of ramps, jumps, and obstacles. Balance, accelerate, and reach the finish line without crashing! A fun and fast-paced HTML5 motocross game for all ages.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Arcade, mapi games, Motocross, Motorcycle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/d8vjyjtwgj1c7opsa1e99ifmvnfvgvn8/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/d8vjyjtwgj1c7opsa1e99ifmvnfvgvn8/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>800</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>67138</id>
<title>Arcade Pong Deluxe</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Arcade Pong Deluxe: Classic arcade action reborn! Challenge smart AI, enjoy full-screen play, responsive controls, and customizable sound. Dive into retro fun!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Air, Arcade, Classic, Defense, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/f15sddte014o8cumjvx9oy0n3puiapn7/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/f15sddte014o8cumjvx9oy0n3puiapn7/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>450</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65267</id>
<title>Underwater Aim</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Underwater Aim dives deep into the classic 8-ball pool experience&mdash;now with a refreshing underwater twist! Challenge your skills in beautifully designed ocean-themed tables where every shot feels smooth and satisfying. Line up your cue, calculate the angles, and sink all your balls before your opponent in this immersive pool game. From shimmering jellyfish lights to coral-lined pockets, each level is bursting with aquatic charm. Play solo, challenge friends, or compete in underwater tournaments. Unlock cues, explore sea-themed arenas, and become the ultimate pool shark of the deep. Cue up and make a splash in Underwater Aim!</description>
<instructions>Use mouse or touch scren for play game.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2 Player, 8 Ball Pool, Pool </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/hksjgjkch7vvkjnpwboj6noif3qm8osd/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/hksjgjkch7vvkjnpwboj6noif3qm8osd/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>66452</id>
<title>College Basketball Games Today </title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>College Basketball Games Today is the ultimate arcade-style college basketball game for fans who love fast-paced sports action! Play solo or challenge a friend in the exciting 2-player basketball mode. With fun cartoon graphics and characters inspired by legendary basketball players, this game offers a thrilling mix of dunks, 3-pointers, and buzzer-beaters. Perfect for quick matches or full tournaments, its the ideal basketball game for kids and adults alike. Whether playing a quick match or climbing the ranks, College Basketball Games Today brings classic basketball arcade gameplay with a modern twist. Get ready to hit the court,</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Basketball </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/red1ovg6fjny2ulquxvt4y3ah0xby91y/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/red1ovg6fjny2ulquxvt4y3ah0xby91y/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64751</id>
<title>Football Manager Simulator</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this new era, all national leagues have been removed and now all teams play in 4 international divisions! Have you ever thought of creating and managing a club? Create your own football club and lead it towards glory in Football Manager Simulator! Manage your squad, tactics, and finances, compete in leagues and climb to the top division, sign football stars and coach your players to make them better! However, the road to glory wont be easy... Youll need to earn the money for coaching, signing players, and academy scouting. Upgrade your stadium to win more money on home matches and get sponsors to earn crucial amounts of money!</description>
<instructions>Navigate through the tabs to access different functionality. Squad allows you to change starting XI; Transfer Market allows signing new talents; League shows your league position; Academy lets you scout for the next big talent; Coaching improves team</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Management, Soccer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/tf0usn5yp3zl9e70xl8qhspky9k8qvx5/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/tf0usn5yp3zl9e70xl8qhspky9k8qvx5/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65479</id>
<title>Tiny Billiard</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description> Tiny Billiard is the ultimate mini pool game &ndash; fast, fun, and full of color! Dive into quick matches with smooth one-touch controls and challenge yourself with crazy trick shots. Unlock a variety of fun cues, each with its own style and effects. Whether youre a casual player or a billiard pro, Tiny Billiard offers addictive gameplay in a cute 2D cartoon world. Perfect for all ages!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>8 Ball Pool, Billiard, mapi games, Pool, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/c3btewong9vmfv2tgd58mds3rua8csnb/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/c3btewong9vmfv2tgd58mds3rua8csnb/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1024</width>
<height>768</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>65183</id>
<title>Pool Legends Pro Masters</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Pool Legends Pro Master is a fast-paced billiards game where precision and speed are the keys to victory! Aim, shoot, and sink the balls as quickly as possible to rack up high scores and dominate the table. The faster you clear the table, the better your rank! With realistic physics, smooth controls, and exciting challenges, Pool Legends Pro Master offers an immersive pool experience for casual players and pros alike. Do you have what it takes to become the ultimate pool legend? Grab your cue and start playing now! </description>
<instructions>Play Pool!</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>8 Ball Pool, Best Games, Poppy Playtime, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/wu0ftlytyls9qo3i0fxaya28455o613b/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/wu0ftlytyls9qo3i0fxaya28455o613b/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64699</id>
<title>Ring Master Legends</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Ring Master Legends is an action-packed boxing game that tests your speed, reflexes, and precision! Step into the ring and punch your way to victory by matching your gloves to the falling balls&mdash;use the Red glove for red balls and the Blue glove for blue balls. The more accurate your hits, the higher your score! With fast-paced gameplay, dynamic animations, and increasing difficulty, Ring Master Legends will keep you on your toes as you strive for the ultimate high score. Do you have what it takes to become a true legend of the ring? Step in, gear up, and start punching! </description>
<instructions>Click and break the balls :)</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Boxing, Click </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/spfuv2y132wi7j1qdrdv77zztly1huvp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/spfuv2y132wi7j1qdrdv77zztly1huvp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64418</id>
<title>Basketball School</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Basketball School is the basketball arcade game in which you must try to score baskets in all the different game modes available. You can play either arcade, time attack, and distance mode. Arcade mode gives you 10 balls to use; you must continue to score baskets although it becomes harder each time you score. Time attack mode requires you to score as many baskets within the time limit as possible; you have unlimited balls but limited time. Distance mode allows you to increase the distance of your shot each time that you score. </description>
<instructions>Drag left mouse button to aim, release to shoot.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ball, Basketball, Skills, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/nbp2sis89qudoxmihm1q6x7mdpotsf6b/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/nbp2sis89qudoxmihm1q6x7mdpotsf6b/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>500</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63811</id>
<title>Velocity Puck</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Get ready for fast-paced, physics-driven air hockey action in Velocity Puck! Designed with Three.js for smooth 3D gameplay, this game brings intense one-on-one air hockey battles to life with dynamic puck physics, AI opponents, and character customization. Key Features: Realistic Physics &ndash; Experience high-speed gameplay with fluid puck movement and skill-based rebounds. Single &amp; Multiplayer (Coming Soon) &ndash; Challenge AI opponents or test your reflexes against real players. Customization &ndash; Choose from different characters and paddle colors to make your mark. Immersive Audio &amp; Visuals &ndash; Enjoy neon-lit arenas and satisfying sound </description>
<instructions> Basic Controls: Move Paddle (Mouse/Touch) Mouse: Move your cursor to control the paddle. Touchscreen: Drag your finger to move the paddle. Hit the Puck Simply move your paddle into the puck to strike it. The force and angle determine the puck&rsquo;s m</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/jll9bmbb1qxr1uux1t1khn56z4xpvibs/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/jll9bmbb1qxr1uux1t1khn56z4xpvibs/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64665</id>
<title>Power Puncher</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Power Puncher is a thrilling arcade game that puts your punching power to the test. As a skilled boxer, your mission is to survive a barrage of wooden boxes by expertly smashing them to pieces. How to Play: Time Your Punches: Carefully watch as wooden boxes of varying sizes and shapes approach you. Aim for the Center: Target the center of each box to deliver the most powerful blow. Avoid Sharp Edges: Dodge the sharp edges of the boxes to prevent injury. Chain Combos: Land consecutive punches to increase your score and unlock special power-ups.</description>
<instructions>Click to Punch!</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Arcade, Boxing, Punch </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/b1bs81bovd287yxmsx5af8vms6awdnm6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/b1bs81bovd287yxmsx5af8vms6awdnm6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64329</id>
<title>Basketball Arcade</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In this game, you will grab your favorite basketball and will try to score as many points as possible. All of the free throws will happen from different angles and distances. Pick your favorite team and try to be the best player around! There is a time limit, so you need to be quick. You have a total of 20 balls that you can use. It&rsquo;s no easy task, since you need to guess the angle and strength that you need to hit. How to play: - Pick up the ball over the table. - Press and hold left mouse button, when shooting, to increase the shooting force. Force will show on the right indicator. - Shoot and try to get the most score before time is over</description>
<instructions>WASD - Movement LMB - Shooting Space - Jump Aim - Mouse</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ball, Basketball, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/zn51bpwab321ow86zhq55orvs30a9zkh/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/zn51bpwab321ow86zhq55orvs30a9zkh/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>500</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64425</id>
<title>Basketball Park</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Start the game with 10 balls. Drag and release to shoot. Score without touching the rim to earn extra balls. Aim for high scores to unlock helpful creatures. Check the leaderboard to see how you compete with the top players. Special creatures might pop up to lend assistance as you hit score milestones, adding a fun and unpredictable twist.</description>
<instructions>Drag and release to shoot</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Ball, Basketball, Highscore, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/kyn5fpfwlh86jgcsff85trjsxntpva2i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/kyn5fpfwlh86jgcsff85trjsxntpva2i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>64175</id>
<title>Bow Masters Arena</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description> Become the Ultimate Archer in Bow Masters Arena! Are you ready to test your archery skills and compete against AI archers? Bow Masters Arena is the ultimate archery showdown where precision, strategy, and quick reflexes determine the champion. Train hard, master your shots, and enter thrilling battles against AI-controlled opponents to prove you are the best archer! How to Play? Train Your Skills &ndash; Perfect your aim and timing in practice mode. Compete in AI Tournaments &ndash; Face off against intelligent AI archers in high-stakes duels. Unlock Powerful Bows &ndash; Upgrade your weapons for more accuracy and strength.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, Arena, arrow </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/7gmrptnujb86szaxdideuock4g6ayc3f/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/7gmrptnujb86szaxdideuock4g6ayc3f/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63860</id>
<title>Baseball Star</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Baseball Star is a fun casual sports game that lets you feel the excitement and joy of playing baseball. As a star on the field. Swing the bat and hitting the ball. Hit the ball with precision. It&rsquo;s easy to start. But the challenges will get harder.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ball, Baseball, Skills, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/lz24q5j25atdbwmkfy9r04cig938m8f9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/lz24q5j25atdbwmkfy9r04cig938m8f9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63807</id>
<title>Penalty Shooters</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step onto the field and play football with your favorite cartoon stars in this action-packed, fun-filled game! Experience thrilling matches, show off your skills, and compete against other characters in exciting challenges. Whether you&rsquo;re scoring goals, making incredible passes, or defending your side, Football Stars offers endless entertainment for football fans of all ages. Join the fun and become a legend on the pitch! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Cartoon, Football, Kids, Mobile, Soccer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ikh1qxnldwl6x7lc8xapp1src26tbdtj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ikh1qxnldwl6x7lc8xapp1src26tbdtj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63534</id>
<title>Hoop Master Basketball Trivia Challenge</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Test your basketball knowledge with this fast-paced and fun quiz game! Dive into 10 exciting questions that challenge your understanding of the sport, from iconic players and legendary matches to surprising stats and trivia. Whether youre a casual fan or a hardcore hoops enthusiast, this game is your slam dunk for basketball trivia. Perfect for quick gaming sessions and for those who love a good challenge. How many can you score?</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, Basketball, Quiz, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/q7mqysmx6prgpafi1wwcwhcqmjg0yf2u/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/q7mqysmx6prgpafi1wwcwhcqmjg0yf2u/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>63056</id>
<title>Flip Master</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Flip Master is an exciting game about acrobatics and parkour! Perform spectacular tricks, execute breathtaking flips, and conquer challenging obstacles. Control your character in the air, perfect your jumping technique, and land flawlessly. Upgrade your skills, explore new locations, and become the ultimate master of extreme flips!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Jumping, Levels, Mobile, Obstacle, Stunts </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/t5h6lmvu96x7kk5bj6v5n6999o7mf9f1/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/t5h6lmvu96x7kk5bj6v5n6999o7mf9f1/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62403</id>
<title>Royal Prince Tailor Master 2025</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The Royal Prince Tailor Master: Clothing Shop 2018 opened the actual personalization for the royal family members and their dresses on their demand. It attracts many customers to modify their clothes. Do you want to help the finest tailor in the city? Help your customers choose the desired styles. Measure your customers body, choose the right fabrics, cut them into perfect shape and copy them. Work with a perfect Tailor and manage customization of the royal dresses combinations. Do you want to become a fashion designer? Do you want to make some great clothes? This real tailor and the clothing shop will help you to understand your dream. </description>
<instructions>characteristics: * Various colors, and clothing styles * Decorate your clothes with beautiful accessories * Dress your clients in princesses or princes with your hands * Enjoy the creation of interesting clothes * Decorate your store\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\\</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Arcade, Boys, Car, car tuning, carparking, Stunts </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/te1ixl4evp63xx4d48nqq99pmrpp4ywm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/te1ixl4evp63xx4d48nqq99pmrpp4ywm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>640</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62743</id>
<title>Beach Volley Clash</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Welcome to Beach Volley Clash! This vibrant and energetic beach sports game takes you to a lively beach arena. You&rsquo;ll face off against powerful opponents. Use your skills and quick reflexes to hit the ball precisely and win every match!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ball, Matching, Skill </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/158487q1u8me9wtra4wd7nrk5qz3hq4y/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/158487q1u8me9wtra4wd7nrk5qz3hq4y/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62106</id>
<title>Car Repair And Wash</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Car washing garage games are a fun and exciting way to enjoy the thrill of car cleaning and customizing virtual cars. In these car washing auto mechanic games, you step into the shoes of a car mechanic and get to work in an Auto garage filled with dirty, dusty, and sometimes even incredibly messy vehicles. Your mission is to transform these dirty cars into sparkling, shiny masterpieces. These mechanic simulator car games allow you to explore your creativity, choosing from various car cleaning tools, paints, and accessories to make the cars look their best.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play Features of car washing mechanic simulator: Experience the fun of washing, repairing, and customizing virtual cars just like a car mechanic Choose from various tools, paints, and accessories to make cars look unique and stylish </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Car, car tuning, carparking </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/bn8u1uqsj4gk6m0q0572qswffawq6soq/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/bn8u1uqsj4gk6m0q0572qswffawq6soq/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>640</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>62008</id>
<title>Real GT Racing Simulator</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Real GT Racing Simulator offers the ultimate driving experience for racing enthusiasts. Get behind the wheel of meticulously detailed cars and race on stunningly realistic tracks. Compete in high-speed circuits, fine-tune your vehicle for peak performance, and rise through the ranks to become a true racing legend. This game emphasizes authentic driving physics, customizable cars, and a variety of racing modes&mdash;from casual races to full championship tournaments. Perfect for players who crave a true motorsport challenge, Real GT Racing Simulator will test your skills and precision on every corner.</description>
<instructions>WASD - move esc - pause</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, Cars, Crazy, drifting, Driving </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/g4ydbpcjitxu3lo0hndbelk00qae6iut/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/g4ydbpcjitxu3lo0hndbelk00qae6iut/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61911</id>
<title>Sprunki Tennis</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play with the Sprunki in this exciting arcade sports game is easy to pick up but challenging to master if you are aiming for high scores! Like in a classic tennis match, returning the balls demands speed and precision one misstep, and its game over! The longer you stay on the court, the faster the tennis balls come flying at you, and its up to you to return each one while dodging airborne bottles. Be warned: earning the Platinum medal is a true test of skill! Only those with grand slam-worthy reflexes can claim it! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>mapi games, Sprunki, Tennis </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/t7476kcs8qiazbv0j6o97iqvx21wp78z/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/t7476kcs8qiazbv0j6o97iqvx21wp78z/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>768</width>
<height>1024</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61624</id>
<title>8 Ball Shoot It All 3D Pool</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>best pool gaming with 3D graphics &amp; real-time 3D Zoom! So interesting, you can play like youre at a real pool table, cue in hand, aiming for a victorious shot! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>3D Games, Sport, Sports, Unity3D </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/irq6s4qz3f0h452m9rtmp1obhfpcfdf3/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/irq6s4qz3f0h452m9rtmp1obhfpcfdf3/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61455</id>
<title>Checkers for two</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Play classic checkers. Plan your moves and try to beat the computer or your opponent. The application may be interesting for fans of checkers and useful for beginners who want to improve their game. You can play together against each other, or against the computer (there are several levels of computer difficulty).</description>
<instructions>To make a move, click or click on the checker, and then click or click on the next cell. All moves should be made towards the edge of the opponents board, you can only walk on black squares. You can walk diagonally. Jumping over the opponents checkers.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>2 Player, 2 Player Games, 3D, 3D Games, Brain, Casual, Educational, Family, Fun, Logic, Logical, Matching, Memory, Play </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/o8szudiez7aflkkdocuvs7z8o3xeawfh/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/o8szudiez7aflkkdocuvs7z8o3xeawfh/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61594</id>
<title>Sprunki VS Pirates</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Sprunki Vs Pirates is an exciting sports game to play for all ages. Get into this technical game that tests your aiming ability to make a goal. The challenge is simple yet thrilling: how long can you stay in the game? Your endurance is determined by how well you can aim. Calculate the right angle and degree of force and launch the Ninja through into the basket! In Sprunki Vs Pirates, you need to master the art of precision. Each level presents new obstacles and challenges, ensuring that the game remains engaging and stimulating.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Basketball, mapi games, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m9jlea8vrshpp1wbps50h8jhu7toajor/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m9jlea8vrshpp1wbps50h8jhu7toajor/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1024</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>61502</id>
<title>Sprunki Ball Juggling</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>How many times can you juggle these two soccer balls? How to play: Tap the left side of the screen to kick the left football. Tap the right side of the screen to kick the right football. Don&rsquo;t let the balls fall! Warning: This game is highly addictive! Meet Sprunki - your quirky sidekick! Sprunki&rsquo;s always cheering you on with wild antics and funny comments as you juggle! The more you play, the crazier Sprunki gets, offering silly tips and goofy distractions that make the game even more fun. Keep those balls in the air... and see how long you can last before Sprunki cracks you up!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Casual, Football, mapi games, Soccer, Sport, Sprunki </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/x1c3mft057lzkpoiyosep65il6niwz5s/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/x1c3mft057lzkpoiyosep65il6niwz5s/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>1024</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>60960</id>
<title>Relative Velocity Casual Physics</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Relative Velocity is a casual 3D navigation game where you control a boat in an environment with waves and currents. The objective is to adjust the relative velocity vector to navigate a path to the finish line while collecting coins along the way. The boats movement physics has been carefully implemented manually to simulate the interaction with waves and currents, offering a fun and engaging experience about relative velocity. Scoring System: Points are based on two factors: the number of coins collected and the total time taken to complete the level. Progressive Levels: The difficulty increases with each level.</description>
<instructions>How to Play Control the boats relative velocity vector using the on-screen joystick. Follow the path to the finish line. Collect coins along the way. Complete levels as quickly as possible to achieve the highest score.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 3D, 3D Games, Casual, Educational, HTML5, Hypercasual, Physics, Science, ships, Simulation, Simulator, Summer, touch </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/skcl4ctdx0s9yffd2mzoyq1fyao1qim6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/skcl4ctdx0s9yffd2mzoyq1fyao1qim6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>333</width>
<height>594</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59545</id>
<title>Car Stunt Chipi Chipi Chapa Chapa Cat</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Car Stunt Chipi Chipi Chapa Chapa Cat is a fun meme game where you need to drive car as chipi cat, collect power-ups for more fun drivinf and drift, and watch Chipy Chipy Chipa Cat and El Primo Bara Bere drift. Go through interesting and exciting levels in the fun game about Chippy Chippy Chippy Chappa Chappa Cat and El Primo. Pass levels of different difficulty and set a personal record.</description>
<instructions>WSAD or arrow keys to move</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Arcade, Car, car tuning, carparking </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/dzn1ctogmep1q5mtqsw8eazb7p999eqt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/dzn1ctogmep1q5mtqsw8eazb7p999eqt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>960</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58497</id>
<title>Downhill Christmas Dash</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>The snow is falling and Santa Claus is hitting the slopes! He has strapped on pair of skis and is racing down the hill collecting gift boxes along the way. Race to the bottom and collect as many gifts as you can, but look out for those evil Snowmen! They are out to stop Santa from his Christmas mission. If you bump into a snowman you will fall and the game will end. There are special power-ups along the way that will help you get a higher score. The winged boots increase your speed and raise the gifts scores. The golden star make you invincible for 8 seconds. The Christmas sports game will challenge your reflexes and get you in the Christmas</description>
<instructions>Use the right and left arrow key or touch the onscreen arrows to control Santas direction. Collect the gifts and avoid the snowmen.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Christmas, Magic, Sports, surprize </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gy8anb0a2zg6t4mg3ey98w29x05plzw6/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gy8anb0a2zg6t4mg3ey98w29x05plzw6/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58515</id>
<title>Drive Ahead Sports</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Want to begin a pixelated sports showdown like no other? In Drive Ahead! Sports, you&rsquo;ll be behind the wheel of amazing vehicles, engaging in exciting soccer matches! Enjoy the rush of driving and the fun of the game! Use your skills to kick the ball, attack the opponents goal, and aim for victory! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Battle, Football, vehicle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/w9r10xj16ki396ug6ug7pdppe9ro0d3e/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/w9r10xj16ki396ug6ug7pdppe9ro0d3e/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1336</width>
<height>640</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59703</id>
<title>Xmas Plinkio</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Drop the magical yellow Christmas Sphere into the festive Pachinko board and watch as it bounces through a dazzling winter wonderland! Navigate a maze of candy canes, sparkling ornaments, and jingling bells to rack up points. Aim for glowing snowflakes to unlock bonus rewards and hit the Santa Hat Zone for the ultimate Christmas jackpot! With every drop, you&rsquo;ll spread holiday cheer&mdash;can you score enough to top Santa&rsquo;s Nice List? Let the Xmas Plinkio fun begin - tap, drop, and win!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Arcade, Ball, Casual, Christmas, mapi games, Physics, Santa, Snow, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/rjofcei81c1r61653868olqnbwlzub1a/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/rjofcei81c1r61653868olqnbwlzub1a/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59317</id>
<title>Soccer Clicker Game</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step onto the pitch! In this match, all you have to do is score goals by clicking on the screen or mouse! Track your goals per second and your total goals as you aim to dominate the field. The clock is set to 45 seconds, and every few seconds, youll get a time bonus to boost your score. Can you become the ultimate striker? Its a simple and fun game - perfect for soccer fans!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, Click, Clicker, Soccer </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/gvfdczltlaud6ornrsjwyogtvz74ydri/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/gvfdczltlaud6ornrsjwyogtvz74ydri/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>600</width>
<height>1024</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>59123</id>
<title>Crazy Basketball Shots</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the thrilling world of Crazy Basketball Shots, where precision meets fun! Test your skills as you aim, shoot, and score in this exciting basketball challenge. The game features a basket hoop and a basketball, providing the perfect setup for endless shooting action. With every shot, the difficulty increases, keeping you on your toes as you perfect your aim and timing. Whether youre a basketball enthusiast or just looking for a quick and engaging way to pass the time, Crazy Basketball Shots is the ultimate game for you! Are you ready to make those epic shots and set high scores? Let the hoops frenzy begin!</description>
<instructions>Mouse or Touch</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Basketball, Crazy, Hypercasual, Kids, Shoot, Sport, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ywlcgobsusmt8glsay6ticjcy64nzd3i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ywlcgobsusmt8glsay6ticjcy64nzd3i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58676</id>
<title>Gravity Ball Challenge</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Embark on an exciting journey with Gravity Ball Adventures, a 2D physics-based puzzle game that puts you in control of a charming, bouncy ball. Your mission is to navigate through a series of challenging levels filled with intricate traps, obstacles, and pitfalls to reach the hoop at the end of each stage. Use your unique ability to manipulate gravity&mdash;turn it on and off&mdash;to overcome the obstacles in your path. Timing and precision are key as you flip gravity to avoid deadly spikes, dodge moving platforms, and slide past tricky barriers. Each level presents a new puzzle to solve, testing your reflexes and strategic thinking.</description>
<instructions>W: Gravity Off S:Gravity On A:Left D:Right</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Avoid, Basketball, Puzzle </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/e6gyiv5voqogcvy02kn5ehdkng6opvqj/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/e6gyiv5voqogcvy02kn5ehdkng6opvqj/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58192</id>
<title>Bunny Goal</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Are you ready to kick, bounce, and score? Bunny Goal combines the thrill of soccer with the fast-paced fun of pinball, creating a unique game that&rsquo;s perfect for all ages! Join our adorable bunny character on a journey to become a soccer superstar. Each level is packed with vibrant environments, challenging obstacles, and dynamic pinball action that requires quick reflexes and sharp strategy. Whether you&rsquo;re looking for a quick fun game to pass the time or aiming to beat every level and set a high score, Bunny Goal has something for everyone. Are you ready to take on the pinball soccer challenge and lead the bunny to victory? </description>
<instructions>Desktop: Click, hold, and drag the mouse to aim the ball in the direction you want to shoot. Release the mouse to launch the ball. Mobile: Simply tap and hold on the screen, drag in the direction you want to aim, and release to launch the ball. </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Casual, Football, html5 games, NapTech Games, Sport, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/mnqj10l3wzrla0pcc7jdw7lqo2wbwiq9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/mnqj10l3wzrla0pcc7jdw7lqo2wbwiq9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>16151</id>
<title>Cartoon Football</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Yuki & Rina are 2 young talented football players. They showed incredible football skills and their coach and manager decided it was time to train them to become Pro Players in the famous “Soccer stars Major Football League”. Before becoming Pro Players, Yûki & Rina must pass the ultimate test, which is a combination of agility, skills and reflex. They have to run on the football field as fast as possible with the ball while dribbling opponents, jump over obstacle, collect items and bonus, and more… </description>
<instructions>Yuki & Rina are 2 young talented football players. They showed incredible football skills and their coach and manager decided it was time to train them to become Pro Players in the famous “Soccer stars Major Football League”. Before becoming Pro Players, </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ben 10, Cartoon, Cartoon Network, Casual, Football, Fun, Funny, Hypercasual, jump, Jumping, Kid, Kids, run, running, Sport, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/vtcmrc1oaxmnxtvvjm23xy547qtw4jq0/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/vtcmrc1oaxmnxtvvjm23xy547qtw4jq0/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58502</id>
<title>Mini Tennis</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>This exciting arcade sports game is easy to pick up but challenging to master if youre aiming for high scores! Like in a classic tennis match, returning the balls demands speed and precision one misstep, and its game over! The longer you stay on the court, the faster the tennis balls come flying at you, and its up to you to return each one while dodging airborne bottles. Be warned: earning the Platinum medal is a true test of skill! Only those with grand slam-worthy reflexes can claim it!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>mapi games, Sport, Tennis </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/0g1lbwa9t0i9se2gx1a15f0x1j5eto2t/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/0g1lbwa9t0i9se2gx1a15f0x1j5eto2t/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>768</width>
<height>1024</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58517</id>
<title>Mini Goalie</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Jump into the action as the goalie in Mini Goalie! In this exciting game, put your reflexes to the test as you slide the goalkeeper across the goal line to block every penalty kick. Your mission as the ultimate goalie is clear: defend the net against an endless wave of incoming shots. Make incredible saves, hone your skills, and keep those goals out! How to Play: The computer will launch soccer balls toward the goal. Swipe on the screen to control your mini goalie and intercept each shot. Get ready to dive, block, and defend! Play Mini Goalie now and become the ultimate Soccer Goalkeeper Superstar!</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Football, mapi games, Soccer, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/ttig4tj1axodc6zcnc88fon5qm27yprt/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/ttig4tj1axodc6zcnc88fon5qm27yprt/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>768</width>
<height>1024</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58484</id>
<title>3D Golf Adventure</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>3D Golf Adventure is a fun and engaging online game designed for players of all ages. This game combines elements of mini-golf with an exciting 3D environment, bringing a fresh twist to the traditional golfing experience.The goal in 3D Golf Adventure is simple: get the golf ball into the hole. Players need to carefully aim and control the power of their shots to navigate through each course. Avoiding Obstacles: Watch out for water hazards and walls scattered around the terrain. These obstacles add a layer of challenge, requiring players to strategize their shots to avoid losing strokes or getting stuck.</description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Ball, Boys, Fun, Golf, Hypercasual, Kids, Physics, Skill, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/lktavtmelnunk2sl1erg9q4hsn85islm/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/lktavtmelnunk2sl1erg9q4hsn85islm/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>854</width>
<height>480</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58243</id>
<title>Basketball Street</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Select your favourite player among the 3 available and show your free throws skills! You have one minute and 25 shots to get as many balls as possible into the basket! Striped balls are worth 2 points (instead of 1): concentrate on these special balls for extra points!</description>
<instructions>Use Mouse To Play and Keyboard</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Arcade, Ball, Ballon, Basketball, Sport </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/xvwtddwzkqcwdcahhsrs5btoza8s218i/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/xvwtddwzkqcwdcahhsrs5btoza8s218i/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>800</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58375</id>
<title>Head ball championship_2</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>my game is based on football and a single 2d game The players head is the main player and the Up arrow and W key jump and Press the left arrow or A key to player move the left side and Right arrow Or D key to player move the Right Side.</description>
<instructions>up arrow key, right arrow key, left arrow key A, W, D</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, 2D, Football </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/m77jn934kb1j9rsltmeeuqvhzt549gc9/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/m77jn934kb1j9rsltmeeuqvhzt549gc9/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>350</width>
<height>600</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57659</id>
<title>Crab Penalty</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the sandy arena of Crab Penalty, where you take on the challenge of scoring goals with an unlikely yet charming player&mdash; a crab! Set on a picturesque beach, this fun and engaging game combines the thrill of penalty shooting with the unique twist of controlling a crab. Aim carefully and use your skills to outsmart the goalie, ensuring your crab kicks the ball into the net. Crab Penalty offers endless entertainment and a delightful seaside adventure. </description>
<instructions>Desktop: Click the mouse left button and swipe the ball . Mobile: Swipe the ball into the goal. </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Animal, Arcade, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/yt8kpi3lpnk6r62jpn7cckge4h9us3ux/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/yt8kpi3lpnk6r62jpn7cckge4h9us3ux/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58193</id>
<title>Football Leauge</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step into the thrill of the stadium with Football League, a fast-paced, action-packed soccer game where you lead your team to victory! Choose your players, master your tactics, and score incredible goals to climb the ranks and become the champion. With intuitive controls, stunning graphics, and dynamic gameplay, Football League delivers an immersive soccer experience for players of all skill levels.</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Tap the right buttons of the mouse to throw the ball to other player. Mobile: Tap the screen to throw the ball to other player. </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>1 Player, Football, NapTech Games, Sport, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/qahsfosbapnzdo3ya16hjf9uudzw7eob/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/qahsfosbapnzdo3ya16hjf9uudzw7eob/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>720</width>
<height>1280</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>58252</id>
<title>Ping Pong Table Tennis</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>In Ping Pong: Table Tennis, you&rsquo;ll enter the exciting world of table tennis matches! This game allows you to enjoy the fun of sports! It&rsquo;s a perfect casual game for every Ping Pong enthusiast.The gameplay is simple and easy to play. Control the ping-pong racket, hit the ball accurately,and react quickly! In every game, use skill and tactics. Beat your opponent and fight for every point. Your opponents will get tougher, try to adjust your strategy and find their weaknesses! </description>
<instructions>Mouse click or tap to play </instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Casual, html5 games, Tennis </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/92la82a07m5svdcghv5t1ytio7bf4q9j/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/92la82a07m5svdcghv5t1ytio7bf4q9j/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>750</width>
<height>1624</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57448</id>
<title>Footy Frenzy</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Step onto the pitch with Footy Frenzy, the ultimate football gaming experience that brings the excitement of the beautiful game to your fingertips! Dive into fast-paced matches, strategize your plays, and score stunning goals. Whether youre playing solo, competing against friends, or taking on opponents from around the world, Footy Frenzy offers immersive gameplay, realistic graphics, and smooth controls that will keep you on the edge of your seat. Get ready to experience the frenzy of football like never before!</description>
<instructions>Desktop: Press the left button of the mouse to move up and down. Mobile: click the up and down button to move caharcter.</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>Football, NapTech Games, Soccer, Sports </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/p90xlik2d70zhis3djsoifasq3ytfxjw/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/p90xlik2d70zhis3djsoifasq3ytfxjw/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1280</width>
<height>720</height>
</item>
<item>
<id>57594</id>
<title>Grid Drifter</title>
<type>html5</type>
<description>Drive the truck through the parking lot with the specified coordinates. Press the arrow keys or the A, D buttons or touch the left and right sides of the phone screen to drive the truck left and right. Avoid if there are other cars.</description>
<instructions>Press A,D butttons or tap screen to play</instructions>
<category>Sports</category>
<tags>drifting, Math, Racing </tags>
<url>https://html5.gamemonetize.com/izcja1nhzk4anp1vzeljy28p66mgvzfp/</url>
<thumb>https://img.gamemonetize.com/izcja1nhzk4anp1vzeljy28p66mgvzfp/512x384.jpg</thumb>
<width>1440</width>
<height>1080</height>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>